{"question": "Which is an album by The Weeknd?", "answers": ["Off the Map", "Echoes of Silence", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "Salival"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Weeknd?", "answers": ["Reggae Legends", "Trilogy", "Red String Tribute", "Live at Pompeii"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Weeknd?", "answers": ["Original Album Series", "The Bonez Tour 2004: Avril's 20th Birthday Party", "In Concert", "House of Balloons"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Weeknd?", "answers": ["One Wild Night", "Made in the Shade", "Thursday", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Weeknd?", "answers": ["From Nashville to Memphis: The Essential '60s Masters", "Inspirations Part I", "Kiss Land", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Lumineers?", "answers": ["Shenanigans", "The Lumineers", "Simply Worship Three", "Gangster and a Gentleman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Music & Me", "Mechanical Bull", "Minutes To Midnight", "Early Avenged Sevenfold releases"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Sounding the Seventh Trumpet", "The Best of Pink Floyd", "In da Club", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Dressed to Kill", "Hail to the King", "Yesterdays", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["9012Live: The Solos", "In the Mix", "Waking The Fallen Demo", "Vampire Weekend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Prairie Wind", "Love Letter", "Martin Scorsese Presents the Blues: Jimi Hendrix", "Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Power Windows", "In da Club", "City of Evil", "Dedication 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["James Arthur", "Megaforce demo", "Halcyon", "Avenged Sevenfold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Ride the Lightning", "Strung Out on Avenged Sevenfold: The String Tribute", "Technical Ecstasy", "In the Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Mixtape Legend", "Comes a Time", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet Re-Release", "Yes Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Waking the Fallen", "Elvis: Viva Las Vegas", "2000 Collection", "Live at Slane Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Live in the LBC & Diamonds in the Rough", "#3", "Earth to Mars", "Death Row: The Lost Sessions Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Guess Who's Back Again", "The Beatles in Mono", "FoREVer", "Dirty Work"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["NASA Music 2: Space Dreams", "All Excess", "King of Majesty", "The Carter Files"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Video Anthology / 1978\u201388", "2000 Demo", "Death Row's Snoop Doggy Dogg Greatest Hits", "The King of Limbs Live From the Basement"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avenged Sevenfold?", "answers": ["Strength Of The World (Single)", "Discovery", "Epic", "An Evening With"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Time to Pretend", "Profiled", "R. Kelly", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["I Am... Yours: An Intimate Performance at Wynn Las Vegas", "21 at 33", "Bad 25", "Full Circle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Live at the Bowl '68", "Men of the World: The Early Years", "Born Is The King", "Overly Dedicated"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Anyway", "Born to Run", "Yellow Submarine", "Limitless and Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["SuperDoors", "Out of Our Heads", "T.R.U. REALigion", "Good Girl Gone Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Playtime Is Over", "Infinite", "The Wall: Live in Berlin", "The Doors Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["The Man Who Sold the World", "The Doors: Vinyl Box Set", "AC/DC in the 20th Century", "Tempest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["The S Dot Carter", "The Soft Parade", "These Days \u2013 Special Edition", "Clinton Sparks Presents: Jay-Z: Live Concert on Smash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Highway 61 Revisited", "Friends", "Acoustic metal", "Live At The Aquarius Theatre: The First Performance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Tokyo Road: Best of Bon Jovi", "The Blueprint 2.1", "Other Voices / Full Circle", "I Walk the Line"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Morrison Hotel", "Lick It Up", "Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "Behind Da Bars"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["All Eyez on Me", "The Essential Iron Maiden", "Late Registration", "The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Queen Ballads", "I Am...", "Ride This Train", "Live at the Aquarius Theatre: The Second Performance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Weird Scenes Inside the Gold Mine", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "The Best of Michael Jackson", "Best Friend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Chapter One", "Other Voices", "Atom Heart Mother", "A Date With Elvis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Open Your Eyes", "Metamorphosis", "Perception", "Home for Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Legacy: The Absolute Best", "Barton Hollow", "Fuckin' Crazy", "You Make Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Singles Collection: The London Years", "In Concert", "Heart of Jamaica", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "Live in Vancouver 1970", "Diamond Dogs", "Doggumentary"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["B Is for Bob", "Soul Rebels", "Live at the Hollywood Bowl", "Hard Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["The One", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Unreleased Tracks", "Strange Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Live in Boston", "Yield", "Oops!...I Did It Again", "Soul Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Kiss Konfidential", "The Best of The Doors", "Iron Maiden", "Seventh Studio Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Positive Mental Octopus", "L.A. Woman", "Born Sinner", "Greatest Video Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["A Real Live One", "Pink Friday", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "An American Prayer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["No Life 'Till Leather", "Tha Massacre (bonus disc)", "Live in Pittsburgh 1970", "Fantasy Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Mellow Moods", "Absolutely Live", "Live at the Roxy", "Reanimation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["GRRR!", "The Future Starts Here: The Essential Doors Hits", "Live at Montreux 2004", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1969-1971", "12 Play", "Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Makaveli 4: Thug in Me", "The Very Best of Prince", "13", "It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away..."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Rap Phenomenon III", "MTV Unplugged", "Bright Midnight: Live in America", "Rumours"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["No Stopping Me", "12 Play: Fourth Quarter", "Boston Live", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Live at the Matrix 1967", "Eagles", "An Introduction to Syd Barrett", "Freedom Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["A Collection", "Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978", "Elvis' Golden Records", "Fan Can 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Madison Blues Live", "The Best of Nirvana", "The Bright Midnight Sampler", "One of These Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Fleetwood Mac", "Live in Detroit", "A Tribute to 2Pac", "Dead Perspective"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["The Music of Korn", "Backstage and Dangerous: The Private Rehearsal", "Because of the Times", "This Is Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Live in New York", "The Lost Planet", "Shangri La", "Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978", "Make It or Break It Videos", "The Rolling Stones", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["\"The Doors \"\"No One Here Gets Out Alive\"\"\"", "En Vivo!", "Buddha Promo", "Meteora"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["The Doors", "From Sea to Shining Sea", "Who's That Girl", "The Diving Board"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["American V: A Hundred Highways", "Caribou", "Pre-Illmatic", "The Very Best of The Doors"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Live on Air", "Scattered Sun", "The Anger Management Tour Live", "Live From Wembley Arena"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Waiting for the Sun", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "The Marshall Mathers LP", "Atom Heart Mother"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Come", "Isle of Wight", "Keys to Ascension 2", "Essential Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Drama", "Nirvana", "Love Death Travel Box Set", "Les 50 Plus Belles Chansons"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["United We Stand", "The Complete Studio Recordings", "A Place at the Table", "Cabin Fever 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of R. Kelly", "More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "Illmatic", "Live in Hollywood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["With the Lights Out", "One Love: 20 Greatest Hits", "Bob Dylan's Greatest Hits", "Live in Philadelphia '70"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Doors?", "answers": ["Saviour King", "Low", "Drama", "The Doors Classics"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The xx?", "answers": ["\u00c6nima", "FACT Mix 70: The xx", "Platinum Collection 2001", "Hybrid Theory"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The xx?", "answers": ["Iron Man", "Fortune", "XX", "A Day at the Races"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The xx?", "answers": ["Rubber Soul", "Red Hot Skate Rock", "Coexist", "The Very Best of Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Most Gigantic Lying Mouth of All Time", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums", "Moist Vagina", "White Collection - Lion Of Zion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Long.Live.A$AP", "Soul Captive", "Show And Prove", "Bob Dylan's Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Ikons", "The Freestyle Manual", "Keys to Ascension", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Backstreet's Back", "For You", "Are You Passionate?", "Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Gold Collection 1970-1971", "The Club Remixes", "Climbing to New Lows", "The Chocolate Invasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["No Sleep 'Til NYC", "And All that Could Have Been", "Fuckin' Crazy", "It's Alright"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Trenchtown Rock", "Taylor Swift", "Reggae Legend", "iTunes Festival: London 2011"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Mr. Timberlake", "The Essential Johnny Cash", "Forever Gold", "How Fly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Bob Marley: Double the Hits", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Led Zeppelin IV", "Oxford's Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Innuendo", "Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits", "The Best of Nas", "I Am... Yours: An Intimate Performance at Wynn Las Vegas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Ben", "Dreadlock Rasta", "Kill All: The Rarities Collection", "In the Present: Live From Lyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Origin of Symmetry", "Flash Gordon", "All The Hits", "Let's Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Hullabaloo Soundtrack", "Dreams of Freedom", "Kinky Reggae", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Club Sonderauflage", "Coffret 4 CD", "Rainbow Country", "Live from London"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Blonde on Blonde", "Live at Madison Square Garden", "GHV2 Megamix", "Chant Down Babylon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["David Bowie", "Going No Where", "The Beatles at the Hollywood Bowl", "Heart of Jamaica"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Metal Up Your Ass", "Toy", "One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001", "Reflections"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Legend: The Best of Bob Marley and the Wailers", "Love and Theft", "Can't Be Tamed", "The Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Elvis Presley", "Diamond Dogs", "The Ray Gillen Years", "Golden Legends"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Black and Blue", "Live @ Lowlands (24.08.2001)", "Bob Marley & Peter Tosh", "The Early Beatles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One", "Shine a Light", "Seven Bridges Road", "Soul Shakedown Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["400 Years", "The Studio Albums 1972-1979", "Elvis: 2nd to None", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Goodies: The Videos & More", "Going No Where", "The Mighty", "Tokyo Tattoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["House of Balloons", "The Mighty Bob Marley", "\"Music From \"\"The Elder\"\"\"", "Jazz"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Downward Spiral", "Late Night Tales: MGMT", "Natural Mystic", "The Top Ten Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Rarities", "Loud", "Encore", "The Platinum Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Absolutely Live", "\u00a1Tr\u00e9!", "Keep on Moving", "A Tribute to 2Pac"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["From Ashy to Classy", "Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "Death of Escobar", "Reggae Lion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Bruce Springsteen with The Sessions Band: Live in Dublin", "The Essential Collection", "Love and Theft", "Live at the BBC"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Essential Jimi Hendrix Volume Two", "Bob Marley", "Rush ABC: Live from Cleveland\u2019s Agora Ballroom 1974", "King of Reggae"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Soul Almighty", "Behind Da Bars", "Backstreet Boys", "Greatest Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Live in Vegas Instrumentals", "The Best of Bob Marley", "Topography: The Yes Anthology", "Symbol Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Gospel Road", "Coexist", "Small Axe", "Led Zeppelin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Golden Hits", "Power Metal demo", "Dreaming Out Loud", "Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Best of Nas", "Soul Rebel", "No Sleep 'Til NYC", "Meteora"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["One Love: 20 Greatest Hits", "A Kind of Magic", "Live in the UK 2008", "Voodoo Child: The Jimi Hendrix Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Legacy CD1", "No More Thank Yous", "Freaked Out & Mixed Up!", "Unplugged Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The World of Bob Marley", "Ultimate Collection", "Other Voices", "The W. Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["No More Thank Yous", "Lively Up Yourself", "The Bends", "Best of Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["No Security", "Freestyle B4 Paystyle", "Les 50 Plus Belles Chansons", "Empire Burlesque"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Bullet in a Bible", "The Complete Best Of", "Born into the 90's", "Union Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Discovery", "Human After All", "Sign 'O' the Times", "From the Vaults Vol.4"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Idiot Computer", "Korn: Collected", "Soul Rebel & Other Great Reggae Hits", "SuperDoors"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["The Great Bob Marley", "Kiss Instant Live", "The Pursuit of Freedom", "Empty Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Sun Is Shining", "God Bless Amerika", "American Idiot: The Original Broadway Cast Recording", "It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away..."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Black Sabbath", "The Best of Bob Marley: 35 Greatest", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Backstreet's Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Faith + Hope + Love", "Because of the Times", "Trench Town Rock", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley?", "answers": ["Woodstock '99 Live Set", "One Love", "The Seventh Coming", "In Utero"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["TP3 Reloaded", "Barbadian Superstardom", "Lateralus", "The White Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["Flashpoint", "Greatest Hits at Studio One", "\u00c6nima", "The Crown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["Revolution", "As Recorded at Madison Square Garden", "Best of 50 Cent", "Loving the Alien"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["Remixed & Revisited", "Plug Me In", "Salival", "Elvis: 2nd to None"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["Riot Act", "Human Touch", "Undertow", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["The Best of Tool", "Labyrinth", "Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume III 1979-1987", "Conscience"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["2000 Collection", "Men of the World: The Early Years", "72826", "Live at the Roxy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tool?", "answers": ["Kerplunk", "Right In Two", "Live in Hyde Park", "The Album Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Darkness on the Edge of Town", "And All that Could Have Been", "Garage Inc.", "Take Off Your Pants and Jacket"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["The Legend", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)", "Dude Ranch", "Before I Self Destruct: The Selects"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Pink Friday", "The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder", "Lyrical Homicide", "1999-06-15: Eddies Attic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Stiff Upper Lip Tour Edition", "The W. Carter Collection 2", "Backstreet Boys", "Icon"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Old Ways", "Live", "Death Row: The Lost Sessions Vol. 1", "Buddha"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["War Angel LP", "Living Things", "Lemmings / Going Nowhere / One Track", "Tokyo Tattoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Access All Areas: A Rock & Roll Odyssey", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls", "The Bright Midnight Sampler", "Cheshire Cat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Best Ballads", "blink-182", "Metallurgy", "Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Old Ways", "The Hits 2000-2006", "I'm Not Dead", "Enema of the State Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Buddha Promo", "Soundtrack Recordings from the Film Jimi Hendrix", "Inside Black Sabbath \u2013 1970\u20131992", "Purple Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["The Ray Gillen Years", "In Da Hood", "It's Only Rock'n Roll", "The Urethra Chronicles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Kornography", "Let It Bleed", "Fly on the Wall", "Enema of the State"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["12 x 5", "Greatest Hits", "Profiled", "Pre-Illmatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Blink-182?", "answers": ["Time Out with Britney Spears", "Neighborhoods", "A Tree with Roots", "Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Journey Through the Past", "Show And Prove", "Oops! I Did It Again: The Best Of Britney Spears", "12 Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Rock of the '70s", "Garage Inc.", "Death of Escobar", "Homegrown"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Everybody's Rockin'", "Coverin'", "Life Is Peachy", "Triumphant (Remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition", "Live Rust", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\" 2\"", "Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["TP.3 Reloaded", "Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works...", "On the Beach", "The Very Best of the Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Old Ways", "Keep On Skanking", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre", "Live After Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Flick of the Switch", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "Trans", "Reality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Live at Massey Hall 1971", "Greatest Hits", "Antrabata Sessions", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Mirror Ball", "Everyday Chemistry", "Over the Counter", "Celebrating Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Blackout", "Re-ac-tor", "Keep the Faith", "Bullet in a Bible"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Yes", "Ragged Glory", "Basic Instinct"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home", "Goodies: The Videos & More", "Hard Rain", "American Stars 'n Bars"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Path of Totality Tour \u2013 Live at the Hollywood Palladium", "Greatest Hits", "Time Stand Still: The Collection", "Physical Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Sugar Mountain - Live At Canterbury House 1968", "Jal Pari", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album", "Burning Desire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Permanent Waves", "Playlist: The Very Best of the Backstreet Boys", "Riverside Blues", "4 Way Street"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Shade 45: Sirius Bizness", "\u00a1Uno!", "Other People's Heartache", "Rust Never Sleeps"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Awake", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Street-Legal", "Psychedelic Pill"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Marley", "Hard Rain", "Comes a Time", "Newpower Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Freedom", "Amnesiac", "The College Dropout", "From Sea to Shining Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Best Tour", "Hot Rocks 1964-1971", "Broken Arrow", "Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Tracks", "Second Night Unplugged", "Decade", "Soul Rebel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Welcome To The Dogg House", "Tonight's the Night", "Pac's Life", "Live on Blueberry Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Soul Rebels", "Meri Kahani", "Queen II", "Neil Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Good Times", "Live in Boston", "Live at the Riverboat 1969", "The Big 10"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Harvest", "The Eminem Show", "The Rainbow Children", "The Lion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Bernstein Tapes", "Essential Rarities", "Melodic Flea Way", "Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Living With War", "Brussels Affair (Live 1973)", "VH1 Storytellers", "NASA Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Most Gigantic Lying Mouth of All Time", "Unplugged", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "Get Rich or Die Tryin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Beatles Box Set", "Rock Island Line", "Lucky Thirteen", "Don't be Fooled by the Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Midnight Lightning", "Latter Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume Two", "The Very Best of Elton John", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Peachtree Road", "Wish You Were Here", "Live on Blueberry Hill", "Road Rock Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["This Note's for You", "Metallurgy", "Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years", "Physical Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Best of 50 Cent", "Fatal Attraction", "Graffiti", "Greendale"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Zuma", "25 Years - The Chain", "Outcesticide IV: Rape of the Vaults", "Snakes & Arrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["The Platinum Collection", "Dreamin Man Live '92", "Avril Lavigne", "Strung Out on Avenged Sevenfold: The String Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["4", "Kiss Sonic Boom Over Europe", "Chrome Dreams", "On Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)", "My World 2.0", "Long May You Run", "The Slim Shady LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Chrome Dreams II", "Simply Worship", "20th Century Masters \u2013 The Millennium Collection: The Best of Kiss", "Pure Heroine"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)", "Return of the Champions", "Harvest Moon", "Headless Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Elvis The King", "A Treasure", "Everybody Loves a Nut", "Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere", "Atom Heart Mother", "Plug Me In", "En Vivo!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Road Trippin' Through Time", "The Number of the Beast", "The Archives Vol. 1 1963\u20131972", "It Was Written"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin III", "A Single Man", "Are You Passionate?", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["B-Sides", "One of the Boys", "Horsemen of the Apocalypse", "Hawks & Doves"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["No More Thank Yous", "American Pie + Best Songs", "Weld", "The Beatles Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["When the Whip Comes Down", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "Invincible", "Sleeps With Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["With the Lights Out", "Le Noise", "2pac", "Unearthed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Recrimination", "Lick It Up", "808s & Heartbreak", "After the Gold Rush"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Bring It On: The Best of Jay-Z", "Jesus Is My Superhero", "B'Day", "Time Fades Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Dance of Death", "Live at the Fillmore East", "Monster", "Wake Up!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Neil Young?", "answers": ["Land of the Free Home of the Brave", "The Singles Boxset (Previously Unreleased bonus disc)", "Soul Almighty", "Prairie Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Live at Wembley '86", "Blue Hawaii", "The Power of Your Love", "Nevermind: The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 9 \u2013 The Witmark Demos: 1962\u20131964", "Greatest Singles Collection", "Overwhelmed"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Forever Gold", "Die for Me", "BBC Archives 1967-1969", "Nimrod"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Another Side of Bob Dylan", "Load", "After the Gold Rush", "Into the Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Bleach", "Animalize", "Reality", "War Angel LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["The Ladder", "The Essential Fleetwood Mac", "G Unit General", "It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away..."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Outcesticide III: The Final Solution", "The Future Starts Here: The Essential Doors Hits", "Makaveli 2: The Lost Album", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Harvest", "World Without End", "The Platinum Collection Volume 2: Shout to the Lord 2", "Live at the Matrix 1967"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["A Saucerful of Secrets", "Live @ The Apollo", "Smells Like Nirvana", "Super Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["The Long Run", "Golden Collection", "Jump Up!", "Fly by Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Cash Cow", "Songs of Our Soil", "Morrison Hotel", "Glitter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin II", "Live in Hyde Park", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\"\"", "#3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Outcesticide IV: Rape of the Vaults", "GRRR!", "In the Present: Live From Lyon", "Queen II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["The College Dropout: Mixtape Version", "Dark Emotion", "Satisfy My Soul", "Detroit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Nevermind", "Death of Escobar", "Dead Perspective", "YesYears"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Br\u00fctal Legend Original Soundtrack", "One Nite Alone... Live!", "I Am... World Tour", "Incesticide"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Preaching the Blues", "Barbadian Superstardom", "My Worlds Acoustic", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\" 2\""], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Smokefest", "The Gospel According to David Bowie", "With the Lights Out", "The Essential Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Never Gone", "Fecal Matter", "Innocence And Instinct", "Ragged Old Flag"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Flashpoint", "Hell Freezes Over", "Tunnel of Love", "The Very Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Live on Ten Legs", "The I Heart Revolution: We're All in This Together", "Rarities", "2112"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["In the Raw", "Merry Christmas II You", "Cross Purposes Live", "Live: Friday the 13th"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Live in Boston", "Unhappy", "Ciara", "Avicii Presents Strictly Miami"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "By Your Side", "Live At Reading", "Greatest Hits Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Catch a Fire", "I Can't Live", "Around the World in a Day", "Avenged Sevenfold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Still I Rise", "The Gospel Road", "Fatal Attraction", "Until We Have Faces"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["MMM...COOKIES - Sweet Hamster Like Jewels from America!", "Let's Cheers to This", "Alive II", "Outcesticide V: Disintegration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Circus", "Live at Bonnaroo", "Nirvana", "Born to Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Dehumanizer", "Playlist: The Very Best of Ciara", "MTV Unplugged in New York", "No Bull: The Director's Cut"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Houses of the Holy", "Moist Vagina", "Flight School", "Live From the Atlantic Studios"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["In the Beginning", "Toy", "Seventh Heaven", "Listen to This Eddie"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Confessions Remixed", "Goats Head Soup", "The Chosen Rejects", "Live: 2 CD Collector's Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Then Play On", "Down With Me", "I'm Not Dead", "Buddha Promo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Dressed to Kill", "Born Sinner", "In Utero", "Jay-Z: Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Class of '06: World's Best Dressed Label Under G.O.O.D Music", "Live in Miami", "Essential Rarities", "Heroes and Heroin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "Madonna: Dalle Origini Al Mito", "Fly by Night", "Rare Unreleased"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Preaching the Blues", "In a Valley by the Sea", "19", "The Eternal Legacy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Maximum Rock N' Roll", "Outcesticide: In Memory of Kurt Cobain", "Unplugged", "Ballbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Jewels", "Rated R", "The Best of Nirvana", "Duets"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Number Ones", "Wish You Were Here / Early Singles", "Grunge Is Dead", "Black and Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Love & Death", "Overexposed", "Animalize", "Age of Giants"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["After the Gold Rush", "Unreleased Tracks", "Experience Hendrix: The Best of Jimi Hendrix", "Reggae Lion"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Sliver: The Best of the Box", "Merry Christmas II You", "Can You Handle Mine?", "Orange Blossom Special"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Michael Jackson's Vision", "Off the Map", "Innuendo", "Twilight of the Gods"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Show And Prove", "Nevermind It's an Interview", "Tupac: Resurrection", "On Stage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Eddie's Head", "Avril Lavigne", "Pyass", "Smells Like Punk Spirit"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["ICON", "Britney", "King of Reggae", "The Downward Spiral"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Demi", "Rush Replay X 3", "20Ten", "Virgin Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Elton John One Night Only \u2013 The Greatest Hits", "Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks", "Live 1994", "In Through the Out Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Cole World: The Sideline Story", "The Here After", "Rare Traxx"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nirvana?", "answers": ["Live at Woodstock", "Dynamic Live", "Meddle", "Snoop Dogg Presents Christmas in tha Dogg House"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Vampire Weekend?", "answers": ["The Black Sabbath Story", "Contra", "Cornerstone EP", "Lively Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Vampire Weekend?", "answers": ["The Jam Machine", "Raw & Uncut", "The Rising Queen", "Modern Vampires of the City"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Vampire Weekend?", "answers": ["Curtis", "Eagles Live", "The Dynasty: Roc La Familia", "Vampire Weekend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Muhammad Ali?", "answers": ["Feel", "Favourite Worst Nightmare", "I am the Greatest", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Tha Carter", "Slow Train Coming", "Mother's Milk", "Makaveli 6"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Songs of Life and Hope", "Late Registration", "Broken", "Tha Carter II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["ChangesOneBowie", "The Carter III", "Great White Wonder", "Keep on Moving"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Wicked Man's Rest", "The Remix Suite", "Lollipop (remix)", "Valleys of Neptune"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["All That There Ever Was (1988-2008)", "Icon", "The W. Carter Collection 2", "The Best of J. Hova"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Tha Block Is Hot", "Sign 'O' the Times", "All of the Above", "Aha Shake Heartbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["At the Apollo", "Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978", "SQ6", "A Tribute to 2Pac"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The T-Wayne Show", "Hot in the Shade", "White Collection - Lion Of Zion", "Sun Is Shining"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Black Tie White Noise", "Keys to Ascension", "Da Drought 3", "Fantasy Ride"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Remixes (vinyl)", "The Drought Is Over 5", "Lollapalooza '92", "Oklahoma City 1972"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Lil Wayne: Suffix", "YesStory", "The Best of AC/DC", "Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["SQ5", "Makaveli 6", "The Very Best of Prince", "Makaveli 2: When My Enemies Fall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["R.", "Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005", "Eminem is Back", "The Drought Is Over Pt. 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Final Cut", "June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets", "Call And Response: The Remix Album", "Dedication 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Live: Walmart Soundcheck CD+DVD", "Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "The Love Songs", "No Ceilings"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Live in Vancouver", "The Greatest Rapper Alive", "Essential Mixes", "Right In Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Graffiti Bridge", "My Face Can\u2019t Be Felt", "December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)", "Is There Anybody out There? The Wall Live 1980-81"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Farewell My Summer Love", "Around the World in a Day", "Get Yer Ya-Ya's Out!", "The W. Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Radiohead Box Set", "Greatest Hits", "The Pursuit of Freedom", "Goodies / The Evolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Scummy Man", "Never Say Die!", "KoRn Live at CBGBs", "Da Drought 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Greatest!", "The Drought Is Over", "blink-182", "Deuce"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Amused to Death", "OK Computer", "The Ray Gillen Years", "Tha Carter IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Talk That Talk", "Alive!", "Live in Pittsburgh 1970", "The Drought Is Over 2: The Carter 3 Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "N.E.W.S.", "I Am Not a Human Being II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Dedication 1", "Headless Cross", "Hannah Montana 3", "Keys to Ascension"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Overwhelmed", "LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "Greatest Kiss", "Rich Gang: Flashy Lifestyle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Beatles Collection", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\"\"", "Sorry 4 the Wait", "Physical Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Sunfly Gold Vol. 34: Linkin Park & Limp Bizkit", "Queen Collection", "Summer Carter", "Vol. 2... Hard Knock Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["I Can't Feel My Face", "Beatlemania! With the Beatles", "Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Loyal to the Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Southern G'z", "Unbreakable", "Hannah Montana: Hits Remixed", "The Black Chronic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Weezy Evolution", "The Freestyle Show", "Get Well Soon...", "A Total Waste of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Live at Pompeii", "Pretty Hate Machine", "How the West Was Won", "Lights Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Batman", "Nothing Was the Same", "Fecal Matter", "Mardi Gras"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Ghetto Barbie", "Trouble Remixes", "News of the World", "I Am Not a Human Being"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Between the Buttons", "Tha Carter 2.5", "Killers", "Bromance (remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Rose That Grew From Concrete", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)", "Tha Carter III", "Musicology"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["First Rays of the New Rising Sun", "The Carter Files", "Bare Trees", "Hell Freezes Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Lyrical Homicide", "Ciara", "Hits of the Eagles", "Remixed & Revisited"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Rebirth", "Live in Hollywood", "Doggystyle", "Oooh What a Green Day!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Born to Run", "S&M", "Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits", "Tha Carter III: The Rebirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["The Unplanned Mixtape", "The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder", "Ghetto Superstar", "Dedication 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "Keep the Faith: An Evening with Bon Jovi", "Taylor Allderdice", "Speak Now - World Tour Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Tha Drought", "Better Dayz", "Korn", "Woodstock '99 Live Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "The Prefix", "A Date With Elvis", "Live 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Ozzy Meets the Priest", "Halcyon", "The Road to Carter 4", "Second Semester"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Fleetwood Mac in Chicago", "Queen Rock Montreal", "In a Word: Yes (1969\u2013)", "New orleans nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Tha Carter 2.7", "Stone Cold Classics (Limited Edition)", "Graffiti Bridge", "Panjaban"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lil Wayne?", "answers": ["Singing Between the Lines", "Great White Wonder", "500 Degreez", "Chaos and Disorder"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Heaven and Hell", "Here and There", "Cabala", "Teenage Dream: The Complete Confection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["17-11-70", "Long.Live.A$AP", "The Sabbath Collection", "Retrospective I: 1974-1980"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Best of Bob Marley", "13", "Behind the Mask", "Live at Budokan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Pac-Man Punch", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)", "Training Day", "Sabotage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1973-1982", "Live at Lollapalooza 2007", "The Last Supper", "Keys to Ascension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Stadium Arcadium", "Killers", "Loose Ends", "The Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["1999", "The Beatles' First", "Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978", "R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Brand New Eyes", "Sound + Vision", "Freshmen Adjustment 2", "The Eternal Idol"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Live at the Hollywood Bowl", "Under Wheels of Confusion", "Live from Live Earth", "Animals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["One Love: The Very Best Of", "The Rules of Hell", "Shine a Light", "Katy Hudson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Don't be Fooled by the Name", "Super Strong God", "One Love: 20 Greatest Hits", "Technical Ecstasy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["One Love: The Very Best Of", "Born Again", "Stranger Than Fiction", "A Saucerful of Secrets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Land of the Free Home of the Brave", "The Very Best of Black Sabbath", "Live at the Gorge 05/06", "Beneath the Boardwalk"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Tyr", "Amused to Death", "Mylo Xyloto", "Get the Funk Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Club Sonderauflage", "The Studio Albums 1990\u20132009", "If You Want Blood You've Got It", "Reggae Lion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Iron Man", "One of These Nights", "VH1 Storytellers: Uncut", "Uno... Dos... Tr\u00e9!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Essentially Yes", "12 x 5", "Rare Traxx", "The Ozzy Osbourne Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Works", "50 Cent Is the Future", "Reggae Legend", "Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Rolling Stones Rock and Roll Circus", "All Excess", "That's the Way Through the Out Door", "Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Bridges to Babylon", "T.R.U. REALigion", "This Is Our God", "Black Box: The Complete Original Black Sabbath (1970\u20131978)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["After Curtis", "Absolutely Live", "Mob Rules", "New orleans nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Black Sabbath", "Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania", "Come Around Sundown", "Lushlife Presents: West Sounds"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["DJ Mix", "Never Say Die!", "Confrontation", "The Doors"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse", "Killers", "Desperado", "The Black Sabbath Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon II: The Legend of Mr. Rager", "Seventh Star", "Doorie", "A Treasure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Mighty Bob Marley", "Inside Black Sabbath \u2013 1970\u20131992", "Kingdom Come", "Saved"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Tha Dogg: Best of the Works", "Archangel Rides Again", "Oracular Spectacular", "Hope"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Keep on Moving", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts-live album", "If You Want Blood You've Got It", "Live Evil"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs", "Hard Rain", "Master of Reality", "Kingdom Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Sabbath Stones", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "Lucky Thirteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970", "Rays of Light", "Dehumanizer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Bible According to Black Sabbath", "Friday Night Lights", "Rolling Papers", "For Badgeholders Only"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Purple Sabbath", "This Note's for You", "Love Letter", "Miss Swing Miss Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour", "The Ray Gillen Years", "2Pacalypse Now", "Malice N Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Makaveli 4: Thug in Me", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Life Is Good", "Past Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["And Their Name Was Treason", "Black Sabbath Vol. 4", "Say You Will", "Friday Night Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "The Miracle", "Madonna Remixed", "Sabbath Bloody Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Keys to Ascension 2", "Tokyo Tattoo", "Blackest Sabbath", "Death Row: Snoop Doggy Dogg at His Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Kings of Hell", "Sigh No More", "The Freestyle Manual", "How Fly"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Empty Sky", "Radiohead Box Set", "Acoustic metal", "Cross Purposes Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Labyrinth", "Daft Club", "Live at Last", "The Best of The Doors"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["The Marshall Mathers LP 2", "Sheer Heart Attack", "We Sold Our Soul for Rock 'n' Roll", "More Than Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Elvis' Christmas Album", "Iron Man: The Best of Black Sabbath", "The Legend of Eagles", "Farewell My Summer Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["In the Zone / Britney", "Cross Purposes", "The Best Of", "Mellow Moods"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Aladdin Sane", "Daft Club", "Rebel Music", "Black Sabbath: The Dio Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 10 \u2013 Another Self Portrait", "Loveland", "Br\u00fctal Legend Original Soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of R. Kelly", "The Mighty Bob Marley", "Forbidden", "Lushlife Presents: West Sounds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Daydream", "Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big", "Paranoid", "\"The Doors \"\"No One Here Gets Out Alive\"\"\""], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Serious Business DJ Clue & Keyz Collaboration", "Live at the Fillmore East", "Born This Way", "Ozzy Meets the Priest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "Union Live", "Headless Cross", "AC/DC in the 20th Century"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Black Sabbath?", "answers": ["Live at Hammersmith Odeon", "It's That Girl", "Absolute Greatest", "Cornerstone EP"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jake Bugg?", "answers": ["Keep the Faith", "Jake Bugg", "En Vivo!", "Good Times"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jake Bugg?", "answers": ["xero", "Archives", "One Love: 20 Greatest Hits", "Shangri La"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Wanted?", "answers": ["Outside", "Britney Spears: Live and More!", "A Kid Named Cudi", "The Wanted (Special Edition)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Flash Gordon", "Spring Break... Here To Party", "Pyass", "The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["World Without End", "In Rainbows: From the Basement", "See You on the Other Side", "The Fame Kingdom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["In His Own Words", "Artpop", "Songs About Jane", "Great White Wonder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["NASA Music", "The Fame", "Power Windows", "Lost Highway: The Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["The Passion of Tupac", "The Remix", "My Worlds Acoustic", "Like a Virgin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["The Best Of", "Small Axe", "A Year Without Rain", "Born This Way: The Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Get Rich or Die Tryin'", "iTunes Session", "Weezy Evolution", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Soul Almighty", "Venus", "The Indispensable Collection", "Live: 2 CD Collector's Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Lady Gaga?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "Jump Back: The Best of the Rolling Stones", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Rebirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Disclosure?", "answers": ["Remix City Vol. 1", "Essential Mixes", "Settle", "Reload"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Disclosure?", "answers": ["FACT Mix 327: Disclosure", "Revolution", "Hard Rain", "Classic Yes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Neidermayer's Mind", "Teenage Dream: The Complete Confection", "A Thing Called Love", "The Great Bob Marley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Katy Hudson", "Greatest Street Hitz", "Underground 3.0", "The Man Who Sold the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Breakout", "MTV Unplugged", "Indigo Nights", "Live @ Rex Club Paris"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Bon Jovi", "Powerage", "Stages", "(A) Katy Perry"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Songs for Communion", "GHV2 Megamix", "Follow the Leader", "One of the Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "The Jimi Hendrix Concerts", "On Stage", "Prism"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Katy Perry?", "answers": ["Teenage Dream", "No Ceilings", "Golden Ballads", "Too Low for Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Golden Hits", "NKOTBSB", "The Eminem Show", "Revenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["The Originals", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Hell Best", "Desire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Jigoku-Retsuden", "Early Avenged Sevenfold releases", "Backstreet Boys", "The Bernstein Tapes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Absolutely Live", "Live From Wembley Arena", "The Promise", "Love Gun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Alive III", "Dude Ranch", "A Date With Elvis", "Jimi Plays Monterey"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Call And Response: The Remix Album", "Ultimate Queen", "Fire: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Carnival of Souls: The Final Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Mr. Wonderful", "Killers", "Other People's Heartache", "Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Days Are Gone", "Believe", "Picture My Pain", "Ikons"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Spirit and Truth", "Gold", "Westside Reloaded", "Help!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Live from London", "KISS Alive! 1975-2000", "More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "The Crush Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["18 Months", "Animalize", "I Can't Feel My Face", "Only By the Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Rock 'n' Roll Music", "The Green Day Collection", "Destroyer- Resurrected", "No Security"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Lick It Up", "Greatest Hits", "The Beatles' First", "Crush"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Invincible", "Remix Project", "Still I Rise", "Kiss Symphony: The DVD"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Up All Night", "Ready 4 War", "My Worlds: The Collection", "Crazy Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Creatures of the Night", "Cunning Stunts", "The Next Level", "Greatest Hits (Disc 1)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Live on Air", "Unapologetic", "Kiss Konfidential", "Born This Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Sex Therapy", "Who You Are", "The Very Best of Kiss", "The Studio Albums 1972-1979"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Goodies / The Evolution", "Abbey Road", "Kiss My Ass: The Video", "World Ballads Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["At the Apollo", "Chikara", "In Rainbows", "Daft Punk Live in NYC"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Test for Echo", "Pure Michael: Motown a Cappella", "KISSology Volume One: 1974\u20131977", "Thursday"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Strung Out on Avenged Sevenfold: The String Tribute", "Clockwork Angels", "Asylum", "Behind the Mask"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Animalize Live Uncensored", "Johnny Cash With His Hot and Blue Guitar", "Backspacer", "Live in Boston"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["20th Century Masters \u2013 The Millennium Collection: The Best of Kiss", "Michael Jackson's This Is It", "From Under the Cork Tree", "S. Carter: The Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Artpop", "Aftermath", "Psycho Circus", "The Tears Of Medusa"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["12 x 5", "American Life", "Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "Hot in the Shade"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Delicate Sound of Thunder", "Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005", "Loyal to the Game", "Hotter Than Hell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Destroyer", "20Ten", "The Final Frontier", "Lo nuevo y lo mejor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Get Yer Ya-Ya's Out!", "Rock the Nation Live!", "Live from SoHo", "Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Love", "Kiss Unplugged", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet", "Halcyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Early Avenged Sevenfold releases", "Flight of the Crow", "Kiss Chronicles: 3 Classic Albums", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["The Sabbath Collection", "Fleetwood Mac in Chicago", "Unmasked", "Peachtree Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Alive!", "Lollapalooza '92", "This Left Feels Right: Greatest Hits With a Twist", "Sugar Mountain - Live At Canterbury House 1968"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Alive II", "Talk", "Radio K.A.O.S.", "Power Metal demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["It Won't Be Soon Before Long", "\"Music From \"\"The Elder\"\"\"", "Sector 1", "Memories: The '68 Comeback Special"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Dynasty", "Femme Fatale / Circus", "Pretty Hate Machine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Shout to the Lord", "Box Set", "Greatest Hits", "Sex Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["All Ice on Me", "Video Pieces", "Kiss Instant Live", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Waking the Fallen", "Rock and Roll Over", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "The Path of Totality"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["All of the Above", "Unfinished Business", "Merry Christmas II You", "Double Platinum"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Symphony: Alive IV", "Houses of the Holy", "Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Monster", "Binaural", "Relapse", "In the Heart of Sin City"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Sliver: The Best of the Box", "Basic Instinct", "Kiss Sonic Boom Over Europe", "Road to Recovery: Withdrawal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Get Freeze It", "Vampire Weekend", "Dressed to Kill", "Collection: 1973 - 2012"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Lo nuevo y lo mejor", "Speak Now - World Tour Live", "The Rules of Hell", "Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Greatest Kiss", "Facedown", "Planet Earth", "Rare Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kiss?", "answers": ["Exile on Main St.", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre", "Live 2003", "Sonic Boom"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Malice N Wonderland", "The Best of the Wailers", "Mardi Gras", "Star Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Taylor Allderdice", "Tha Carter III: The Rebirth", "Dookie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Melodic Flea Way", "Tha Carter II", "Flight School", "Stone Cold Classics (Limited Edition)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Maiden England", "Live at Last", "Relapse", "Grow Season"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Goodies: The Videos & More", "Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania", "The Collection 1973-84", "MDNA World Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Beast over Hammersmith", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Reuben Morgan", "Tempest", "Kush & Orange Juice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Love Death Travel Box Set", "The Chronic 2010", "Kiss & Tell", "Hallucinogenic Recipe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["The Complete BBC Radio Sessions", "St. Anger (studio rehearsals)", "Rolling Papers", "Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Acoustic metal", "Mac & Devin Go to High School", "The Buddha of Suburbia", "The Beat"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Burn After Rolling", "Bounce", "The Massacre", "2 of One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["The Platinum Collection", "Prince of the City 2", "Chant Down Babylon", "MTV Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Cabin Fever", "Live in Detroit", "A Collection", "0 Fucks Given"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Deal or No Deal", "Future Games", "Before the Flood", "Tokyo 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Outside", "Bringing It All Back Home", "Echoes of Silence", "Show And Prove"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Golden Collection", "How Fly", "Led Zeppelin Boxed Set", "Never Done Before"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["Cabin Fever 2", "Rainbow Bridge", "Something Else", "Three Kings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Wiz Khalifa?", "answers": ["A Total Waste of Time", "O.N.I.F.C.", "You Can Dance", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Talk", "The Road to El Dorado", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["2pac", "FACT Mix 70: The xx", "Die for Me", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["M!ssundaztood", "Untouchables", "Live in Vegas Instrumentals", "The Beatles' Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Immortal", "\u2026and Justice for All", "B'Day", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["FutureSex/LoveSounds", "Speak My Mind", "Neon Lights", "Barbadian Superstardom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Off the Map", "Revolver", "I Am... World Tour", "Best Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Alphabet St.", "Revolution", "Greatest Hits at Studio One", "Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works..."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["God Is In The House", "Greatest Hits", "Neon Lights", "Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It) Dance Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["In Utero", "Miss Swing Miss Soul", "American Idiot", "Gotham City Clubbin Part 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["XX", "Ring the Alarm: Remixes", "Is There Anybody out There? The Wall Live 1980-81", "Die for Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["And All that Could Have Been", "4", "As Recorded at Madison Square Garden", "Who's the New Girl?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah", "The Best Songs R&B", "Paradise Valley", "I Am... Yours: An Intimate Performance at Wynn Las Vegas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Who's That Girl", "I Am\u2026 Sasha Fierce", "Live 1994", "Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Glitter", "Time to Pretend", "4 Intimate Nights With Beyonc\u00e9", "This Is Our God"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Live at Wembley", "Red", "Pre-Illmatic", "Live in Australia with the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Beyonc\u00e9?", "answers": ["Dangerously in Love", "Greatest Hits 1973-1982", "Dreams of Freedom", "Aladdin Sane"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Tokyo Road (live)", "Live in Vancouver", "Household Objects", "The Blueprint 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Bring It On: The Best of Jay-Z", "Ten", "Release the Panic", "Boy in Detention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Sings the Ballads of the True West", "The Black Album: Acappella", "Are You Passionate?", "Suck It and See"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Tailgates & Tanlines", "Planet Waves", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "Magna Carta... Holy Grail"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Chosen Rejects", "The Streets Is Watching", "The Long Run", "Pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Path of Totality Tour \u2013 Live at the Hollywood Palladium", "Greatest Hits", "Here We Go Again", "Smokefest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\"\"", "The Commission", "Gangster and a Gentleman", "God's Plan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Serious Business DJ Clue & Keyz Collaboration", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge", "The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Best of the 'B' Sides"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Natural Mystic", "The Black Chronic", "Bob Marley", "\"The \"\"Demo\"\" Tape\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["18 Months", "S. Carter: The Remix", "All We Know Is Falling", "iTunes Festival: London 2011"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Infinity on High", "Lost Dogs", "The Late Mixtape", "S.Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["AM", "Talwar", "Vol. 2... Hard Knock Life", "ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The S Dot Carter", "Flight School", "When the Wind Blows", "John Wesley Harding"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["\"Music From \"\"The Elder\"\"\"", "Rocks Germany 2001", "Kingdom Come", "Hail to the Thief"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse", "Kiss Konfidential", "Tha Carter II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["BBC Archives 1970-1971", "The Blueprint 2.1", "Human After All: Remixes", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["I am the Greatest", "Fortune", "Rap Phenomenon III", "Virtual Zabriskie Point"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Chapter One: Greatest Hits", "Young Americans", "The New Breed", "Going No Where"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Latin Album", "Songs of Life and Hope", "Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "C-Note"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Neon Lights", "Radiohead Box Set", "Hope", "My President Is Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Fade 2 Black - The Mixtape", "Homesick", "Halcyon Days", "Gagging Order: Acoustic Renditions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001", "American Gangster", "Eminem & Friends", "Asylum"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Virtual XI", "The Platinum Collection", "The Purple Album", "Counterparts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Something New", "Soled Out", "Freedom Songs", "Let's Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Platinum Collection \u201999", "Johnny B. Goode", "Watch the Throne", "Story of My Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Heroes and Heroin", "Get Freeze It", "In the Present: Live From Lyon", "The (Unofficial) Black Album Remix (vs. Paul Nice)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Bernstein Tapes", "The Dynasty: Roc La Familia", "Songs of Freedom", "DJ Mix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "Live in Texas", "Rocafella", "Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Live in Texas", "Because of the Times", "The Black Album", "Live: 2 CD Collector's Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Jay-Z: Unplugged", "500 Degreez", "Accoustic Concert Live Performance", "Limitless and Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Trilogy", "The Black & Tan Album", "Decks n' Drums n' 909", "Iron Man: The Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Magnification", "Better Dayz", "Grace Under Pressure", "God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Echoes of Silence", "Morning Symphony Ideas", "The Slim Shady LP", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Clinton Sparks Presents: Jay-Z: Live Concert on Smash", "Tha Doggfather", "Led Zeppelin BBC Sessions", "Boy in Detention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Magical Mystery Tour", "Chapter One", "White America", "The Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["HOWWA 2", "Live at Lollapalooza 2007", "Looking Back at...", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Trin-i-tee 5:7", "The Blueprint", "Live @ Lowlands (24.08.2001)", "The Crown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Number Ones", "Howwa 3 Dynastia", "After the Gold Rush", "SQ5"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Jatt Soorme", "Blond Ambition World Tour Live", "The Best of J. Hova", "Toy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Reasonable Doubt", "Kiss the Sky", "blink-182", "Union Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["Demi", "Unfinished Business", "B.O.A.T.S. II: Me Time", "Master of Puppets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Art of Letting Go", "The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One", "The Best of Both Worlds", "Human Touch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["2 of One", "Voodoo Soup", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Best Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jay-Z?", "answers": ["The Uplift Mofo Party Plan", "Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter", "Christiane F.: Wir Kinder vom Bahnhof Zoo", "Elvis' Christmas Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red?", "answers": ["All Ice on Me", "Live From Wembley Arena", "Release the Panic", "Runaway Love (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red?", "answers": ["Red Hot Skate Rock", "Counterparts", "Until We Have Faces", "Pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red?", "answers": ["Innocence And Instinct", "Diamond Collection", "The Wiz: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack", "Ozzy Meets the Priest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red?", "answers": ["Indigo Nights", "Pin Ups", "Cross Purposes", "Red String Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red?", "answers": ["White America", "Ten", "End of Silence", "Trap-A-Velli"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Double Up", "The Singles Collection", "Wish You Were Here", "All the World's a Stage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Tree Full of Secrets", "The Drought Is Over", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions (American Land Edition)", "Uprising"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Smoking Blues", "Flies on the Soundboard", "Purest Feeling", "Automatic Gunfire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Blueprint", "Fat Old Gigs", "The World of Bob Marley", "2Pac & Friends"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Obscurity", "Live at Slane Castle", "Save Rock and Roll", "Issues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["A Nice Pair", "Dressed to Kill", "The Best Songs R&B", "From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Tha Carter 2.7", "A Day at the Races", "The Future Is Now", "The Best of Pink Floyd: A Foot in the Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "Die for Me", "Oooh What a Green Day!", "The Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Power Dance Hits", "The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "The 20/20 Experience \u2013 2 of 2", "For the Fans (disc 2)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["At the Beeb", "Atom Heart Mother", "Booze Blues N' Tattoos", "Dedication 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Early Avenged Sevenfold releases", "Black Sabbath Vol. 4", "The Complete Greatest Hits", "Pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["My Favorite Videos (So Far)", "Boy in Detention", "Led Zeppelin Boxed Set", "The Film-soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["More", "The Fame Kingdom", "The Johnny Cash Children's Album", "Dehumanizer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Madonna Remixed", "Tonite Let's All Make Love in London... Plus", "Don't Forget", "Minutes to Midnight - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Carter III", "I'm Breathless", "Shine On", "E=MC\u00b2 Adventure Box"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["A Real Dead One", "BBC Archives 1970-1971", "God Is Able", "Slow Train Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Kaya", "Live at River Plate", "Long Time No See", "Stranger Than Fiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["not my fault", "Settle", "Training Day", "Amsterdam '69"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Best of Pink Floyd", "On the Beach", "St. Anger (studio rehearsals)", "Early Classics"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["A Collection of Great Dance Songs", "Rare", "In Nuce", "Seven Bridges Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Animals", "Rare Masters", "Kiss Chronicles: 3 Classic Albums", "Rainbow Bridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Best of the Pink Floyd / Masters of Rock", "Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "Remixed & Revisited", "Tha Carter 2.7"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["50 Best Songs \u2013 The Motown Years: Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "12 Play", "The Embryo", "The Promise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Live at Wembley '86", "Chronicles", "Elvis", "Virtual Zabriskie Point"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Chapter One: Greatest Hits", "Greatest Hits '94", "Wish You Were Here / Early Singles", "Carry the Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Immaculate Collection", "Queen", "The Complete Zabriskie Point Sessions", "A Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Crown", "Love and Theft", "Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "Rock and Roll Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Desperado", "Relics", "Astral Traveller", "I Am... World Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Late Mixtape", "Playlist: The Very Best of Ciara", "The Mighty Bob Marley", "The Division Bell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Close to the Edge", "Rock to the Rock", "Pyass", "Rainbow Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Madonna", "The Final Cut", "Berlin Trilogy", "For Bon Far Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "The Dark Side of the Moon", "Deal or No Deal", "S&M"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Black Sabbath", "Crystal Ball", "Mob Rules", "An Introduction to Syd Barrett"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Meddle", "The Sabbath Collection", "Awesome as Fuck", "Unsurpassed Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Obscured by Clouds", "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "Voodoo Lounge", "King Creole"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Unplugged Again", "Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida", "R U Still Down? (Remember Me)", "A Saucerful of Secrets"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Rhapsody in Pink: The Psychedelic Years", "For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)", "Tribute", "One Wild Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Dynamic Live", "Live at Pompeii", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album", "Rock of the Westies"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Keep the Faith", "Greatest Hits Live", "A Momentary Lapse of Reason", "Red String Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Space Odyssey", "Is There Anybody out There? The Wall Live 1980-81", "The Best of Snoop Dogg", "Moody Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Kanye West Presents: Promise", "Discovery", "Live @ The Apollo", "Don't Call Me Marshall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Works", "The Doors Box Set", "Queen 40", "The S Dot Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Erotica", "For All You've Done", "Zabriskie Point", "Coexist"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Household Objects", "SuperDoors", "Rarities", "Headless Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Love Letter", "The Best of Eagles", "The Freestyle Show", "Interstellar Encore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["7800\u00b0 Fahrenheit", "Collaborations", "Ozzy Meets the Priest", "Ummagumma"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["The Revival", "The Wall Singles Collection", "Yesterdays", "GHV2 Megamix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Definitive Collection Mini LP Replica CD Boxset", "AM", "ISELECT", "What Syd Wants"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Sky High: Presented by DJ Benzi and Plain Pat", "An American Prayer", "Fight (For Your Cause)", "BBC Archives 1967-1969"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink Floyd?", "answers": ["Delicate Sound of Thunder", "Live in Vegas Instrumentals", "Great Country Songs", "Planet Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Manny Pacqui\u00e1o?", "answers": ["Merry Christmas", "Sticky & Sweet Tour Live in Buenos Aires", "The Best of Nirvana", "Pac-Man Punch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Manny Pacqui\u00e1o?", "answers": ["Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Laban Nating Lahat Ito", "A Farewell to Kings", "Born Sinner"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Future?", "answers": ["Long Time No See", "Bon Scott Rarities", "I\u2019m With You", "Pluto"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Future?", "answers": ["Hell Best", "Waking Up", "The Rolling Stones", "Free Bricks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Oxford Devils", "The Road to El Dorado", "The 20/20 Experience: The Complete Experience", "Time to Pretend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Scary Monsters (and Super Creeps)", "Never Say Never: The Remixes", "Daytrotter Session-live album", "Black Sabbath Vol. 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["MGMT", "Laban Nating Lahat Ito", "Live at the BBC", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["...Baby One More Time / Oops!... I Did It Again", "Climbing to New Lows", "Golden Ballads", "Ghetto Barbie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Lucky Town", "Greatest Hits", "Codeine Cowboy (A 2 Chainz Collective)", "Late Night Tales: MGMT"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["End of Silence", "American Life/Music", "Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks", "Live @ Glastonbury '08-live album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones", "Friends", "Oracular Spectacular", "Ultimate Collection Volume II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Classic", "Night Visions", "Live @ Coachella '08-live album", "F.A.M.E."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by MGMT?", "answers": ["Tokyo 1990", "Relapse", "Viva la Vida / X&Y", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts-live album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Believe (Acoustic)", "Greatest Hits", "Barbadian Superstardom", "iTunes Live From SoHo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["The Essential Elvis Presley", "Rare Masters", "Taylor Swift", "Purest Feeling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Household Objects", "Maximum Rock N' Roll", "Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1", "Connect Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Cross Purposes Live", "Unplugged", "Speak Now", "Recovery"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Boss's Birthday Party", "White Collection - Lion Of Zion", "Speak Now - World Tour Live", "Stop That Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Paramore", "Red", "Archives", "Aftermath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Taylor Swift?", "answers": ["Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs", "Can't Tell Me Nothing: The Official Mixtape", "Fearless", "And All that Could Have Been"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tamar?", "answers": ["Love and War", "Live. Love. ASAP", "Good Girl Gone Bad (remix bonus disc)", "Amazing Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tamar?", "answers": ["Tamar", "Metallica Live in Concert", "Shenanigans", "Prism"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["The Black Album", "Still I Rise", "Alive 1997", "Triple Feature"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Live at the House of Blues", "2006-04-29: Coachella Valley Music Festival", "Forever Gold", "Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Alive 2007", "Kingdom Come", "Yeezus", "Listen to This Eddie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["What About Now", "Daft Club", "Best of Queen", "God's Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Best 99", "On Another Planet", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D", "The Eminem Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Original Album Series", "Like a Virgin", "Magna Carta... Holy Grail", "Daft Punk Live in NYC"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["TRON: Legacy", "Future Games", "Bonfire", "The Pious Bird of Good Omen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Paradise Valley", "Hammer of Gods", "Live in London", "Remix After All"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Signals", "Goodies / The Evolution", "DJ Mix", "Headless Cross"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["A Kid Named Cudi", "Morrison Hotel", "Louis Vuitton Spring", "Second Semester"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Alive", "Kill All: The Rarities Collection", "Live @ Rex Club Paris", "Numb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["True Blue", "Rolling Papers", "Random Access Memories", "Led Zeppelin III"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Can't Tell Me Nothing: The Official Mixtape", "One Day in Your Life", "Discovery: Bonus Tracks From daftclub.com", "The Works"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Human After All: Remixes", "Magic", "The Singles", "Live at Massey Hall 1971"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Never Say Never: The Remixes", "Best of Queen", "Decks n' Drums n' 909", "Planet Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Discovery", "The Singles Collection Volume 3", "Bad", "iTunes Live From SoHo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Digital Decks", "Time Stand Still: The Collection", "Live at the Riverboat 1969", "The Complete Works"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns", "Elvis' Golden Records", "Greatest Hits", "Homework/Discovery"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Musicology", "Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005", "Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Daft Punk?", "answers": ["Closure", "With the Lights Out", "Human After All", "4"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mumford & Sons?", "answers": ["Eagles", "Sigh No More", "iTunes Live From SoHo", "Breakout: Video Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mumford & Sons?", "answers": ["Piece of Mind", "One of These Nights", "Animalize", "iTunes Festival: London 2010"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mumford & Sons?", "answers": ["Cash Cow", "Let It Be... Naked", "The Road to Red Rocks", "Tha Gangsta Mix"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mumford & Sons?", "answers": ["Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "Up All Night", "Live at Slane Castle", "Riverside Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mumford & Sons?", "answers": ["That's My Work Vol. 1", "Here and There", "Babel", "American Stars 'n Bars"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["New Jersey: The Videos", "Untitled Korn album", "Loose Ends", "John Legend: Live from Philadelphia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Lemmings / Going Nowhere / One Track", "Solo Sessions Vol. 1: Live at the Knitting Factory", "Best Of", "Pink Friday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["The Best of Michael Jackson", "Love in the Future", "Con Todo", "Christmas Duets"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Legend Remixed", "Year Zero", "Once Again", "In a Valley by the Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Today", "Get Lifted", "The White Album", "Perception"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Climbing to New Lows", "Live From Philadelphia", "I Believe the Promise", "The Best of Tool"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Wake Up!", "Planet Waves", "Golden Ballads", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Live at SOB's New York City", "Makaveli 2000", "Soul Rebel & Other Great Reggae Hits", "Super Strong God"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["The Best of Bob Marley", "Bob Dylan at Budokan", "1988", "Evolver"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Legend?", "answers": ["Live at the House of Blues", "The Doors", "Live at River Plate", "Boston Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel Remix Edition", "Doorie", "Purest Feeling", "Greatest Hits 1973-1982"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["The Early Years", "Rays of Light", "Steel Wheels", "Pyass"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Number 1's", "The Fame Kingdom", "Zanjeer -The Game Changer", "Hangami Halaat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["Jal Pari", "Madonna: Dalle Origini Al Mito", "Farewell I Tour (Bonus Disk)", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Atif Aslam?", "answers": ["The 50th Anniversary Collection", "Meri Kahani", "Tokyo Road", "The White Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Pearl Jam Twenty", "2Pacalypse Now", "TP-2.com", "Reunion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Box Set", "More Experience", "Rap Hard", "R. Kelly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Time Stand Still: The Collection", "Trin-i-tee 5:7", "Behind Da Bars", "Crash Landing"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Black Panties", "The Lost Tapes 2", "Never Say Die!", "Any Given Thursday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["The R. In R&B Greatest Hits Collection: Volume 1 (remix bonus disc)", "Metallica", "Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "All the World's a Stage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Rebellious Soul", "The Best of Both Worlds", "Greatest Hits III", "Collaborations"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["The Remixes", "Long Road Out of Eden", "My Diary", "Elvis: 2nd to None"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Jigoku-Retsuden", "Live From Wembley Arena", "In the Mix", "Bare Trees"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["12 Play: Fourth Quarter", "Love You Live", "2 of One", "Prince from Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of R. Kelly", "Hannah Montana Forever", "The City Is Mine", "Changesbowie"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["R.", "Other Voices", "Boy in Detention", "Looking Back at..."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Finally Famous", "At San Quentin", "Play", "Dance of Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "TP.3 Reloaded", "Freshmen Adjustment", "Relapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Write Me Back", "The Drake LP", "The Best of David Bowie 1969/1974", "Korn Live: The Encounter"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Born into the 90's", "Radiohead for Haiti", "Kaya", "HIStory"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["TP3 Reloaded", "Kiss Instant Live", "Tonite Let's All Make Love in London... Plus", "iTunes Festival: London 2010"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["The Lion King", "A Tree with Roots", "Remix City Vol. 1", "Night Visions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Archangel Rides Again", "Playtime Is Over", "\"The \"\"Demo\"\" Tape\"", "Ciara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Under the Covers: Essential Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Loveland", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)", "BBC Archives 1967-1969"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["New orleans nightmare", "Love Land", "Personal File", "Destroyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["More Malice", "17-11-70", "Epic", "Valleys of Neptune"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Infinity on High", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Rap Phenomenon III", "Chocolate Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["These Days", "All of the Above", "AM", "Trapped in the Closet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Alphabet St.", "Voodoo Child: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming", "Unfinished Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["For Those Who Have Heart", "Iron Man: The Best of Black Sabbath", "Gotham City Clubbin Part 2", "Stars Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Interstellar Encore", "Love Letter", "Earlybird - BBC 1973", "The Beatles' Christmas records"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Live at Lollapalooza 2007", "In Rainbows", "Live at the Fillmore East", "Double Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["Untitled", "Who's the New Girl?", "Hold Your Fire", "Family Jewels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["LiveAndWell.com", "12 Play", "\u00c6nima", "The Immaculate Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by R. Kelly?", "answers": ["One Nite Alone", "Dynamic Live", "My Worlds Acoustic", "Happy People / U Saved Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bastille?", "answers": ["Here Is Mariah Carey", "All We Know Is Falling", "Greatest Hits", "Bad Blood"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bastille?", "answers": ["The Collection 1973-84", "On the Beach", "The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Other People's Heartache"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bastille?", "answers": ["Connect Set", "The Queen Collection", "Alive III", "Bloody Shirt"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Live in Miami", "Live at Wembley", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Don't be Fooled by the Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Best Friend", "The Ultimate Collection", "Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel Remix Edition", "Sleeps With Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["F.A.M.E.", "Black Box: The Complete Original Black Sabbath (1970\u20131978)", "Look to You", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Desire", "In a Valley by the Sea", "The White Album", "Long May You Run"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Abbey Dawn.Love Revolution", "Glorious Ruins", "Live at River Plate", "The Road to El Dorado"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["iTunes Session", "United We Stand", "Jump Back: The Best of the Rolling Stones", "The Essential Elvis Presley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Daydream", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta", "The Singles", "The I Heart Revolution: We're All in This Together"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["All of the Above", "Drama", "Somebody to Love (remix)", "An Evening With"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["[a_CROSS//the_EARTH]:: Tear Down The Walls", "Access All Areas: A Rock & Roll Odyssey", "Essential Mixes", "Avenged Sevenfold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Absolute Greatest", "Coffret 4 CD", "Beggars Banquet", "The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Zion", "Last Night on Earth: Live in Tokyo", "Sabbath Bloody Sabbath", "AC/DC Gold 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["MDNA World Tour", "A Kid Named Cudi", "This Note's for You", "Everyday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Korn Kovers", "The Original Fleetwood Mac", "To the Ends of the Earth", "The Final Riot!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["So You Wanna Freestyle?", "Hannah Montana: Hits Remixed", "...Baby One More Time", "Simply Worship Three"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["4", "A Beautiful World", "Metamorphosis", "Aftermath"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["King of Majesty", "For Colored Girls/Pre-Pain Medicine", "Led Zeppelin II", "The Illmatic Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["For Badgeholders Only", "Unidos Permanecemos", "Dirty Mind", "That's My Work Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["Bedtime Stories", "Faith + Hope + Love", "The Love Songs", "The Seventh Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["More Than Life", "Icon", "\u00c7a Ira", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong United?", "answers": ["2pac", "Unified:Praise", "Exit... Stage Left", "Doorie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ed Sheeran?", "answers": ["Rare Traxx", "Born Sinner", "Soul Revolution 1 & 2", "Songs of Life and Hope"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits at Studio One", "Stiff Upper Lip", "For the Fans", "Maximum Presure"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Kings of Hell", "Profiled", "Fucking Crazy", "One Love at Studio One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Marshall Bruce Mathers III", "Yesstories", "Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "Barbadian Superstardom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Dance of Death", "Music & Me", "Curtis", "Stan: A Tribute to Eminem"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978", "Eminem Presents: The Re-Up", "Black Tie White Noise", "Get the Funk Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Coda", "Texas (San Antonio)", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door", "8 Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["HIStory", "American Life/Music", "The Freestyle Manual", "The Green Day Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The New Breed", "Jewels", "Long Time No See", "Station to Station"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Eminem is Back", "Splitting the DNA", "The Razors Edge", "Boss's Birthday Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Live Shit: Binge & Purge", "For Those Who Have Heart", "Merry Christmas II You", "Encore"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Every Song Tells a Story", "Live at Big Day Out 2000", "Off the Wall", "TKOL RMX 1234567"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Bootleg Series Vol. 8 \u2013 Tell Tale Signs: Rare and Unreleased 1989\u20132006", "Greatest Hits Live", "Fuckin' Crazy", "Black Holes and Revelations"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Losing It", "Back in Black", "Good Girl Gone Bad", "Black Holes and Revelations"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["And Their Name Was Treason", "Platinum Collection 2001", "Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life", "Seek Bromance (Remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Nothing Was the Same", "Come", "Star Mark Greatest Hits (disc 2)", "Best Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Dead Perspective", "The First Ten Years: The Videos", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "[a_CROSS//the_EARTH]:: Tear Down The Walls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Very Best of the Eagles", "The Marshall Mathers LP 2", "Carnival of Souls: The Final Sessions", "Mirage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Queen II", "Shine a Light", "Family Values Tour '98", "Acid Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Die for Me", "Le Roi Lion", "Welcome To The Dogg House", "All We Know Is Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Limitless and Free", "Stillmatic", "The Passion of Tupac", "The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970", "Road to Recovery: Withdrawal", "Green Shadows", "N.E.W.S."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Youngest Head Nigga in Charge (Hub City Threat: Minor of the Year)", "Make It or Break It Videos", "Loving You", "Just Finish It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Metallica", "Eminem & Friends", "Born Sinner", "Man in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["T.R.U. REALigion", "Die for Me", "On Another Planet", "Remix Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Hits 1", "Good Times", "More Experience", "Shade 45: Sirius Bizness"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Return of the Champions", "Devil in a Blue Dress", "Loving the Alien", "White America"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Wiz: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack", "Gold Collection 1970-1971", "Infinite", "The Beatles Stereo Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["L.A. Woman", "The Marshall Mathers LP", "Great White Wonder", "Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Daft Club", "DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "Live and Fucked Up", "Deuce"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["So You Wanna Freestyle?", "Riot Act", "Born in the U.S.A.", "Rock of the '70s"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Slim Shady LP", "More Boring Days", "Relayer", "Gold Collection 1970-1971"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)", "Aftermath", "The Singles Boxset (Previously Unreleased bonus disc)", "Awake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Born Again", "Love Gun", "The Lost Tapes 2", "Curtain Call: The Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Magna Carta... Holy Grail", "Freestyle B4 Paystyle", "All Access Europe", "Ode to Deodorant / Brothers + Sisters"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Circus", "Made in Heaven", "The Underground Collection", "Come Around Sundown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Legend of Hip Hop", "Elvis at Sun", "KISS Alive! 1975-2000", "Relapse"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Yestoday", "Girl 6", "Madonna", "Unrelease V"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["David Live", "Howwa 3 Dynastia", "Raw & Uncut", "A Hard Day\u2019s Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Absolute Greatest", "Pluto", "Don't Call Me Marshall", "Mardi Gras"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Caress of Steel", "The Anger Management Tour Live", "Live at the 10 Spot", "S. Carter: The Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Exodus", "Jazz", "Made in Heaven", "The Freestyle Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Ready 4 War", "By Your Side", "Songs From The Underground", "Graffiti Bridge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Doggumentary", "Live at the Fillmore East", "Conscience", "Simply Worship 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["Recovery", "The Golden Unplugged Album", "The Madonna Collection", "My Worlds"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eminem?", "answers": ["The Eminem Show", "The Last Supper", "All I Want Is You", "These Days \u2013 Special Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["The Wall Singles Collection", "Splitting the DNA", "TKOL RMX 1234567", "Rush ABC: Live from Cleveland\u2019s Agora Ballroom 1974"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["That's My Work Vol. 1", "Road to Revolution: Live at Milton Keynes", "I Am Not a Human Being II", "R."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Minutes to Midnight - Live Around the World", "Legend Remixed", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2", "Seven Bridges Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Welcome to the New Administration", "VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson", "Live 2003", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Toy", "In da Club", "xero", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Best of 2Pac", "The Beatles' Story", "Recharged", "Houses of the Holy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Personal File", "Live in Texas", "Flashpoint", "Love and Theft"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Meteora", "Late Orchestration", "Early On (1964-1966)", "Vol. 2... Hard Knock Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Justified", "My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy", "For This Cause", "Las Vegas Theory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Plug Me In", "The Woman in Black", "Remix After All", "Hybrid Theory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Underground 3.0", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "Live from Live Earth", "The Script"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Glorious Ruins", "Forty Licks", "Promised Land", "Meteora - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["For All You've Done", "MMM...COOKIES - Sweet Hamster Like Jewels from America!", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990", "Playlist: The Very Best of Britney Spears"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Sunfly Gold Vol. 34: Linkin Park & Limp Bizkit", "The Remixes (vinyl)", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Bon Scott Rarities", "Orlando 2000", "Visionary: The Video Singles", "Led Zeppelin BBC Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003", "Come Around Sundown", "Rebirth", "Songs From The Underground"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits III", "Viva la Vida or Death and All His Friends", "A Thousand Suns", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["En Vivo!", "The Sabbath Collection", "Living Things", "The Remixes (vinyl)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["The Blueprint 3", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "Oxford's Angels", "Hybrid Theory - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Le Roi Lion", "Roll the Bones", "Live from SoHo", "TBA"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Project Revolution", "Prince", "The College Dropout", "Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Reanimation", "Archangel Rides Again", "Prince of the City 2", "The Civil Wars"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Room for Squares", "Love Death Travel Box Set", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)", "Minutes To Midnight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["Dub Tribute to Linkin Park", "Soul Almighty", "Kerplunk", "NASA Music 2: Space Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Linkin Park?", "answers": ["The Civil Wars", "The Doors Box Set", "2002: New York", "Live in London"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["The Late Mixtape", "Zion", "Room for Improvement", "The Very Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Greatest Street Hitz", "In Rainbows", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums", "Heartbreak Drake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Have a Nice Day", "Comeback Season", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 10 \u2013 Another Self Portrait", "Greatest Hits (Disc 1)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Singles Club", "2112", "Dead Perspective", "Dream Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Rarities", "Live Killers", "All-Madden: This Aint That Radio Shit Vol 2", "Texas (San Antonio)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Grunge Is Dead", "Take Care", "Early Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume One", "Unbroken"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Outcesticide III: The Final Solution", "Untitled Nas album", "Steel Wheels", "The Drake LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Discovery: Bonus Tracks From daftclub.com", "Eye's and Imagination", "Thank Me Later", "Paradise Valley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["KISS Alive! 1975-2000", "Black Magic Woman: The Best of Fleetwood Mac", "Seven Bridges Road", "No More Thank Yous"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Nothing Was the Same", "Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life", "Recovery", "Issues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Live at the Hollywood Bowl", "The Uplift Mofo Party Plan", "MDNA World Tour", "So Far Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Drake?", "answers": ["Remix Project", "Stone's Been Rolled Away", "Born King", "The Indispensable Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Hits of the Eagles", "E=MC\u00b2", "The Singles Collection", "Single Ladies (Put a Ring on It) Dance Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Selected Works: 1972\u20131999", "Goodies: The Videos & More", "Moving Pictures", "Psychedelic Pill"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Second Night Unplugged", "Rated R", "Dirty Mind", "The 50 Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["One Day in Your Life", "Get Freeze It", "Grace Under Pressure Tour", "Issues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Oklahoma City 1972", "Jump Up!", "Greatest Hits 1969-1971", "Somebody to Love (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Dub Tribute to Linkin Park", "Best Selection", "Old Record", "Elvis Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["On the Border", "Dead Man Walkin", "Old Record", "Get Lifted"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Baggy's Rehearsal Sessions", "A Collection of Michael Jackson's Oldies", "The Complete Greatest Hits", "Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Around the World in a Day", "The Very Best Of", "All the World's a Stage", "The Blueprint 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Tha Carter III", "Eagles", "Rock of the '70s", "Tyr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["International Superhits", "Makaveli 2: The Lost Album", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "The Very Best of the Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["What's The 901?", "Selected Works 1972-1999", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre", "21 at 33"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Farewell I Tour (Bonus Disk)", "Black Sabbath Vol. 4", "The Early Days", "N.E.W.S."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["KoRn Live at CBGBs", "With Teeth", "Farewell Tour I", "2000 Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Songs of Life and Hope", "Meteora - Live Around the World", "Tha Carter III: The Rebirth", "Alive"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Metallica", "The Very Best of Eagles", "The Beatles 1967-1970", "Born to Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Forty Licks", "Absolution", "A Thing Called Love", "Hell Freezes Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Metallurgy", "Aftermath", "Seven Bridges Road", "Powerslave"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Circus / Blackout", "G Unit General", "Double Up", "Farewell I Tour: Live from Melbourne"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Outcesticide IV: Rape of the Vaults", "The Long Run", "The White Album", "Live Evil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Pink Friday", "Heartache Tonight", "Early On (1964-1966)", "The Freewheelin' Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["AC/DC Live", "The T-Wayne Show", "Let It Be... Naked", "Forum Assago Milan (13-06-2009)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Long Road Out of Eden", "Dehumanizer", "Tha Last Meal", "Cheshire Cat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Carter III", "Hotel California", "Live at Donington", "A Tribute to Johnny Kidd and the Pirates"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Love Songs", "Curtis", "Eagles Live", "Jimi Hendrix: The Singles Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Their Greatest Hits 1971-1975", "An American Prayer", "Trenchtown Rock", "Revolver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Wasted Time (Minneapolis 25-02-1995)", "Platinum Collection 2000", "Retrospective II: 1981-1987", "The Anger Management Tour Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Soundtrack Recordings from the Film Jimi Hendrix", "Con Todo", "Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida", "The Legend of Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Music of the Sun", "The Eagles / Desperado", "Xpectation", "Golden Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Barton Hollow", "The Studio Albums 1972-1979", "Gold", "Death of Escobar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Absolution", "Something's Coming: The BBC Recordings 1969\u20131970", "The Man Who Sold the World", "Rock Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["For Badgeholders Only", "Madonna Remixed", "For You", "Earlybird - BBC 1973"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Best of Eagles", "Pluto", "Sun Is Shining", "Sticky & Sweet Tour Live in Buenos Aires"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["Don't be Fooled by the Name", "As Recorded at Madison Square Garden", "Best Ballads", "Believers Never Die \u2013 Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["One of These Nights", "Yield", "Discovery", "Falling Away from Me: The Best of Korn"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Eagles?", "answers": ["The Collection 1973-84", "Desperado", "The Freestyle Manual", "Madonna Remixed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Thriller 25", "Best Ballads", "Goats Head Soup", "Their Greatest Hits 1971-1975"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection", "What About Now", "Live at SOB's New York City", "Alphabet St."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Powerage", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Around the World", "Tokyo Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Lost Highway: The Concert", "Ten", "Man on the Moon III", "From Fear to Eternity: The Best of 1990\u20132010"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "Blackout", "The Complete Works", "The Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Soled Out", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls", "These Days \u2013 Special Edition", "Cash Cow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Shade 45: Sirius Bizness", "Sex Therapy", "Target Exclusive", "Born and Raised"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Don't Call Me Marshall", "Slippery When Wet", "World Without End", "The Black & Tan Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Smells Like Punk Spirit", "Golden Ballads", "Tokyo Road (live)", "Elton John's Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Hymns by Johnny Cash", "AM", "Lost Highway", "One Nite Alone... Live!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Live at the House of Blues", "The Union", "7800\u00b0 Fahrenheit"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Crush", "Journey Through the Past", "Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970", "Hybrid Theory - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Megaforce demo", "The Essential Iron Maiden", "The Language of My World", "Cross Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Reflections", "The Platinum Collection", "Best of 50 Cent", "Access All Areas: A Rock & Roll Odyssey"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Live at Bonnaroo", "Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978", "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "An Evening With"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["100 Million Bon Jovi Fans Can't Be Wrong", "Open Your Eyes", "Graffiti", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Life Is Good", "The Singles", "The Album", "One Wild Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Climbing to New Lows", "Bounce", "Tiny Desk Concert", "Every Song Tells a Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["MDNA World Tour", "Reality", "Live Evil", "This Left Feels Right Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Alive", "Hammer of Gods", "Playtime Is Over", "Hall of Fame"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["This Left Feels Right: Greatest Hits With a Twist", "The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Shout to the Lord", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Blaze Of Hits", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Kanye West Presents: Promise", "Meteora - Live Around the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["World Name", "Live at the House of Blues", "Alcoholic (Remixes)", "Live at Madison Square Garden"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Live in Philadelphia '70", "King of the Air Waves", "MDNA", "Live in Texas"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["The Eternal Idol", "The Circle", "Greatest Hits 98", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["A Date With Elvis", "Power Flower Trouble Fruits", "Here We Go Again", "Bon Jovi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)", "Greatest Hits", "Death of Escobar", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["New Jersey", "Made in the Shade", "Lana Del Ray a.k.a. Lizzy Grant", "Zanjeer -The Game Changer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits '94", "Stars Dance", "The Black Chronic", "Southern G'z"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["24 Shots", "I Am Not a Human Being", "These Days", "Help!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Breakout: Video Singles", "Singles Collection: The London Years", "Twilight of the Gods", "Burn After Rolling"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Overwhelmed", "Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "Honky Ch\u00e2teau", "Hard & Hot"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Songs of Life and Hope", "Have a Nice Day", "Sk8er Girl", "God He Reigns"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "In Brazil: LP", "Live from London", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["The Remixes", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Obscurity", "Keep the Faith"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90", "Greatest Hits: The Ultimate Collection", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003", "Red Hot Skate Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["The Eminem Show", "Greatest Hits", "One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001", "God's Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["The Freewheelin' Bob Dylan", "Project Revolution", "Stan: A Tribute to Eminem", "New Jersey: The Videos"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Live from London", "IV", "The Lost Tapes", "Friends In High Places"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Tokyo Road: Best of Bon Jovi", "Kornoise", "Slap Happy", "Shrine '69"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Neidermayer's Mind", "Can You Handle Mine?", "We Are Not Unused", "Bleach"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Beatles VI", "Inside Out", "25 Years - The Chain", "Tracks Through Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Blackest Sabbath", "The Wall: Live in Berlin", "Keep the Faith: An Evening with Bon Jovi", "Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["The Crush Tour", "Bitter Tears", "17-11-70", "Meddle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bon Jovi?", "answers": ["Nevermind", "The Love Songs", "It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away...", "Forever Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by One Direction?", "answers": ["Have a Nice Day", "Up All Night", "Bye Bye Bruce", "Conscience"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by One Direction?", "answers": ["Take Me Home", "Illmatic", "Madonna: The Confessions Tour", "The Pursuit of Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by One Direction?", "answers": ["Towering Above the Rest", "World Without End", "Midnight Memories", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by One Direction?", "answers": ["Daytrotter Session-live album", "Live in Texas: 7 June 2006", "Story of My Life", "Low"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["The Bends", "Drama", "Earth to Mars", "All Eyez on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["The Lost Planet", "The Beginning of the N VLS", "Kiss Symphony: The DVD", "Coffret 4 CD"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Berlin Trilogy", "ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne", "Unorthodox Jukebox", "Out of Our Heads"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruno Mars?", "answers": ["Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "Heart of Jamaica", "The Indispensable Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ariana Grande?", "answers": ["Pearl Jam Twenty", "Led Zeppelin II", "I Can't Live", "Yours Truly"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Alive III", "Pin Ups", "Purest Feeling", "Help!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Graffiti Bridge", "Something New", "Days Are Gone", "Flick of the Switch"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Queen Collection", "Beatles \u201965", "The Road to Carter 4", "On the Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Never Say Never: The Remixes", "With Teeth: Summer Tour 2006 Radio Collaboration", "With Teeth", "Past Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Divers & Submarines", "Lana Del Ray a.k.a. Lizzy Grant", "The Beatles\u2019 Long Tall Sally", "Live on Air"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Age of Giants", "Roots of a Legend", "TRON: Legacy", "Yesterday\u2026 and Today"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Beatles' Story", "Metallurgy", "Playlist: The Very Best of the Backstreet Boys", "Celebrity"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Hitstory", "Unplugged", "Please Please Me", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["AM", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album", "The Beatles Collection", "Femme Fatale"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Unsurpassed Masters", "Get Rich or Die Tryin'", "I Might Be Wrong: Live Recordings", "Runaway Love (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Labyrinth", "Beatles VI", "Going No Where", "Hills Praise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Road to Recovery: Withdrawal", "Born Is The King", "As/Is", "1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Legend of Hip Hop", "Parade: Music From the Motion Picture Under the Cherry Moon", "Hey Jude", "Wrecking Ball"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Power (remix)", "Live at the BBC", "Iron Man 2", "The Crown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Symbolic Beginning", "Destroyer", "The Winter Album", "The Beatles in Mono"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Grey Album", "2 Tracks Demo", "FACT Mix 327: Disclosure", "Heartbreak Drake"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Mellow Moods", "Animalize Live Uncensored", "Rock 'n' Roll Music", "Scary Monsters (and Super Creeps)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "Unidos Permanecemos", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "Once Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Physical Graffiti", "20 Greatest Hits", "The Eternal Legacy", "Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Video Anthology Vol. 1", "Toy", "Magical Mystery Tour", "Best of Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Live in Chicago 05.16.2006", "Olympic Gold", "1962\u20131966", "The Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Serious Moonlight", "The Beatles\u2019 Second Album", "Kiss the Sky", "I'll Stay Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["With The Beatles", "Brave New World", "Sun Is Shining", "Live At Reading"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Love Songs", "A Nice Pair", "Great Country Songs", "Alphabet St."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["20Ten", "Better Dayz", "The Beatles at the Hollywood Bowl", "Live in Chicago 05.16.2006"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["In the Heart of Sin City", "A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Under the Red Sky", "Live Rust"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["50 Best Songs \u2013 The Motown Years: Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Heaven and Hell", "Malice N Wonderland", "Tomorrow Never Knows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Love Songs", "Exclusive", "At the Beeb", "Introducing\u2026 The Beatles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["King of Pop", "The Lost Prophecy", "Beatlemania! With the Beatles", "In Da Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Tha Dogg: Best of the Works", "Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars", "Anthology 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Babylon by Bus", "The Beatles Stereo Box Set", "2Pacalypse Now", "The Top Ten Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Songs of Our Soil", "Makaveli 6", "Abbey Road", "Mother's Milk"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Singles", "Rubber Soul", "Viva la Vida or Death and All His Friends", "Self Portrait"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Broken", "18 Months", "Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band", "The Club Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour", "On the Border", "The Beatles Box Set", "Pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Anthology 3", "Sleeping With the Past", "What Live Album !?", "The Gospel Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Get Lifted", "Everyday Chemistry", "Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "Guess Who's Back Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Off the Map", "Let It Be... Naked", "The Ballads", "In the Zone / Britney"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Who Then Now?", "Beatles for Sale", "I Created Disco", "Hendrix in the West"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["See You Again: 2008 Mix", "AC/DC in the 20th Century", "Slap Happy", "Let It Be"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "Steel Wheels", "Doggystyle", "The White Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Lemmings / Going Nowhere / One Track", "A Farewell to Kings", "Spirit and Truth", "The Beatles 1967-1970"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["James Arthur", "Lovesexy", "Can't Be Tamed", "Yellow Submarine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Fame and Fashion (David Bowie\u2019s All Time Greatest Hits)", "The Beatles' First", "Stop That Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Having a Blast", "Loose Ends", "A Collection of Beatles Oldies", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Meet the Beatles!", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome", "Falling Away from Me: The Best of Korn", "The Drought Is Over 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Love and Theft", "Science & Faith", "Outcesticide IV: Rape of the Vaults", "Anthology 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["Live in New York", "Crystal Ball", "Revolver", "Manhattan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Beatles' Christmas records", "Hard Rain", "Working on a Dream", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["The Early Beatles", "Icon", "High Voltage", "Under Wheels of Confusion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Beatles?", "answers": ["OK Computer", "BLACK SCVLE", "Born This Way: The Remix", "Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Passenger?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "All the Little Lights", "My President Is Black", "Katy Hudson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Passenger?", "answers": ["Stiff Upper Lip", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)", "Wide Eyes Blind Love", "Unfinished Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Passenger?", "answers": ["Divers & Submarines", "Vol. 2... Hard Knock Life", "The Wall Singles Collection", "Comes a Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Passenger?", "answers": ["Just Finish It", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 2", "The VS. Redux", "Flight of the Crow"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["As/Is", "From Elvis in Memphis", "The Crush Tour", "How the West Was Won"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Tonight", "E=MC\u00b2 Adventure Box", "Hitstory", "In the Flesh - Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["It Was Written", "Origin of Symmetry", "Promised Land", "Unfinished Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["At San Quentin", "Happy People / U Saved Me", "In the Zone / Circus", "Fun in Acapulco"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Make It or Break It Videos", "The Ozzy Osbourne Years", "The Complete Elvis Presley Masters", "Until We Have Faces"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Chrome Dreams II", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "No Stone Unturned", "Welcome to My World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "Pot Luck", "Dead Man", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Black Panties", "Greatest Hell's Hits", "Aloha From Hawaii: Via Satellite", "The Best of David Bowie 1980/1987"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Blue Hawaii", "Speak My Mind", "The Seventh Coming", "NASA Music 2: Space Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Yesterday\u2026 and Today", "Led Zeppelin", "Elvis Is Back!", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Queen II", "Guess Who's Back?", "Elvis The King", "Here We Go Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Something to Remember", "His Hand in Mine", "Recharged", "Friends"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Summer Carter", "Rebirth", "Ciara", "Elvis"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Death of Escobar", "Live in New York City", "Elvis Presley", "A Thing Called Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["A Date With Elvis", "Live on Air", "Exit... Stage Left", "The Very Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Vitalogy", "Rich Gang: Flashy Lifestyle", "Keys to Ascension 2", "As Recorded at Madison Square Garden"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Deuce", "Elvis in Concert", "Argenfornication", "And Their Name Was Treason"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Die for Me", "On Stage", "Cabin Fever", "The Stripped Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Infinity on High", "Beatles for Sale", "Live in Hollywood", "Elvis Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Ode to Deodorant / Brothers + Sisters", "Elvis Movies", "Absolution Tour", "20Ten"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Elvis' Christmas Album", "Blue Moves", "Live At Easy Street", "TKOL RMX 1234567"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "Steel Wheels", "Viva Elvis", "Gagging Order: Acoustic Renditions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Duets", "Controversy", "From Nashville to Memphis: The Essential '60s Masters", "Show And Prove"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "Live in Boston", "A Treasure", "The 20/20 Experience \u2013 2 of 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Destroyer- Resurrected", "The Top Ten Hits", "Newpower Soul", "The Ozzy Osbourne Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Under the Covers: Essential Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Incesticide", "Elvis: Ultimate Gospel", "Jump to the Jam"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Weezy Evolution", "G.I. Blues", "2 of One", "Victim of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Heartbreak Drake", "The 50 Greatest Hits", "Sabotage", "Caribou"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005", "Christmas Duets", "Teenage Dream: The Complete Confection", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Girl Happy", "The Best of Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Bob Dylan: the Collection", "No Sleep 'Til NYC"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Elvis: 2nd to None", "A Single Man", "Ghosts I\u2013IV", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Power Dance Hits", "Pac's Life", "Looking Back to Yesterday", "King Creole"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Moody Blue", "Flight of the Crow", "Enema of the State Demo", "Music From the Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Human After All: Remixes", "Kiss Instant Live", "Good Times", "Bon Jovi"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Loveland", "Puff Puff Pass Tuesdays Mixtape Vol. 1", "Great Country Songs", "Symbol Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Loving You", "Hesitation Marks", "House of Yes: Live From House of Blues", "Super Strong God"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Live at the Riverboat 1969", "Freedom Songs", "7800\u00b0 Fahrenheit", "Elvis at Sun"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Pearl Jam", "He Touched Me", "On Another Planet", "In the Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Tracks Through Time", "The Massacre", "La voix du Rock", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Definitive Collection Mini LP Replica CD Boxset", "Southern G'z", "Live", "Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Grace Under Pressure Tour", "All the Little Lights", "Stone Age", "Prince from Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Today", "Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "Anyway", "The Purple Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Cherry Blue Skies", "Jailhouse Rock", "Bon Jovi", "Br\u00fctal Legend Original Soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Memories: The '68 Comeback Special", "The Gold Experience", "Talk", "S&M"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Killers", "Backstreet Boys", "Elvis' Golden Records", "SQ6"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Having Fun With Elvis on Stage", "Time Out with Britney Spears", "Trouble Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Latter Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume Two", "Hey Jude", "The Sun Sessions", "In the Zone / Britney"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Destroyer", "War Angel LP", "The Best of Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Elvis: Viva Las Vegas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elvis Presley?", "answers": ["Can't Be Tamed", "Hannah Montana 2 / Meet Miley Cyrus", "Friday Night Lights", "The Essential Elvis Presley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Goats Head Soup", "The Soft Parade", "Essential Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["3rd Eye Girl", "Open Your Eyes", "Elvis", "B-Sides"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Funhouse Tour: Live in Australia", "Powerslave"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Try to Shut Me Up Tour 2003 [Weekend Music]", "A Decade of Silence", "Got to Be There", "Kanye West presents: The Lost Tapes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["My Favorite Videos (So Far)", "The Complete Blue Horizon Sessions: 1967\u20131969", "Chronicles", "Hell Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Ray of Light", "The Graduate", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre", "Atom Heart Mother"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Goodbye Lullaby", "The Best Of", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles", "Cosmic Climb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Diamond Collection", "American Pie + Best Songs", "From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah", "Save Rock and Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["All Over the Place", "Rebirth", "Talk", "The Number of the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["How Fly", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Tattoo You", "Symbolic Beginning"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Boom Chicka Boom", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "The Best Damn Thing", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1970-2002", "The Best Damn Tour: Live in Toronto", "Help!", "The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["The Best of the Red Hot Chili Peppers", "All Things Are Possible", "Revival", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Under My Skin", "An Introduction to Syd Barrett", "Dirty Work", "Spitting"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["What You Don't Know", "Controversy", "King of the Air Waves", "Abbey Dawn.Love Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Alive 1997", "Quebec Magnetic", "Icon", "The Bonez Tour 2004: Avril's 20th Birthday Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Rush ABC: Live from Cleveland\u2019s Agora Ballroom 1974", "Shenanigans", "Unplugged at Jovem Pan", "Under the Covers: Essential Red Hot Chili Peppers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["People Just Like Us", "Outside", "June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets", "Sk8er Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Confessions on a Dance Floor", "Natural Mystic: The Legend Lives On", "My World", "Destroyer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Take a Bow (remixes)", "Emotional Rescue", "Grace Under Pressure", "\"12\"\" Masters: Essential Mixes\""], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["The Beat", "World Name", "Divers & Submarines", "Live at Wembley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Avril Lavigne", "Maximum Led Zeppelin", "All That Glitters Is Gold", "Dungeon Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "Reincarnated", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990", "Let Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Pink Friday", "Texas (San Antonio)", "Korn Live: The Encounter", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avril Lavigne?", "answers": ["Bonez Tour 2005: Live at Budokan", "1999-06-15: Eddies Attic", "FACT Mix 70: The xx", "Believe (Acoustic)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Things Falling Apart", "This Is Us", "Brand New Eyes", "Never Let Me Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Singles Club", "Keys to Ascension 2", "Pearl Jam Twenty", "Under My Skin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["All We Know Is Falling", "Reload", "Heartbreak Drake", "The Legend of Johnny Cash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Pure Heroine", "A Momentary Lapse of Reason", "Solo Sessions Vol. 1: Live at the Knitting Factory", "Riot!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["With Teeth: Summer Tour 2006 Radio Collaboration", "The Final Riot!", "A Bigger Bang", "Sticky Fingers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Sleeping With the Past", "Ragged Old Flag", "What You Don't Know", "Live in Stockholm"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Time", "Black Panties", "Paramore", "Amnesiac"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Ultimate Queen", "Live in the UK 2008", "In a Word: Yes (1969\u2013)", "All Excess"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Paramore?", "answers": ["Hard & Hot", "Best of Kanye West", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "Second Semester"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down", "Iron Man", "Hunky Dory", "Other Voices / Full Circle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Changesbowie", "Remix Album", "Inside Out", "Dreamin Man Live '92"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Spirit and Truth", "Working on a Dream", "Toy", "Woodstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Complete Greatest Hits", "The Best of Bob Dylan", "All Saints", "Favourite Worst Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["1999 Revisited", "N.E.W.S.", "Tonight", "Blue Wild Angel: Live at the Isle of Wight"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["In Rainbows", "Don't be Fooled by the Name", "The Prophet Returns", "Hannah Montana 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "Queen on Fire \u2013 Live at the Bowl", "The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars", "The Marshall Mathers LP 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Let There Be Rock", "Shout to the Lord 2000", "Essential Mixes", "Rare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Absolution Tour", "Re-ac-tor", "Ballbreaker", "Christiane F.: Wir Kinder vom Bahnhof Zoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Station to Station", "Ring of Fire: The Best of Johnny Cash", "The Times They Are a-Changin'", "The Rising Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Very Best", "The Best of David Bowie 1980/1987", "Tamar", "The Rules of Hell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Berlin Trilogy", "Rock Island Line", "Doggy Stuff", "Good as I Been to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Live in Chicago 05.16.2006", "Best Ballads", "IV", "The Buddha of Suburbia"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Me Against the World", "Dead Perspective", "Girl 6", "David Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Towering Above the Rest", "Low", "Human After All", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Megaforce demo", "Live at the Gorge 05/06"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["2006-04-29: Coachella Valley Music Festival", "Works", "B Is for Bob", "ChangesTwoBowie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Language of My World", "Live in Philadelphia '70", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Ziggy Stardust: The Motion Picture"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Black Chronic", "Outside", "At His Best", "Greatest Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Bye Bye Bruce", "Forever Gold", "Heathen", "Deal or No Deal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Write Me Back", "Greatest Hits Live", "Sound + Vision", "The Seventh Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Better Dayz", "It Was Written", "Iron Man", "David Bowie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["A Day at the Races", "Grow Season", "Live Santa Monica \u201972", "Woodstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["I Walk the Line", "Earthling", "The Very Best", "Anthology"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Serious Moonlight", "Living With War", "Doggumentary", "The Drought Is Over 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Mixtape Legend", "The Man Who Sold the World", "The Complete BBC Radio Sessions", "Right In Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["ISELECT", "Dat Kid From Cleveland", "Britney Spears: The Unreleased", "Sunday Morning Coming Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Late Night Tales: MGMT", "Hannah Montana 2: Non-Stop Dance Party", "Early On (1964-1966)", "The Truth About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Singles Collection", "The Essential Korn", "BBC Session", "Coda"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Harvest Moon", "Save Rock and Roll", "Fame and Fashion (David Bowie\u2019s All Time Greatest Hits)", "Lushlife Presents: West Sounds"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Digital Decks", "The Nigger Tape", "The Gospel According to David Bowie", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Listen to This Eddie", "Pin Ups", "Hannah Montana 3", "What Separates Me from You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Beatles Collection", "Nashville Skyline", "The Platinum Collection", "I Can't Feel My Face"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "A Farewell to Kings", "The Here After", "ChangesOneBowie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Complete Best Of", "7800\u00b0 Fahrenheit", "Pre Ordained", "Scary Monsters (and Super Creeps)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Elton John's Greatest Hits", "Experience", "Aladdin Sane", "Soul Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The VS. Redux", "Ready for the Weekend", "Diamond Dogs", "Working on a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Femme Fatale", "Labyrinth", "Exodus", "R."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["X&Y", "Fortune", "King of Majesty", "Lodger"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Catching Up With the B Sides", "Nine to the Universe", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions (American Land Edition)", "Let's Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Deuce", "Christmas Duets", "The Best of Bowie", "A Collection of Great Dance Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["U Know Big Sean\u2013Finally Famous Vol. 2", "The Best of David Bowie 1969/1974", "Kon The Louis Vitton Don", "B-Sides of the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Numb", "not my fault", "Man in Black", "Never Let Me Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Born This Way", "Ragged Old Flag", "Reality", "Box of Tricks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Live in Charlotte", "Stripped", "\"\"\"Heroes\"\"\"", "The Very Best of Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Black Tie White Noise", "The Yes Album", "You Make Me", "Sk8er Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Untouchables", "Gold Collection 1970-1971", "Best of Bowie", "2000 Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Ummagumma", "Young Americans", "Believe (Acoustic)", "In the Present: Live From Lyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["The Complete Studio Recordings", "Bleach", "Beginnings: The Lost Tapes 1988\u20131991", "Stage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Favourite Worst Nightmare", "Ragged Old Flag", "Daft Club", "'Hours...'"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by David Bowie?", "answers": ["Live at the Rainbow", "Led Zeppelin BBC Sessions", "The Last Supper", "LiveAndWell.com"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by ASAP Rocky?", "answers": ["Queen Ballads", "Elvis: Viva Las Vegas", "Kaya", "Live. Love. ASAP"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by ASAP Rocky?", "answers": ["Wish You Were Here / Early Singles", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Uprising", "Say You Will"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by ASAP Rocky?", "answers": ["Pre-Madonna", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Don't be Fooled by the Name", "Long.Live.A$AP"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by ASAP Rocky?", "answers": ["Who's That Girl", "Madison Blues Live", "BLACK SCVLE", "Born Is The King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["All Excess", "Weld", "Street's Disciple", "Mighty to Save"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Don't Forget", "Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2", "Around the World in a Day", "People Just Like Us"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming", "Follow You", "The Best of Pink Floyd", "Britney Spears: Live and More!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["TP.3 Reloaded", "That's the Way Through the Out Door", "Beatles \u201965", "Jesus Is My Superhero"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Show Your Glory", "Training Day", "Greatest Hits Live", "The Language of My World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Before I Self Destruct: The Selects", "Songs for Communion", "Rubber Soul", "The Grey Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Stone's Been Rolled Away", "Live at the 10 Spot", "A Bigger Bang", "Caribou"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Number of the Beast", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D", "For All You've Done", "Songs From the West Coast"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Exile on Main St.", "The Platinum Collection Volume 2: Shout to the Lord 2", "Weezy Evolution", "Number Ones"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["In the Zone / Circus", "Horsemen of the Apocalypse", "The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "God He Reigns"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["New Morning", "Super Hits", "Early On (1964-1966)", "Hills Praise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Darlene Zschech", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Nothing Was the Same", "Mardi Gras"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Rated R", "Heartache Tonight", "No Strings Attached", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Relics", "Greatest Hits", "Cherry Blue Skies", "Shout to the Lord 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["UP: Unified Praise", "Presto", "Megaforce demo", "Panjaban"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Daydream", "The Legend of Johnny Cash", "Double Platinum", "Hope"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Prophet Returns", "Oooh What a Green Day!", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums", "I Believe the Promise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Babylon by Bus", "In His Own Words", "I Am... World Tour", "Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["R30 - Live in Frankfurt", "Acoustic metal", "You Are My World", "More Malice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Lively Up", "Cosmic Climb", "The Graduate", "The Platinum Collection Volume 1: Shout to the Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Next Level", "Cabin Fever 2", "For This Cause", "Land of the Free Home of the Brave"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Chocolate Factory", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Cornerstone", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["13", "2 Tracks Demo", "Friends In High Places", "Da Drought 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Prophet Returns", "Fly From Here", "Greatest Hits", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Reuben Morgan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Mimi", "Simply Worship 2", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "1962\u20131966"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Con Todo", "Believe", "Circus", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["No Stone Unturned", "Born Is The King", "Alive 1997", "One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Ultimate Worship", "Live in Chicago 05.16.2006", "The Fame Kingdom", "Profiled"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Time", "Overwhelmed", "Led Zeppelin", "Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Shout to the Lord (Special Gold Edition)", "The Best of David Bowie 1969/1974", "Best Ballads", "Live at SOB's New York City"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Cornerstone EP", "The Last Supper", "*NSYNC", "Early Avenged Sevenfold releases"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Celebrating Christmas", "Before I Self Destruct", "Queen 40", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Forever", "Bad", "Best Tour", "Soul Almighty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Boston Box", "The Power of Your Love", "Smokefest Underground", "Playlist: The Very Best of Korn"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Very Best", "Kid A", "Spirit and Truth", "All I Want Is You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Born to Die", "Bob Dylan", "Rockin' Live From Italy 1993", "Shout to the Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Buddha Promo", "Ultimate Collection Volume II", "Yes", "World Name"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Simply Worship", "On the Beach", "Kanye West Presents: Promise", "Brave New World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["1999 Revisited", "X&Y", "39/Smooth", "By Your Side"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Kanye West Presents: Promise", "Live in Vancouver 1970", "Unrelease V", "Super Strong God"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["This Is Our God", "Purest Feeling", "Tha Carter II", "Unorthodox Jukebox"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Don't be Fooled by the Name", "Mother's Milk", "Yesterday\u2026 and Today", "Awake"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "The Collection 1973-84", "The Torture Never Stops", "God Is In The House"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Mighty Bob Marley", "Band of Gypsys 2", "The Mighty Bob Marley", "All Things Are Possible"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "God Is Able", "Weld", "Pink Friday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["More Boring Days", "2Pac & Friends", "Saviour King", "8 Mile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["The Spirit of Radio: Greatest Hits 1974-1987", "Blessed", "Mother's Milk", "Rock of the '70s"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Random Access Memories", "B-Sides", "Jump to the Jam", "The Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Anatomy of a Drum Solo", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D", "Touching Heaven Changing Earth", "Darkness on the Edge of Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["Grunge Is Dead", "Unrelease V", "Simply Worship 3", "Emancipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Hillsong Music?", "answers": ["20 Greatest Hits", "I Am Not a Human Being", "Amazing Love", "Blurred Lines"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Deuce", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Reuben Morgan", "X", "Greatest Hits 1970-2002"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Hall of Fame", "Insomniac", "Graffiti", "The Lost Tapes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["International Villager", "The Solid Gold Collection", "In My Zone", "Still I Rise"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Chris Brown", "Aftermath", "I Am... Yours: An Intimate Performance at Wynn Las Vegas", "The Bright Midnight Sampler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Boy in Detention", "Don't Shoot Me I'm Only the Piano Player", "Friday Night Lights", "Outakes and Demos 1985-1988"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Vitalogy", "F.A.M.E.", "Rainbow Show", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Ray of Light", "Tha Carter III: The Rebirth", "Fortune", "Superpop"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["The Complete Works", "A Place at the Table", "Trap-A-Velli 2: (The Residue)", "In My Zone 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Chris Brown?", "answers": ["Exclusive", "The One", "This Note's for You", "New Jersey: The Videos"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by HAIM?", "answers": ["Kerplunk", "Days Are Gone", "Deuce", "Unapologetic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["TRON: Legacy", "Greatest Hits 1970-2002", "Every Song Tells a Story", "21st Century Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Fight (For Your Cause)", "The Circle", "Live in Australia with the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra", "Chrome Dreams II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Union", "\u00c7a Ira", "Sunday Down South", "Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Cornerstone", "Sleeping With the Past", "X", "Gotham City Clubbin Part 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Kon The Louis Vitton Don", "21 at 33", "Sticky Fingers", "Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Rock of the Westies", "With The Beatles", "Live at the House of Blues", "Live at Eddie's Attic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Captain & the Kid", "Woodstock '99 Live Set", "Aladdin Sane", "Sleeps With Angels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Toy", "Leather Jackets", "Rap Phenomenon III", "Live/1975-85"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Kiss Instant Live", "Empty Sky", "Live from Live Earth", "100 Million Bon Jovi Fans Can't Be Wrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Power Metal demo", "Buddha", "Live At Easy Street", "Victim of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Ice on Fire", "20th Century Masters \u2013 The Millennium Collection: The Best of Kiss", "Unbroken", "The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Golden Legends", "Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida", "Live at Woodstock", "Ghetto Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Born to Run: 30th Anniversary Edition", "The Big Picture", "King of the Air Waves", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts-live album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Bad", "Stan: A Tribute to Eminem", "The Road to El Dorado", "In the Heart of Sin City"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Live at Donington", "Too Low for Zero", "\u00a1Tr\u00e9!", "Keep the Faith: An Evening with Bon Jovi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Curtain Call: The Hits", "I Am Not a Human Being", "Bad 25", "Madman Across the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Duets", "Sticky & Sweet Tour Live in Buenos Aires", "Carry the Cross", "The Complete BBC Radio Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged", "To Be Continued...", "Live at Montreux 2004", "Good Girl Gone Bad (remix bonus disc)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "The Metallica Collection", "Tales From Topographic Oceans", "Elton John's Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume III 1979-1987", "Presence", "The Best of Nas", "Star Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Pre-Madonna", "Here and There", "Binaural", "The Dynasty: Roc La Familia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Bridges to Babylon", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts", "Live in Vancouver", "The Very Best of Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["ChangesOneBowie", "Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "17-11-70", "Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Album Collection", "Captain Fantastic and The Brown Dirt Cowboy", "The Essential Mariah Carey", "Anatomy of a Drum Solo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Comeback Season", "The One", "Guess Who's Back Again", "The Rose That Grew From Concrete"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["John Legend: Live from Philadelphia", "Off the Wall", "Weezy Evolution", "Songs From the West Coast"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Shout to the Lord", "The Lion King", "Kiss the Sky", "This Is Rihanna"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Blue Moves", "Cliff 'Em All", "The Script", "Beam Me Up Scotty"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["The Kings of Hell", "Peachtree Road", "Towering Above the Rest", "Band of Gypsys"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Blonde on Blonde", "One Nite Alone", "Rare Masters", "Sorry 4 the Wait"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["3121", "Lady Samantha", "Nevermind: The Singles", "Nebraska"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Jump Up!", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet Re-Release", "The Best of David Bowie 1980/1987", "The Beatles Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "Caribou", "Pink Friday"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Live in Ottawa", "Cross Purposes Live", "18 Months", "Good Morning to the Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Bob Dylan: the Collection", "TBA", "Korn Live: The Encounter", "A Single Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Finally Famous-The Mixtape", "Breaking Hearts", "No Limit Top Dogg", "Flash Gordon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "Retrospective III: 1989x13x32x30x30x38", "Johnny B. Goode", "The Last Supper"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Drama", "When the Wind Blows", "I Am...", "Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Going No Where", "Reg Strikes Back", "American Stars 'n Bars", "N.E.W.S."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Le Roi Lion", "Nevermind: The Singles", "Let It Bleed", "Live on Ten Legs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["All of the Above", "Living Things", "The Beatles\u2019 Long Tall Sally", "Don't Shoot Me I'm Only the Piano Player"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["I Walk the Line", "Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978", "American V: A Hundred Highways", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Slow Train Coming", "Other Voices", "Rocket Man: The Definitive Hits", "A Total Waste of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Rocket Man: Number Ones", "MDNA World Tour", "Playlist: The Very Best of Britney Spears", "Under the Red Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["50 Cent Is the Future", "Elton John One Night Only \u2013 The Greatest Hits", "The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition", "Shakurspeare"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Gnomeo & Juliet", "Fan Can 4", "X", "S.Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume II", "Magic", "At the Beeb", "Pyass"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Tumbleweed Connection", "2011-06-04: KROQ Weenie Roast 2011-live album", "1999", "TP-2.com"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["No Strings Attached", "Tha Last Meal", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Friends"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["International Superhits", "Ummagumma", "Honky Ch\u00e2teau", "Fatal Attraction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Elton John?", "answers": ["Night Visions", "The Final Frontier", "Christiane F.: Wir Kinder vom Bahnhof Zoo", "The Diving Board"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by TGT?", "answers": ["Live 2 Tell", "Favourite Worst Nightmare", "Friends", "Three Kings"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Calvin Harris?", "answers": ["Backtracks", "A Real Live Dead One", "Ready for the Weekend", "The Best of The Doors"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Calvin Harris?", "answers": ["I Created Disco", "The Best of the Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Blurred Lines", "The Script"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Calvin Harris?", "answers": ["At the Apollo", "18 Months", "Fade 2 Black - The Mixtape", "Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Funhouse", "Scary Monsters (and Super Creeps)", "Insomniac", "Elvis' Golden Records"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["XX", "M!ssundaztood", "A Girl like Me", "Please Please Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Outakes and Demos 1985-1988", "Pink: Live in Europe", "Different Stages Live", "The Complete Zabriskie Point Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Iron Man: The Best of Black Sabbath", "Funhouse Tour: Live in Australia", "The Remix", "Thursday"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["The Very Best of Eagles", "Queen on Fire \u2013 Live at the Bowl", "Blue Wild Angel: Live at the Isle of Wight", "Live From Wembley Arena"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["The Uplift Mofo Party Plan", "Can't Take Me Home", "Sk8er Girl", "Cabala"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Kornography", "Evolver", "Return of the Champions", "Greatest Hits... So Far!!!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Babel", "Feedback", "Pink's fifth studio album", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1", "Try This", "Playlist: The Very Best of the Backstreet Boys", "No Life 'Till Leather"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Finally Famous", "The Road to Carter 4", "The Dynasty: Roc La Familia", "The Album Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["500 Degreez", "Meteora - Live Around the World", "I'm Not Dead", "Howwa 3 Dynastia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Old Record", "The Truth About Love", "The Downward Spiral", "Westside Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Thriller 25 Super Deluxe Edition", "Jal Pari", "Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Yesshows", "Oracular Spectacular", "Pink Box", "Burning Desire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pink?", "answers": ["Kinky Reggae", "The Hits 2000-2006", "The Lost Tapes 2", "Valleys of Neptune"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Inspirations Part I", "Smells Like Punk Spirit", "God's Plan", "The Drought Is Over 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Absolution Tour", "Halcyon", "Revival", "Absolutely Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Origin of Symmetry", "L.A. Woman", "Outcesticide: In Memory of Kurt Cobain", "The Future Is Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Showbiz", "DJ Mix", "I\u2019m With You", "Blessed"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["The Mighty Bob Marley", "On Fire", "HAARP", "Codeine Cowboy (A 2 Chainz Collective)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Class of '06: World's Best Dressed Label Under G.O.O.D Music", "Any Given Thursday", "This Is A Muse Demo", "Platinum Collection 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Story of My Life", "\u2026and Justice for All", "Black Holes and Revelations", "Bangerz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Boss's Birthday Party", "Absolution", "Ready 2 Die", "[a_CROSS//the_EARTH]:: Tear Down The Walls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Hell Best", "Promised Land", "The Singles Collection", "2 Tracks Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Devil in a Blue Dress", "Hullabaloo Soundtrack", "Sector 1", "The Drought Is Over Pt. 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["The 2nd Law", "Me Against the Music", "Tha Gangsta Mix", "The Kings of Hell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["The New Breed", "Born to Run", "Newton Abbot Demo", "A Kind of Magic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["True (Deluxe Edition)", "The Resistance", "All That There Ever Was (1988-2008)", "Morrison Hotel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Muse?", "answers": ["Live @ Lowlands (24.08.2001)", "Take a Bow (remixes)", "Seventh Studio Project", "Under the Red Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The Vault... Old Friends 4 Sale", "Family Jewels", "Curtain Call: The Hits", "Freshmen Adjustment 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The S Dot Carter", "No Bull: The Director's Cut", "2002: New York", "0 Fucks Given"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["If You Want Blood You've Got It", "Hallucinogenic Recipe", "Interstellar Encore", "Ready 4 War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Fatal Attraction", "Hard & Hot", "Hannah Montana 3", "Ballbreaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Elvis: 2nd to None", "Riot Act", "Tokyo Road: Best of Bon Jovi", "Live From the Atlantic Studios"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Stiff Upper Lip", "A Day at the Races", "Three Kings", "Feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Darkness on the Edge of Town", "Street-Legal", "Live", "Still Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["All of the Above", "Long Road Out of Eden", "Hell Best", "Transmissions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Jigoku-Retsuden", "Highway 61 Revisited", "Plug Me In", "Dangerous"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Kaya", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "The Black & Tan Album", "Live from Live Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["A Real Live Dead One", "xero", "AC/DC Live", "21 at 33"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Purple Sabbath", "Powerage", "Demi Lovato"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Radiohead Box Set", "Soundtrack Recordings from the Film Jimi Hendrix", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Trilogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The Rules of Hell", "Kornoise", "For Bon Far Gone", "Blue Hawaii"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["MGMT", "Bon Scott Rarities", "Live in Vegas Instrumentals", "Never Done Before"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Love Land", "Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Blow Up Your Video", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Nastradamus", "Live at River Plate", "Live: Friday the 13th", "Star Power"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Bad Boy Boogie (live)", "Meddle", "The Entire Population of Hackney", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The Best of AC/DC", "\"Music From \"\"The Elder\"\"\"", "Queen in Nuce", "King of Reggae"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Best of AC/DC", "Bon Jovi", "Battle Studies", "Bob Dylan at Budokan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Chris Brown", "iTunes Festival: London 2010", "Welcome to the New Administration", "High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Another Side of Bruce Springsteen", "Babylon by Bus", "Iron Man 2", "The Language of My World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down", "Volts", "Wrecking Ball", "Radiohead for Haiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Rave In2 the Joy Fantastic", "8 Mile", "Highway to Hell", "Controversy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["In the Present: Live From Lyon", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "21st Century Breakdown", "Fly on the Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Beneath the Boardwalk", "In the Zone / Circus", "AC/DC Gold 2000", "Best of Kanye West"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Get Lifted", "Amnesiac", "Black Ice", "The Eagles / Desperado"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Elvis in Concert", "Greatest Hits", "Age of Giants", "Doggy Stuff"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Tailgates & Tanlines", "Who Made Who", "Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "Absolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Buddha Promo", "Dungeon Demo", "For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)", "Automatic Gunfire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Back in Black", "Valleys of Neptune", "Stages", "Inspirations Part I"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Red", "Bonfire", "Sigh No More", "Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Space Odyssey", "The Crown", "2000 Collection", "Kaya"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Any Given Thursday", "Ride on Bon", "Behind Da Bars", "iTunes Live From SoHo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 98", "Sunday Down South", "Greatest Hell's Hits", "From the Vaults Vol.4"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Dub Tribute to Linkin Park", "Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones", "Booze Blues N' Tattoos", "Digital Decks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Golden Ballads", "See You Again: 2008 Mix", "Looking Back to Yesterday", "Preaching the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Lateralus", "The Razors Edge", "The Don Killuminati: The 7 Day Theory", "Broken Arrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Shenanigans", "Vitalogy", "Tha Last Meal", "Backtracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["The Path of Totality Tour \u2013 Live at the Hollywood Palladium", "Chances Are", "Panjaban", "T.N.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Room for Squares", "Greatest Hits", "Live at Budokan", "Warning! High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Flies on the Soundboard", "Live at the BBC", "In Brazil: LP", "Modern Vampires of the City"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["BBC Session", "Death Magnetic", "I Might Be Wrong: Live Recordings", "Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Until the End of Time", "The Drought Is Over 5", "Live: 2 CD Collector's Edition", "Free Bricks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Follow the Leader", "Maiden England", "Tomorrow Never Knows", "AC/DC in the 20th Century"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90", "Let There Be Rock", "Legacy: The Absolute Best", "Erotica"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Higher Ground", "Greatest Hits", "Maximum Rock N' Roll", "The Very Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Rumours", "Argenfornication", "Boxed", "Flick of the Switch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by AC/DC?", "answers": ["Stiff Upper Lip Tour Edition", "Viva la Vida / X&Y", "Amazing Love", "Love in the Future"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Born Again", "Greatest Hits Live", "Fleetwood Mac in Chicago", "NASA Music 2: Space Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Unbreakable", "Burning Desire", "Man on the Moon III", "Live and Fucked Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Anthology 3", "Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "Live and Fucked Up", "The Best of Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["The Singles 1999\u20132006", "Return of the Champions", "Dat Kid From Cleveland", "Woodstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Toy", "Rock in Rio", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "Indicud"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["On Stage", "On Another Planet", "Goats Head Soup", "Louis Vuitton Spring"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Rap Hard", "The Indispensable Collection", "Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks", "The Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["A Kid Named Cudi", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990", "Millenium Hits 2000", "Live at Montreux 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Space Odyssey", "Stone's Been Rolled Away", "The Truth About Love", "Love and War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["Atom Heart Mother", "Soul Shakedown Party", "NASA Music", "Tha Massacre (bonus disc)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kid Cudi?", "answers": ["The Union", "Meteora", "Man on the Moon II: The Legend of Mr. Rager", "The Art of Letting Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Reasonable Doubt", "All That Glitters Is Gold", "Hannah Montana 2 / Meet Miley Cyrus", "Prince from Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Decks n' Drums n' 909", "AC/DC in the 20th Century", "Hannah Montana 3", "Youth and Young Manhood / Aha Shake Heartbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana", "Britney Spears: Live and More!", "Never Done Before", "Ozzy Meets the Priest"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Best of Hannah Montana", "Madman Across the Water", "The Biggest Thing Since Colossus ...", "Right In Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Killers", "Planet Earth", "Hannah Montana: Hits Remixed", "Rocafella"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["From Elvis in Memphis", "Lucky Town", "5 Album Set", "Breakout"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana: Karaoke From the Hit TV Show", "Farewell Tour I", "Love Songs", "Oops!...I Did It Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["The One", "Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection", "Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection", "See You Again: 2008 Mix"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Greatest Hits Live", "Jigoku-Retsuden", "Golden Legends"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Live in New York", "Let's Dance", "Hannah Montana Forever", "Reality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Mac & Devin Go to High School", "Korn: Collected", "Can't Be Tamed", "X & Y Live 2005"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["All The Hits", "Ultra Rare Trax", "Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "Bangerz"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["No Stopping Me", "R & G (Rhythm & Gangsta): The Masterpiece", "Dreams of Freedom", "The Hits: Chapter One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Miley Cyrus?", "answers": ["Something to Remember", "Fly by Night", "Hannah Montana 2: Non-Stop Dance Party", "Breaking Hearts"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Immortal In-House Cassettes", "All That Glitters Is Gold", "Wide Eyes Blind Love", "Until the End of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["That's the Way Through the Out Door", "Born to Die", "Dangerously in Love", "Ciara"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin Boxed Set", "The Resistance", "Blurred Lines", "Around the World in a Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Mighty Bob Marley", "In His Own Words", "A Collection of Michael Jackson's Oldies", "Gonzaga '68"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1969-1971", "Dead Man Walkin", "The Bernstein Tapes", "Elvis Is Back!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Collection 1973-84", "An Evening With", "Hammer of Gods", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet Re-Release"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Song Remains the Same", "Brussels Affair (Live 1973)", "Hard Rain", "Tiny Desk Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["You Shook Me", "Christmas", "The Drought Is Over", "The Here After"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Dark Emotion", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "Early Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume One", "Kiss My Ass: The Video"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Live on Blueberry Hill", "Panjaban", "Greatest Hits III", "These Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Selected Works 1972-1999", "Voodoo Child: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Physical Rarities", "Bounce"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Based On a T.R.U. Story", "Tattoo You", "The Complete BBC Radio Sessions", "The Sun Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Past Lives", "Dead Man", "Stone's Been Rolled Away", "Greatest Hits 1973-1982"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["What Separates Me from You", "Natty Dread", "The Big Picture", "Coda"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin Boxed Set 2", "Crush", "4 Intimate Nights With Beyonc\u00e9", "Unmasked"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Hot Rocks 1964-1971", "School Daze", "Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970", "Mr. Wonderful"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["In the Zone", "Live in Pittsburgh 1970", "Doggystyle", "Cabala"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Stars Dance", "Listen to This Eddie", "The Green Day Collection", "Sliver: The Best of the Box"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Dreams of Freedom", "Live at the Bowl '68", "Antrabata Sessions", "Best of Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Jigoku-Retsuden", "Love Land", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet", "Whole Lotta Rock!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["In Da Hood", "Prairie Wind", "The Prequel", "Further Down the Spiral"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Pyass", "R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour", "Led Zeppelin Remasters", "Cross Purposes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Rush in Rio", "Destroyer", "Heartbreak Drake", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "Justified", "Classic Ballads", "Trouble Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Once Again", "DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "Girl Happy", "Mothership"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The 20/20 Experience: The Complete Experience", "Led Zeppelin BBC Sessions", "Land of the Free Home of the Brave", "Small Axe"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Early Avenged Sevenfold releases", "For Badgeholders Only", "Spring Break... Here To Party", "Soul Rebel & Other Great Reggae Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["2Pac Live", "Houses of the Holy", "Dark Emotion", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Three Kings", "La voix du Rock", "For the Fans (disc 2)", "Golden Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Greatest: Duets", "So You Wanna Freestyle?", "Presence", "Settle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Numb", "Led Zeppelin", "Anyway", "Awake"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Live at SOB's New York City", "Halcyon", "MGMT", "Celebration Day"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Don't be Fooled by the Name", "Led Zeppelin III", "Funhouse", "That's My Work Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["In Rainbows: From the Basement", "Survival", "The Last Rehearsal", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin IV", "Beggars Banquet", "Live Rust", "The Doors: Vinyl Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Definitive Collection Mini LP Replica CD Boxset", "Songs for Communion", "Southern G'z", "Serious Moonlight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Nas & Ill Will Records Presents QB's Finest", "How the West Was Won", "The Studio Albums 1990\u20132009", "Live. Love. ASAP"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away...", "Burn Like a Candle", "The (Unofficial) Black Album Remix (vs. Paul Nice)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Selected Works 1972-1999", "Latter Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume Two", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls", "Fleetwood Mac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Gotham City Clubbin Part 2", "Brutal Artistry", "Yesterday\u2026 and Today", "The Great Bob Marley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["My Favorite Videos (So Far)", "Digital Decks", "Profiled", "Aftermath"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Studio Daze", "Live At The Aquarius Theatre: The First Performance", "No Stopping Me", "B.O.A.T.S. II: Me Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Live Tracks", "Love & Death", "The Complete Studio Recordings", "Reg Strikes Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Unbroken", "Fortune", "Maximum Led Zeppelin", "Men of the World: The Early Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition", "2 of One", "A Tribute to Johnny Kidd and the Pirates", "To Be Continued..."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Complete Zabriskie Point Sessions", "Hannah Montana: Karaoke From the Hit TV Show", "As Recorded at Madison Square Garden", "Riverside Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["In Through the Out Door", "Grunge Is Dead", "T.R.U. REALigion", "Sugar Mountain - Live At Canterbury House 1968"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["The Best of Red Hot Chili Peppers", "The Wall", "Time and a Word", "Olympic Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Legacy: The Absolute Best", "Around the World", "The Ultimate Fan Extras Collection", "Physical Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Led Zeppelin?", "answers": ["Songs for Communion", "Encore", "MGMT", "Led Zeppelin II"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by /Passenger?", "answers": ["Back in Black", "R30 - Live in Frankfurt", "The Pursuit of Freedom", "Wicked Man's Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Demi Lovato", "AC/DC in the 20th Century", "Bringing It All Back Home", "No Security"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Stone Age", "Madman Across the Water", "Another Side of Bob Dylan", "Ultimate"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Live at the 10 Spot", "Doggystyle", "Backspacer", "Together Through Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Greatest Singles Collection", "The Remix", "Live at Pompeii", "Saved"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["A Decade of Silence", "Christmas in the Heart", "Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "Live 2 Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["This Left Feels Right Live", "Unified:Praise", "Classic Yes", "Modern Times"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Asylum", "The Emancipation of Mimi", "Biograph", "Abbey Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Then Play On", "The 50th Anniversary Collection", "Caribou", "T.N.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Prefix", "World Ballads Collection", "Live from Live Earth", "The Essential Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Commission", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 10 \u2013 Another Self Portrait", "Born Again", "Ready 2 Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Jimi Plays Berkeley", "Never Done Before", "A Tree with Roots", "Curtain Call: The Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["HOWWA 2", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 8 \u2013 Tell Tale Signs: Rare and Unreleased 1989\u20132006", "Neidermayer's Mind", "The Golden Unplugged Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["LiveAndWell.com", "Makaveli 2: When My Enemies Fall", "Love Land", "Tempest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Blonde on Blonde", "A Bunch of Rarities: Is This Legal?", "Hullabaloo Soundtrack", "Daydream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001", "Hard Rain", "Megaforce demo", "Death Row's Snoop Doggy Dogg Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Times They Are a-Changin'", "VH1 Storytellers", "Amsterdam '69", "Flight of the Crow"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Bonez Tour 2004: Avril's 20th Birthday Party", "Live in Praha", "Bob Dylan's Greatest Hits", "Promised Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Lights", "Space Odyssey", "Shot of Love", "Dynamic Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Carnival of Souls: The Final Sessions", "The Freewheelin' Bob Dylan", "Africa Unite: The Singles Collection", "The Baggy's Rehearsal Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Live Magic", "The Vaudeville Years: 1968 to 1970", "N.E.W.S.", "Down in the Groove"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Return of the Champions", "Watch the Throne", "Pac-Man Punch", "Blood on the Tracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Under the Red Sky", "Ring of Fire: The Best of Johnny Cash", "Youth & Young Manhood", "Immortal In-House Cassettes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Oh Mercy", "Backspacer", "The Greatest Rapper Alive", "One of the Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Jump Back: The Best of the Rolling Stones", "Before the Flood", "Ring the Alarm: Remixes", "Live From Philadelphia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Planet Waves", "Under My Skin", "Nimrod", "Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Let It Bleed", "Slow Train Coming", "Ragged Glory", "For the Fans (disc 2)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Bob Dylan", "I Created Disco", "Playlist: The Very Best of Mariah Carey", "Live at the Fillmore East"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Kinky Reggae", "Live from London", "New Morning", "The New Breed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Songs From the West Coast", "Bob Dylan at Budokan", "Divers & Submarines", "Watch the Throne"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Street's Disciple", "Live 2003", "Nashville Skyline", "Mr. Wonderful"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Dylan & The Dead", "Love & Death", "The Bright Midnight Sampler", "Hymns by Johnny Cash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Live on Two Legs", "Open Your Eyes", "Legend of Hip Hop", "Love and Theft"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Revival", "Keep on Moving", "Try to Shut Me Up Tour 2003 [Weekend Music]", "Bob Dylan: the Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Connect Set", "Born and Raised", "All the Little Lights", "World Gone Wrong"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Keys to Ascension 2", "Legacy: The Absolute Best", "Time Out of Mind", "Boston Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "Live After Death", "Elvis: Viva Las Vegas", "Bob Dylan: The 30th Anniversary Concert Celebration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Knocked Out Loaded", "The Adventures of Mimi", "Antrabata Sessions", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["More Malice", "Live in Boston", "Diary of a Soldier", "The Best of Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Street-Legal", "Live on the Other Side", "Random Access Memories", "Live Compilation"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Rattlesnake Shake", "Sucka Free", "Good as I Been to You", "Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Basement Tapes", "Over the Counter", "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "Monster"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Infidels", "Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band", "Viva Elvis", "Human After All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["\"The Born in the U.S.A. 12\"\" Single Collection\"", "Never Say Die!", "Orlando 2000", "John Wesley Harding"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Great White Wonder", "Born to Run", "The 20/20 Experience", "Blackout"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Live on Blueberry Hill", "Live in Cologne", "Highway 61 Revisited", "War Heroes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Peachtree Road", "In the Zone", "Desire", "Live from Le Cabaret"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Cole World: The Sideline Story", "Relics", "Live at the Riverboat 1969", "Empire Burlesque"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["The Bootleg Series Vol. 9 \u2013 The Witmark Demos: 1962\u20131964", "Aladdin Sane", "New Jersey: The Videos", "Kornoise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Dylan?", "answers": ["Demi Lovato", "Remix Album", "Elvis Presley", "Self Portrait"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Lorde?", "answers": ["The Singles Collection", "Come", "The Sun Sessions", "Pure Heroine"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Jimi Hendrix Concerts", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Closure", "The Language of My World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Makaveli 4: Thug in Me", "Road Rock Vol. 1", "Eminem Presents: The Re-Up", "Fixed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Street King Immortal", "Pretty Hate Machine", "In Through the Out Door", "Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Johnny Cash Children's Album", "Broken", "Super Soaker", "American Idiot"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Eagles / Desperado", "Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume II", "Aladdin Sane", "Year Zero Remixed"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Wasted Time (Minneapolis 25-02-1995)", "Purest Feeling", "Riot!", "Stone's Been Rolled Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Black & Blue", "Untitled Nine Inch Nails album", "The Early Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Things Falling Apart", "Got Live If You Want It!", "Ray of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Year Zero", "The Complete Blue Horizon Sessions: 1967\u20131969", "Bounce", "Houses of the Holy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Best Of", "Ode to Deodorant / Brothers + Sisters", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth", "Triumphant (Remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["B'Day", "Sector 2", "The Very Best of Kiss", "Further Down the Spiral"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["War Angel LP", "AM", "Live on Ten Legs", "Ghosts I\u2013IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Best Tour", "With Teeth: Summer Tour 2006 Radio Collaboration", "Vol. 2... Hard Knock Life", "My Worlds Acoustic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Best of Bob Marley", "Orlando 2000", "The Downward Spiral", "Definitive Collection Mini LP Replica CD Boxset"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Dat Kid From Cleveland", "Pot Luck", "When the Whip Comes Down", "Elvis Movies"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Hits 2000-2006", "Snakes & Arrows Live", "Killers", "All That There Ever Was (1988-2008)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Fragile", "Blaze Of Hits", "BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts", "Riot Act"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["On the Beach", "Thug Revolution", "The Graduate", "And All that Could Have Been"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Snakes & Arrows Live", "With Teeth", "Live in Texas", "Blessed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["Good Girl Gone Bad", "Any Given Thursday", "The Final Riot!", "The Slip"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nine Inch Nails?", "answers": ["The Essential Bob Dylan", "The Rise and Fall of Ziggy Stardust and the Spiders from Mars", "Hesitation Marks", "Heartbreak Drake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Civil Wars?", "answers": ["The Civil Wars", "Symphonic Live", "The Ballads", "S&M"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Civil Wars?", "answers": ["Live at Eddie's Attic", "Kaya", "Egocentric Plastic Men", "Meteora"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Civil Wars?", "answers": ["White Collection - Lion Of Zion", "The Underground Collection", "A Place at the Table", "Love in the Future"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Civil Wars?", "answers": ["Perception", "Eminem Presents: The Re-Up", "Barton Hollow", "Highway 61 Revisited"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by J. Cole?", "answers": ["Elvis in Concert", "Born Sinner", "The Dance", "Butterfly"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by J. Cole?", "answers": ["The Come Up", "In Da Hood", "The Here After", "Hot Space"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by J. Cole?", "answers": ["Friday Night Lights", "The Doors: Vinyl Box Set", "Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection", "Hallucinogenic Recipe"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by J. Cole?", "answers": ["Good Times", "Loving the Alien", "Talkin' Blues", "The Warm Up"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by J. Cole?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "Songs About Jane", "The Seventh Coming", "Cole World: The Sideline Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Shout to the Lord (Special Gold Edition)", "Dreaming Out Loud", "David Live", "Green Shadows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Mirage", "B-Sides", "Exit... Stage Left", "Hot Space"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Good Morning to the Night", "The Black Chronic", "The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Marley", "Shrine '69", "Thursday", "Unbreakable"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Penguin", "Stripped", "Issues", "Charmbracelet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Jazz", "Moist Vagina", "Mr. Wonderful", "Selected Works: 1972\u20131999"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Very Best of Fleetwood Mac", "Bon Jovi", "Cabin Fever 2", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Glitter", "In Da Hood", "Ultimate Collection", "Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Woodstock '99 Live Set", "The Golden Unplugged Album", "Rattlesnake Shake", "Live in Bucharest: The Dangerous Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Introducing\u2026 The Beatles", "SQ6", "Golden Legends", "Rumours Outtakes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Love Songs", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "Vintage Years", "Stranger Than Fiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Magical Mystery Tour", "Classic Yes", "Rumours", "The Bright Midnight Sampler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Doors", "Pop Disaster Tour 2002", "Tango in the Night", "The Very Best of Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["S&M", "Low", "Oh Mercy", "Who's the New Girl?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Boston Box", "Nebraska", "Unplugged at Jovem Pan", "When the Whip Comes Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Heroes Are Hard to Find", "My World", "Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming", "\u00a1Uno!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Access All Areas: A Rock & Roll Odyssey", "The Vaudeville Years: 1968 to 1970", "Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania", "From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Madison Blues Live", "The Massacre", "Cornerstone EP", "Beatles \u201965"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Black Magic Woman: The Best of Fleetwood Mac", "Hits of the Eagles", "Listen to This Eddie", "The Spirit of Radio: Greatest Hits 1974-1987"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Trenchtown Rock", "The Come Up", "Pre-Madonna"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Tusk", "Fantasy Ride", "Playlist: The Very Best of the Backstreet Boys", "Queen Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "Femme Fatale", "Bleeding Heart", "Show Your Glory"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Deal or No Deal", "25 Years - The Chain", "Greatest Singles Collection", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged", "The Pious Bird of Good Omen", "Fun in Acapulco", "Blood on the Dance Floor (HIStory in the mix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Gold", "Johnny Cash: The Complete Columbia Album Collection", "Say You Will", "Caribou"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["No Bull: The Director's Cut", "Hannah Montana 2: Non-Stop Dance Party", "Beginnings: The Lost Tapes 1988\u20131991", "Mystery to Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Outcesticide V: Disintegration", "Rastaman Vibration", "Hybrid Theory", "Preaching the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Latin Album", "God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project", "English Rose", "Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "Shakurspeare", "Ride the Lightning", "Fleetwood Mac in Chicago"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Prince from Another Planet", "Burn Like a Candle", "The Early Years", "Grunge Is Dead"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years", "Ultimate Collection", "Hesitation Marks", "Stars Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Future Games", "When the Whip Comes Down", "How the West Was Won", "GHV2 Megamix"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Live at the Boston Tea Party", "Live Rust", "With Teeth", "Eponyme"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Bare Trees", "Looking Back at...", "Freshmen Adjustment 2", "Spring Break... Here To Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Complete Blue Horizon Sessions: 1967\u20131969", "Hemispheres", "John Legend: Live from Philadelphia", "Keep on Moving"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Live in Boston", "Flight 666 - The Original Soundtrack", "3121", "Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Dreams of Freedom", "AM", "Kiln House", "Fade 2 Black - The Mixtape"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Heist", "Boston Live", "Epic", "Michael Jackson: Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["4", "Save Rock and Roll", "Fleetwood Mac", "Sorry 4 the Wait"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Boston Blues", "Golden Hits", "Trap-A-Velli 2: (The Residue)", "Diary of a Soldier"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Black Magic Woman", "Tracks", "Live at SOB's New York City", "Midnight Lightning"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Woodstock", "Men of the World: The Early Years", "The Very Best", "The 20/20 Experience \u2013 2 of 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Unreleased Tracks", "Behind the Mask", "Essentially Yes", "2Pac Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["The Collection 1973-84", "Backstreet's Back", "Then Play On", "Wake Up!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Tunnel of Love", "The Black Album: Acappella", "Listen to This Eddie", "The Original Fleetwood Mac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Finally Famous-The Mixtape", "The Dance", "The Most Gigantic Lying Mouth of All Time", "Batman"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "Thank Me Later", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\"\"", "The King of Limbs Live From the Basement"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["M!ssundaztood", "Tupac: Resurrection", "The Essential Fleetwood Mac", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Live at the BBC", "IV", "Rebellious Soul", "Household Objects"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fleetwood Mac?", "answers": ["Native", "UP: Unified Praise", "Ballbreaker", "The Biggest Thing Since Colossus ..."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["The Eagles / Desperado", "A Day at the Races", "Play", "Common Courtesy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["Live at Big Day Out 2000", "G.I. Blues", "And Their Name Was Treason", "18 Tracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged", "Homesick", "Acoustic Jams", "Mischief: The Mixtape"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "Old Record", "Immortal In-House Cassettes", "Rays of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["The Rolling Stones Rock and Roll Circus", "Lick It Up", "For Those Who Have Heart", "Lucky Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["72826", "Rock and Roll Over", "What Separates Me from You", "17 Numbers by the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by A Day To Remember?", "answers": ["Jimi Hendrix: The Singles Album", "American Pie + Best Songs", "2011-06-04: KROQ Weenie Roast 2011-live album", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by OneRepublic?", "answers": ["God Is Able", "The R. In R&B Greatest Hits Collection: Volume 1 (remix bonus disc)", "Waking Up", "The Bright Midnight Sampler"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by OneRepublic?", "answers": ["BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts", "Dreaming Out Loud", "Atom Heart Mother", "Rattlesnake Shake"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by OneRepublic?", "answers": ["The Final Frontier", "Madman Across the Water", "World Name", "Native"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["On the Beach", "Oh Mercy", "Millenium Hits 2000", "I\u2019m With You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Live Rare Remix Box", "Something New", "Rockin' Live From Italy 1993", "Remix Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Platinum Collection 2001", "Live at Slane Castle", "The Beatles' First", "The Club Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["What Hits!?", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape", "Salival", "Loving the Alien"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Reload", "Live at the BBC", "For You", "Under the Covers: Essential Red Hot Chili Peppers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The Best Of", "Evolver", "Smokefest", "Unfinished Business"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["T.R.U. REALigion", "Number 1's", "Live at S\u00f6dra Teatern", "Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["American Stars 'n Bars", "Box Set", "At Folsom Prison", "Platinum Collection \u201999"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Black Box: The Complete Original Black Sabbath (1970\u20131978)", "Rated R", "Power Flower Trouble Fruits", "Atom Heart Mother"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The Essential Iron Maiden", "By the Way", "Behind Da Bars", "MMM...COOKIES - Sweet Hamster Like Jewels from America!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Blood Sugar Sex Magik", "Essential Mixes", "A Night at the Opera", "The Fragile"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Innocence And Instinct", "E=MC\u00b2", "Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years", "Organic Soundball"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The First Ten Years: The Videos", "Forever Gold", "The Emancipation of Mimi", "Outakes and Demos 1985-1988"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Fatal Attraction", "Pistol of Fire", "Melodic Flea Way", "Tunnel of Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Piece of Mind", "Greatest Hits", "People Just Like Us", "The Blueprint 2.1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Best Ballads", "20Ten", "What Live Album !?", "Stillmatic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Live at the Orpheum Theatre", "The Uplift Mofo Party Plan", "The Lost Planet", "Best of Both Worlds Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Shindig Demo", "The Plasma Shaft", "Heart of Jamaica", "Black & Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Fly on the Wall", "The Beatles' First", "Off the Map", "B-Sides"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Makaveli 5: Thug Passion", "The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Daydream", "Best Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Katy Hudson", "The Best of Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Hannah Montana 2: Non-Stop Dance Party", "Doorie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["In da Club", "Live at Big Day Out 2000", "HOWWA 2", "Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Crystal Ball", "All the Little Lights", "The Vaudeville Years: 1968 to 1970", "Freaky Styley"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Lollapalooza '92", "Once Again", "Live 1994", "Forever Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["King of the Air Waves", "Rebirth", "Project Revolution", "Positive Mental Octopus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Jesus Is My Superhero", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape", "Distant Relatives", "Argenfornication"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Slap Happy", "Alive", "Stan: A Tribute to Eminem", "Daydream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["One Wild Night: Live 1985-2001", "Who Then Now?", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Zion", "Reflections", "Higher Ground", "The S Dot Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Californication", "SQ6", "Unbroken", "For This Cause"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The Best of David Bowie 1969/1974", "Live in Hyde Park", "Freedom", "Music from the Major Motion Picture Crossroads"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Insomniac", "Wake Up!", "X&Y", "Stadium Arcadium"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Woodstock '99 Live Set", "The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "Live at the Showbox", "Year Zero"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Red Hot Skate Rock", "Stiff Upper Lip", "Glitter", "A Real Dead One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Riverside Blues", "Green Day: Rock Band Soundtrack", "Alive 1997", "Tokyo Tattoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Rubber Soul", "The Basement Tapes", "The Best of the Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Going No Where"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Music Box", "Out in L.A.", "Neon Lights", "Here We Go Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta", "Immortal In-House Cassettes", "HOWWA 2", "Woodstock 99"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Visions of the Beast", "Untitled", "B-Sides", "Rebirth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Road Trippin' Through Time", "Absolution", "Rainbow Bridge", "All Saints"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Mother's Milk", "Rock to the Rock", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door", "No Life 'Till Leather"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Artpop", "Breaking Hearts", "Live at Budokan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["The Very Best", "The Complete Best Of", "Rust Never Sleeps", "Songs From the West Coast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Radiohead for Haiti", "Viva Elvis", "En Vivo!", "One Hot Minute"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Red Hot Chili Peppers?", "answers": ["Get the Funk Out", "Still Life", "Live Killers", "Madman Across the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["Midnight Lightning", "Man on the Moon III", "Training Day", "Live from London"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["Yield", "Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "No Sleep 'Til NYC", "21st Century Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["Finally Famous-The Mixtape", "In the Mix", "Section.80", "Greatest Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["Overly Dedicated", "Fun in Acapulco", "Curtain Call: The Hits", "Born This Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["2 of One", "Good Morning to the Night", "C4", "The Film-soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kendrick Lamar?", "answers": ["Youngest Head Nigga in Charge (Hub City Threat: Minor of the Year)", "MDNA World Tour", "Old Ways", "Red String Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Civil Wars", "Simply Worship", "Fuck Death Row", "Love Gun"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["That's My Work Vol. 1", "New orleans nightmare", "Love You Live", "Everyday Chemistry"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Gotham City Clubbin Part 2", "Snoop Dogg Presents Christmas in tha Dogg House", "Hyde Park Live", "Live in Pittsburgh 1970"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Massacre", "Another Side of Bob Dylan", "Dookie", "Puff Puff Pass Tuesdays Mixtape Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love (remix)", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Welcome To The Dogg House", "Introducing\u2026 The Beatles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Soul Captive", "Doggystyle", "Tracks Through Time", "Yesshows"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Blood on the Dance Floor (HIStory in the mix)", "Doggy Stuff", "Xpectation", "Live in Bucharest: The Dangerous Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Buddha Promo", "LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "Live in London", "Malice N Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Ozzy Osbourne Years", "Tha Dogg: Best of the Works", "Year Zero", "Somebody to Love (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Fixed", "The Best of Snoop Dogg", "Lights Out", "Essential Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Death Row: Snoop Doggy Dogg at His Best", "72826", "Riot!", "Who You Are"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album", "At His Best", "Made in the Shade", "18 Tracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Like a Prayer", "Continuum", "I Might Be Wrong: Live Recordings", "Tha Last Meal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Tyr", "Ego Trippin'", "Legacy CD1", "X&Y"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Bones", "The Essential Michael Jackson", "The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "The Platinum Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Rush Through Time", "Top Dogg", "Don't Forget", "Makaveli 8"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["iTunes Festival: London 2010", "A Real Dead One", "Doggumentary", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Jamaican Episode", "Forty Licks", "The Confessions Tour", "Live at the BBC"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["25 Years - The Chain", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "Out of Our Heads", "More Malice"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Prince of the City: Welcome to Pistolvania", "Aha Shake Heartbreak", "Lyrical Homicide", "Westside Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg - We Da West Vol 1", "\"\"\"Heroes\"\"\"", "Live Rust", "Merry Christmas II You"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Bible According to Black Sabbath", "Earthling", "Throw Your Dubs Up", "Call And Response: The Remix Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Katy Hudson", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 10 \u2013 Another Self Portrait", "Getcha Girl Dogg", "Kush & Orange Juice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Death Row: The Lost Sessions Vol. 1", "Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "The Late Mixtape", "Legacy: The Absolute Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Originals", "Presto", "Cabin Fever", "Paid tha Cost to Be da Bo$$"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Reincarnated", "White Collection - Lion Of Zion", "X&Y", "Working on a Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Daft Club", "A Tribute to 2Pac", "Neighborhoods", "2 Tracks Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape", "Bare Trees", "Lo nuevo y lo mejor", "What You Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Power (remix)", "Over the Counter", "The Essential Fleetwood Mac", "Live At Reading"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["I Wanna Rock Mixtape", "Meddle", "Blond Ambition World Tour Live", "Diamond Dogs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Rose That Grew From Concrete", "Mac & Devin Go to High School", "Profiled", "Metamorphosis"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["West Coast King", "Seventh Studio Project", "Dookie", "Black Panties"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Back in Black", "Smokefest", "Live at Eddie's Attic", "Hawks & Doves"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Good Girl Gone Bad", "Smokefest Underground", "Uno... Dos... Tr\u00e9!", "The Late Mixtape"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["As Recorded at Madison Square Garden", "B'Day", "No Limit Top Dogg", "Live Rare Remix Box"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Training Day", "Chrome Dreams II", "Legend of Hip Hop", "Dark Emotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Revival", "Only in America", "Radiohead Box Set", "The Bright Midnight Sampler"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Personal File", "The R. In R&B Greatest Hits Collection: Volume 1 (remix bonus disc)", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment", "For Colored Girls/Pre-Pain Medicine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Off the Wall", "Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "3rd Eye Girl", "Can You Handle Mine?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Nightmare", "Tha Carter IV", "Blaze!", "Aladdin Sane"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Best of Michael Jackson", "Loose Ends", "Doggy Style Hits", "Funhouse Tour: Live in Australia"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Between the Buttons", "Broken", "Death Row's Snoop Doggy Dogg Greatest Hits", "Ghosts I\u2013IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Dead Man Walkin", "Take This to Your Grave", "Cash Cow", "Alive 1997"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["\"The Doors \"\"No One Here Gets Out Alive\"\"\"", "Live at Bonnaroo", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Tha Doggfather"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Madonna Remixed", "Lucky Thirteen", "Vs. and Vitalogy", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Legacy CD1", "BBC Archives 1970-1971", "Scummy Man", "R & G (Rhythm & Gangsta): The Masterpiece"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["The Emancipation of Mimi", "Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works...", "Diamonds and Pearls", "Oops!...I Did It Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks", "Rush - Profiled!", "Texas (San Antonio)", "The Best of the Wailers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Snoop Dogg?", "answers": ["It's Barbie Bitch", "Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1", "Live at the Showbox", "1988"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Rocket Man: The Definitive Hits", "The First Ten Years", "You Can Dance", "Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works..."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Somebody to Love (remix)", "Strength Of The World (Single)", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)", "Live Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["By Your Side", "It's That Girl", "Chrome Dreams II", "Signals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["It's Alright", "Planet Earth", "Sexual Exposure", "The Chocolate Invasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Other People's Heartache", "The Immaculate Collection", "Justified", "Broken"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Beatles' First", "Hangami Halaat", "2006-04-29: Coachella Valley Music Festival", "Greatest Hits Vol 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["True Blue", "The Unplanned Mixtape", "In My Zone", "Farewell I Tour: Live from Melbourne"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Purple Album", "Off the Wall", "Pre-Madonna", "Musique Vol. 1 1993\u20132005"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["American Life", "Keystudio", "Meri Kahani", "Tree Full of Secrets"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Here After", "Pistol of Fire", "Slap Happy", "Rays of Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Living With War", "Confessions on a Dance Floor", "\u00c6nima", "Talk That Talk"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Art of Letting Go", "Greatest Hits (Disc 1)", "Iron Maiden", "The Blueprint 2.1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Superpop", "Crash Landing", "Don't Forget", "Looking Back to Yesterday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Marshall Mathers LP 2", "Magna Carta... Holy Grail", "Sticky & Sweet Tour Live in Buenos Aires", "Technical Ecstasy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Indigo Nights", "The Complete Studio Albums (1983-2008)", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Who's the New Girl?"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "Ray of Light", "2 Tracks Demo", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Bedtime Stories", "See You on the Other Side", "The Pious Bird of Good Omen", "Metallica Live in Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Please Please Me", "Rare Masters", "**** Live in Phoenix", "Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Grace Under Pressure", "Live Santa Monica \u201972", "Dungeon Demo", "Celebration: The Video Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Madonna: Dalle Origini Al Mito", "Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)", "The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "20 Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["E=MC\u00b2 Adventure Box", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990", "Limitless and Free", "Live at Slane Castle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Dirty Work", "Inspirations Part I", "What You Don't Know", "Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["I'm Breathless", "Led Zeppelin II", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "The Illmatic Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["God's Son", "Madonna", "Rated R", "The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Dynasty", "Erotica", "I Am... World Tour", "Hall of Fame"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Like a Virgin", "Flash Gordon", "Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter", "No Code"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Nigger Tape", "Madonna: The Confessions Tour", "The Embryo", "The Studio Albums 1989-2007"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["\"The \"\"Demo\"\" Tape\"", "The Complete Studio Albums (1983 \u2013 2008)", "Five Feet High and Rising", "Thriller 25 Super Deluxe Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["MDNA World Tour", "Bromance (remixes)", "Take Care", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Never Say Die!", "Love Land", "Like a Prayer", "Follow You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Madonna Collection", "Blood on the Dance Floor (HIStory in the mix)", "Lo nuevo y lo mejor", "Vs."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Something to Remember", "Soul Revolution 1 & 2", "\u00c6nima", "blink-182"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Live Shit: Binge & Purge (disc 3)", "GHV2 Megamix", "Don't Forget", "Live Rust"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["'Hours...'", "American Idiot: The Original Broadway Cast Recording", "American Life/Music", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative / Live and More!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Unplugged Again", "Battle Studies", "Rocks Germany 2001", "Cosmic Climb"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Re-ac-tor", "Blues", "In the Zone / Britney", "Original Album Series"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Greatest: Duets", "Tha Carter 2.5", "Hard Candy", "Inside Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Royal Box", "Natty Dread", "The Legend of Johnny Cash", "Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Flight of the Crow", "Magic", "Blond Ambition World Tour Live", "21"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Love & Death", "The Unplanned Mixtape", "Celebration", "Yes Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["The Evolution of Robin Thicke", "Pop Disaster Tour 2002", "Dance Hits & Remixes", "Stop That Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["A Collection", "Madonna Remixed", "Beneath the Boardwalk", "December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Untitled Korn album", "The Confessions Tour", "Live 1994", "Time Machine 2011: Live in Cleveland"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "Live at the Matrix 1967", "Confessions Remixed", "Alive!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["In the Beginning", "Fire: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Cheshire Cat", "Mixtape Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Remixed & Revisited", "The 2nd Law", "True", "Having a Blast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t Back Down", "American Pie + Best Songs", "Cherry Blue Skies", "American Gangster"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection", "For Those Who Have Heart", "MDNA", "The Best Damn Tour: Live in Toronto"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Super Club Mix", "Bye Bye Bruce", "Hot Space", "Never Say Die!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Madonna?", "answers": ["Freaked Out & Mixed Up!", "Doggystyle", "Who's That Girl", "Melodic Flea Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Born Is The King", "Around the World in a Day", "Live in New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Boss Keeps Rockin'", "New Morning", "LotusFlow3r", "The Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Live in Vancouver", "Virgin Songs", "[a_CROSS//the_EARTH]:: Tear Down The Walls", "Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Film-soundtrack", "The Very Best of Prince", "Is There Anybody out There? The Wall Live 1980-81", "The Beatles\u2019 Second Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg Presents Christmas in tha Dogg House", "Rave Un2 the Joy Fantastic", "Ego Trippin'", "Shine a Light"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["One Nite Alone... Live!", "Rastaman Vibration", "Before the Flood", "No Security"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life", "C4", "Soled Out", "C-Note"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["New orleans nightmare", "The Wall Singles Collection", "Parade: Music From the Motion Picture Under the Cherry Moon", "Lively Up Yourself"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["One Night in Japan", "MTV Unplugged", "Burn After Rolling", "Tokyo 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "Call And Response: The Remix Album", "Purple Rain", "Dedication 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Kid A", "Lodger", "Flick of the Switch", "Xpectation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "The Rising", "The Chocolate Invasion", "Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Open Your Eyes", "Reg Strikes Back", "Boom Chicka Boom", "Emancipation"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Power Metal demo", "The Hits: Chapter One", "One Nite Alone", "Infinite"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Heroes and Heroin", "Hollywood Affair", "Sky High: Presented by DJ Benzi and Plain Pat", "Prairie Wind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Mac & Devin Go to High School", "Live in London", "Elvis", "N.E.W.S."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Very Best of Fleetwood Mac", "Symbol Album", "Iron Man: The Best of Black Sabbath", "Daytrotter Session-live album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Batman", "The Complete BBC Radio Sessions", "Legacy CD1", "The Wiz: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Graffiti Bridge", "I Wanna Rock Mixtape", "These Days", "For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Time", "Hard & Hot", "Project Revolution", "Diamonds and Pearls"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Write Me Back", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "The Slaughterhouse", "Reload"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Bootleg Series Vol. 8 \u2013 Tell Tale Signs: Rare and Unreleased 1989\u20132006", "The Very Best", "No Life 'Till Leather", "The Rainbow Children"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Prequel", "Broken", "Finally Famous", "Crystal Ball"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Louis Vuitton Spring", "Sign 'O' the Times", "Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "In a Valley by the Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Behind Da Bars", "The Massacre", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape", "The Gold Experience"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["One Love", "The Freestyle Show", "Prince", "2000 Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Raretrax 2", "1999", "Anyway", "Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Live at River Plate", "The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "LiveAndWell.com", "Planet Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Lovesexy", "Nas & Ill Will Records Presents QB's Finest", "New Jersey: The Videos", "B-Sides"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Controversy", "Greatest Hits III", "Greatest Hits 98", "Discovery"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Manic Hedgehog demo tape", "A Collection of Great Dance Songs", "Absolutely Live", "Black Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Behind the Mask", "Monster", "NASA Music", "Indigo Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Hits 1", "Pulse", "The Collection", "Korn Kovers"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["12 x 5", "20Ten", "FACT Mix 327: Disclosure", "The Drought Is Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Archives", "Favourite Worst Nightmare", "Ultimate", "Sabotage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Live from SoHo", "School Daze", "Best Tour", "Alphabet St."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Looking Back at...", "The Hits 2", "Days Are Gone", "Stiff Upper Lip Tour Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Tiny Desk Concert", "Greatest Singles Collection", "The Hits/The B-Sides", "Soul Rebel & Other Great Reggae Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Olympic Gold", "My World", "The W. Carter Collection 2", "1999 Revisited"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["The Final Cut", "Amused to Death", "No Strings Attached", "For You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Vapor Trails", "Symbolic Beginning", "Today", "\"12\"\" Masters: Essential Mixes\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Daytrotter Session-live album", "Dream Factory", "Ready 2 Die", "In the Mix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Chaos and Disorder", "4 CD Catalogue Set", "En Vivo!", "The Boss Keeps Rockin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["C4", "Rock the Nation Live!", "Physical Rarities", "Musicology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Atom Heart Mother", "Slow Train Coming", "LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "3rd Eye Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Training Day", "The Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Makaveli 2000", "Dirty Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Loveland", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "Prince from Another Planet", "Newpower Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Pac's Life", "Penguin", "T.R.U. REALigion", "3121"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["not my fault", "Rave In2 the Joy Fantastic", "DJ Mix", "Fly by Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson", "Mothership", "The Vault... Old Friends 4 Sale", "Unplugged: The Complete Acoustic Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Prince?", "answers": ["Snakes & Arrows Live", "The Gospel According to David Bowie", "Girl 6", "Young Americans"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Rock of the '70s", "Live in New York", "The Fame Kingdom", "In Da Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["T.R.U. REALigion", "Dat Kid From Cleveland", "Best of Yes", "Cabin Fever 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Best of AC/DC", "Greatest Hits Live", "The Best of the Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Tokyo Road: Best of Bon Jovi"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["My World", "Forever", "90125", "It's Alright"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["LotusFlow3r", "The Wanted (Special Edition)", "2000 Demo", "YesStory"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The City Is Mine", "Best 99", "Yesstories", "Ghetto Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Classic Yes", "Saved", "Pink's fifth studio album", "Early Classics"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Physical Rarities", "Cornerstone", "The Singles Boxset (Previously Unreleased bonus disc)", "Drama"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Let's Dance", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles", "Fragile", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Who You Are", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth", "Yesshows", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Ladder", "The Tears Of Medusa", "An Introduction to Syd Barrett", "Splitting the DNA"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Astral Traveller", "Erotica", "Some Girls", "Music From the Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Journey Through the Past", "Live at Montreux 2003", "Tracks", "Animalize"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Look to You", "The Lost Broadcasts", "The Biggest Thing Since Colossus ...", "Sex Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Thursday", "Yesterdays", "Ghosts I\u2013IV", "Animals"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["13", "Black Box: The Complete Original Black Sabbath (1970\u20131978)", "Tormato", "Magical Mystery Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Freshmen Adjustment", "The Doors", "Other Voices", "House of Yes: Live From House of Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Greatest Video Hits", "Lost Treasures 1993-1997", "The Freestyle Manual", "Knocked Out Loaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Yes Remixes", "Life Is Good", "The Sabbath Collection", "Freshmen Adjustment 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Promised Land", "Climbing Up the Walls", "9012Live: The Solos", "Live!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["No Sleep 'Til NYC", "Rocafella", "Time and a Word", "Midnight Memories"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Labyrinth", "Binaural", "Essentially Yes", "iTunes Session"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Word Is Live", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1", "Diamond Dogs", "Splitting the DNA"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Dynamic Live", "Best of the 'B' Sides", "Symphonic Live", "Diamonds and Pearls"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Station to Station", "Greatest Hits III", "News of the World", "The Ultimate Yes: 35th Anniversary Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Hits 2", "Keys to Ascension 2", "Live at Slane Castle", "Wasted Time (Minneapolis 25-02-1995)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Backstreet Boys", "Snakes & Arrows", "These Days", "Topography: The Yes Anthology"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Highlights: The Very Best of Yes", "Greatest Hits", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "B-Sides of the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Don't Shoot Me I'm Only the Piano Player", "Open Your Eyes", "Aladdin Sane", "Simply Worship Three"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Fly From Here", "Moody Blue", "Martin Scorsese Presents the Blues: Jimi Hendrix", "Christiane F.: Wir Kinder vom Bahnhof Zoo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["In Nuce", "Going for the One", "What Separates Me from You", "Some Girls"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "Chrome Dreams", "Tales From Topographic Oceans", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Parachutes", "The T-Wayne Show", "In the Present: Live From Lyon", "The Ray Gillen Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Beatles\u2019 Long Tall Sally", "Magnification", "Rihanna 3CD Collector's Set", "Taylor Swift"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["With the Lights Out", "The Archives Vol. 1 1963\u20131972", "Tailgates & Tanlines", "The Solid Gold Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project", "In a Word: Yes (1969\u2013)", "Between the Buttons", "A Bigger Bang"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Outside", "Are You Passionate?", "Legend Remixed", "Close to the Edge"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Sabotage", "Greatest Hits", "Big Generator", "June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["In the Beginning", "In a World Like This", "Something's Coming: The BBC Recordings 1969\u20131970", "The Videos 1989\u20132004"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Keystudio", "Death on the Road", "Boom Chicka Boom", "Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Remixed & Revisited", "Relayer", "Dylan & The Dead", "Funhouse Tour: Live in Australia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["The Collection 1973-84", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment", "Union", "Puff Puff Pass Tuesdays Mixtape Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2", "God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project", "Union Live", "The Complete Studio Recordings"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Icon", "Catch a Fire", "Double Up", "The Yes Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["YesYears", "The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder", "Sliver: The Best of the Box", "From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Live @ Rex Club Paris", "Reality", "Keys to Ascension", "The Rainbow Children"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Loose Ends", "Under the Red Sky", "400 Years", "Yes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Talk", "The Blueprint 2.1", "The Black Album: Acappella", "True"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Blue Wild Angel: Live at the Isle of Wight", "Men of the World: The Early Years", "Jailhouse Rock", "Yestoday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Yes?", "answers": ["Harvest Moon", "Yessongs", "Live in Texas: 7 June 2006", "Blue Wild Angel: Live at the Isle of Wight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Miguel Jontel Pimentel?", "answers": ["Black and Blue", "Kaleidoscope Dream", "Fixed", "Sorry 4 the Wait"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Miguel Jontel Pimentel?", "answers": ["Stone Age", "The Dance", "Creatures of the Night", "All I Want Is You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Miguel Jontel Pimentel?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "Mischief: The Mixtape", "Science & Faith", "Metal Up Your Ass"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["TKOL RMX 1234567", "My Worlds: The Collection", "Caress of Steel", "Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Psychedelic Pill", "In Concert", "Cornerstone EP", "My World 2.0"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Believe", "Korn", "The Best of the Red Hot Chili Peppers", "The Wall: Live in Berlin"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "Flickering Flame: The Solo Years Volume 1", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Under the Mistletoe"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Live Magic", "Studio Daze", "I'm Breathless", "My Worlds Acoustic"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Reg Strikes Back", "Somebody to Love (remix)", "Mother's Milk", "Forty Licks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["This Left Feels Right Live", "Believe (Acoustic)", "Devils & Dust", "Rush in Rio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["A Year Without Rain", "Blaze Of Hits", "My Worlds", "The Late Mixtape"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Bieber?", "answers": ["Never Say Never: The Remixes", "Best of Yes", "More Experience", "Duets"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["The Streets Is Watching", "The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse", "With Teeth: Summer Tour 2006 Radio Collaboration", "Good Girl Gone Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Collaborations", "With Teeth", "Rated R", "New orleans nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["The Woman in Black", "Anthology 2", "Other Voices / Full Circle", "Mac & Devin Go to High School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Loud", "Amused to Death", "Around the World", "Rattlesnake Shake"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of Korn", "Devil in a Blue Dress", "The Singles 1999\u20132006", "Live at Eddie's Attic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Ale to the Thieves", "Early Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume One", "Barbadian Superstardom", "Latter Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["A Girl like Me", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "The Crown", "Flies on the Soundboard"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Justified", "Profiled", "Unapologetic", "Warning! High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "The Lumineers", "Diamond Dogs", "St. Anger"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Made in the Shade", "Until the End of Time", "Rated R: Remixed", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["All Over the Place", "White America", "Take a Bow (remixes)", "Every Song Tells a Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)", "Talk That Talk", "From Under the Cork Tree", "Live at Big Day Out 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Music of the Sun", "American Life/Music", "Preaching the Blues", "G.I. Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Live from Le Cabaret", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums", "Take Me Home", "Good Girl Gone Bad (remix bonus disc)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Coffret 4 CD", "Epic", "B'Day", "The Best of Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["When the Whip Comes Down", "This Is Rihanna", "Rocket Man: Number Ones", "Decade"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rihanna?", "answers": ["Rihanna 3CD Collector's Set", "Live in Vancouver 1970", "Soundtrack Recordings from the Film Jimi Hendrix", "Mothership"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Smokefest Underground", "DJ A-Trak & Kanye West: Welcome 2 Kanye's Soul Mix Show", "Best of AC/DC", "**** Live in Phoenix"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Wrecking Ball", "One Nite Alone", "Beast over Hammersmith", "From Under the Cork Tree"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["The Complete Studio Albums (1983-2008)", "Settle", "The Complete Zabriskie Point Sessions", "Infinity on High"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["The Queen Collection", "Sunday Morning Coming Down", "Revenge", "Believers Never Die \u2013 Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Mr. Wonderful", "A Thing Called Love", "Folie \u00e0 Deux", "Moody Blue"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["My Worlds", "Welcome to the New Administration", "The Essential Mariah Carey", "T.N.T."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Neidermayer's Mind", "Mother's Milk", "Rocket Man: Number Ones", "Save Rock and Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Street's Disciple", "NASA Music 2: Space Dreams", "ITunes Essentials - Fall Out Boy", "American Stars 'n Bars"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Fall Out Boy?", "answers": ["Power Metal demo", "\u00a1Dos!", "Take This to Your Grave", "Band of Gypsys 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["A Rush of Blood to the Head / Parachutes", "Me Against the World", "Beatlemania! With the Beatles", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["Road Trippin' Through Time", "Bob Dylan at Budokan", "Tokyo Road: Best of Bon Jovi", "Trap-A-Velli"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["All Ice on Me", "Video Pieces", "This Is A Muse Demo", "Kid A"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["Me Against the World 2: Codeine Withdrawal", "Insomniac", "One of the Boys", "My Worlds: The Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["Selected Works: 1972\u20131999", "Ozzy Meets the Priest", "The Resistance", "B.O.A.T.S. II: Me Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["Trap-A-Velli 2: (The Residue)", "Southern G'z", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan", "Heaven and Hell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["4 Intimate Nights With Beyonc\u00e9", "ISELECT", "Low", "Codeine Cowboy (A 2 Chainz Collective)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["Wicked Man's Rest", "Let Go", "Vs.", "Based On a T.R.U. Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 2 Chainz?", "answers": ["T.R.U. REALigion", "Infinite", "19", "The 20/20 Experience \u2013 2 of 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by James Arthur?", "answers": ["Tha Carter II", "The James Arthur Collection", "The Best Damn Thing", "Midnight Memories"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by James Arthur?", "answers": ["James Arthur", "Happy People / U Saved Me", "Dream Factory", "Best Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Harvest", "Trouble Remixes", "For the Fans (disc 2)", "Ben"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Ode to Deodorant / Brothers + Sisters", "Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)", "The Rising", "Slippery When Wet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "A Tree with Roots", "Freestyle B4 Paystyle", "Plug Me In"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Greatest Singles Collection", "The Remixes", "Tormato", "His Hand in Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["In Da Hood", "Unhappy", "Earthling", "X & Y Live 2005"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Rebellious Soul", "You Make Me", "4 CD Catalogue Set", "Waking the Fallen"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Wide Eyes Blind Love", "Number 1's", "Barbie World: The Mixtape", "Live 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["DJ Mix", "Viva la Vida or Death and All His Friends", "Wasted Time (Minneapolis 25-02-1995)", "Tales From Topographic Oceans"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["iTunes Festival: London 2011", "For Bon Far Gone", "Tokyo 1990", "Human After All"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["The Singles 1999\u20132006", "Pre-Madonna", "Plug Me In", "Greatest Hits 1970-2002"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Rave In2 the Joy Fantastic", "A Rush of Blood to the Head / Parachutes", "Simply Worship 3", "The Lost Prophecy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Keep on Moving", "The Path of Totality", "Queen Rocks", "Live in Charlotte"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["A Rush of Blood to the Head (instrumental)", "Manic Hedgehog demo tape", "Unreleased Tracks", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Live at the Matrix 1967", "Black & Blue", "Parachutes", "Knocked Out Loaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Live Santa Monica \u201972", "Heathen", "2 of One", "Viva la Vida / X&Y"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Smokefest Underground", "Greatest Hits", "Serious Moonlight", "The Purple Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["The Remixes (vinyl)", "The Collection: Britney Spears", "Science & Faith", "Delicate Sound of Thunder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["The Seventh Coming", "Boxed", "Ice on Fire", "Viva la Vida (The Dirty Funker remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Native", "Best of You", "Because of the Times", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Peachtree Road", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003", "Madonna: The Confessions Tour", "The Beatles Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Night Visions", "X&Y", "Nine to the Universe", "Meddle"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Limitless and Free", "Visionary: The Video Singles", "A Rush of Blood to the Head", "ITunes Essentials - Fall Out Boy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Coldplay Live 2012", "The Beatles in Mono", "Other Voices", "The Studio Albums 1990\u20132009"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Coldplay?", "answers": ["Live: Friday the 13th", "Listen to This Eddie", "Hot in the Shade", "Mylo Xyloto"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Year Zero", "Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones", "You Make Me", "Prince from Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Long May You Run", "Seek Bromance (Remixes)", "High Voltage", "Tupac: Resurrection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["The Fame Kingdom", "Greatest Hits (Disc 1)", "Untouchables", "Avicii Presents Strictly Miami"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Nebraska", "No More Thank Yous", "Pink Box", "The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Fade Into Darkness", "The College Dropout", "Training Day", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative / Live and More!", "True", "Love Songs", "Iron Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["Bromance (remixes)", "One Nite Alone... Live!", "The Sabbath Stones", "Neon Lights"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["The Beatles Box Set", "Alcoholic (Remixes)", "The Future Starts Here: The Essential Doors Hits", "\u00a1Dos!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Avicii?", "answers": ["The Bible According to Black Sabbath", "True (Deluxe Edition)", "The Essential Mariah Carey", "21"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ellie Goulding?", "answers": ["Halcyon Days", "Undercover", "Riot!", "The Baggy's Rehearsal Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Ellie Goulding?", "answers": ["The Original Soul of Michael Jackson", "Mr. Timberlake", "Halcyon", "American III: Solitary Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Ellie Goulding?", "answers": ["Seventh Heaven", "The Black & Tan Album", "Lights", "Showbiz"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Live from SoHo", "Coexist", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Live from Le Cabaret", "Fragile", "The Spirit of Radio: Greatest Hits 1974-1987", "Thursday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Good as I Been to You", "Towering Above the Rest", "It Won't Be Soon Before Long", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Only By the Night", "Is Anybody Out There", "Climbing to New Lows", "Rush in Rio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Soul Captive", "Erotica", "Live: Friday the 13th", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["iTunes Session", "Live @ Coachella '08-live album", "Live at the 10 Spot", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["When the Sun Goes Down", "In a Valley by the Sea", "Overexposed", "FoREVer"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["3rd Eye Girl", "Hands All Over", "Farewell My Summer Love", "Black Holes and Revelations"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["The Tears Of Medusa", "The Long Run", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment", "Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Unplugged at Jovem Pan", "Remix Album", "Songs About Jane", "Symphony: Alive IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Maroon 5?", "answers": ["Waking The Fallen Demo", "Call And Response: The Remix Album", "Heaven and Hell", "Mirage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Imagine Dragons?", "answers": ["Night Visions", "Feyenoord Stadium Night", "Rock Island Line", "Chikara"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Virtual Zabriskie Point", "The Complete Elvis Presley Masters", "The Singles Collection", "On Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Working on a Dream", "Welcome To The Dogg House", "Paranoid", "Keystudio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Blown Away", "Makaveli 4: Thug in Me", "Diamond Collection", "Talk That Talk"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Hannah Montana 2: Non-Stop Dance Party", "Bob Dylan: The 30th Anniversary Concert Celebration", "Behind Da Bars", "Live: Friday the 13th"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Curtis", "\u00c7a Ira", "Wake Up!", "On the Border"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Something Else", "Gangster and a Gentleman", "You Are My World", "The Best of Nirvana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Dedication 1", "Chronicles", "No More Thank Yous", "Before I Self Destruct: The Selects"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Jay-Z: Unplugged", "The Here After", "After Curtis", "Live at Montreux 2003"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Fun in Acapulco", "Playlist: The Very Best of Ciara", "By Your Side", "Before I Self Destruct"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Tha Massacre (bonus disc)", "Buddha Promo", "Show Your Glory", "Ready for the Weekend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["God's Plan", "Scary Monsters (and Super Creeps)", "Tribute", "Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Tha Doggfather", "Every Song Tells a Story", "Mixtape Legend", "Chant Down Babylon"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Hard Candy", "Bulletproof", "Killers", "For All You've Done"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Tokyo Tattoo", "Forever King", "The Hits 1", "Gotham City Clubbin Part 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Emancipation", "Dungeon Demo", "Talkin' Blues", "Guess Who's Back?"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Power of the Dollar", "Horsemen of the Apocalypse", "Coffret 4 CD", "The Very Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Coldplay Live 2012", "The Complete Studio Recordings", "Street King Immortal", "Heartbreak Drake"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Native", "In da Club", "Everybody's Rockin'", "MMM...COOKIES - Sweet Hamster Like Jewels from America!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["For Badgeholders Only", "Fresh Out Da Body Shop", "Martin Scorsese Presents the Blues: Jimi Hendrix", "Getcha Girl Dogg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Remix City Vol. 1", "The Bootleg Series Vol. 10 \u2013 Another Self Portrait", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Going No Where"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Millennium", "Freestyle B4 Paystyle", "Live 1994", "If You Want Blood You've Got It"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Can't Take Me Home", "John Legend: Live from Philadelphia", "Get Rich or Die Tryin'", "Music Box"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Looking Back at...", "50 Cent Is the Future", "Discovery: Bonus Tracks From daftclub.com", "The Dark Side of the Moon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The Urethra Chronicles", "Greatest Street Hitz", "Waking Up", "Look to You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["For the Fans", "Viva Elvis", "Greatest Hits '94", "War Angel LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["In Da Hood", "The Black Sabbath Story", "Collectors Box", "Madonna: The Confessions Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Pluto", "Avril Lavigne", "Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Computer K.O."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Hail to the King", "Burning Desire", "The New Breed", "Master of Reality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The City Is Mine", "Yes Remixes", "Olympic Gold", "Kiss Chronicles: 3 Classic Albums"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Best of 50 Cent", "Long Road Out of Eden", "Unmasked", "Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Around the World", "A Tribute to 2Pac", "Radio K.A.O.S.", "Diary of a Soldier"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Melodic Flea Way", "Good Girl Gone Bad", "The Future Is Now", "Spirit and Truth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["5 (Murder by Numbers)", "Reality", "Fan Can #2", "At Folsom Prison"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The Road to Carter 4", "G Unit General", "Soled Out", "A Matter of Life and Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The Best of Nas", "The Big 10", "Monster", "The Road to Red Rocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Empty Sky", "Lost Dogs", "24 Shots", "From the Muddy Banks of the Wishkah"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Live in Pittsburgh 1970", "Flickering Flame: The Solo Years Volume 1", "Nu-Mixx Klazzics Vol. 2", "The Massacre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The Lost Tape", "Symbol Album", "Tha Blue Carpet Treatment Mixtape", "Ultimate Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Dehumanizer", "From Ashy to Classy", "The R. In R&B Greatest Hits Collection: Volume 1 (remix bonus disc)", "What About Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["blink-182", "Lights Out", "Goodbye Yellow Brick Road", "Automatic Gunfire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["Rock 'n' Roll Music", "YesStory", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions", "Guess Who's Back Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 50 Cent?", "answers": ["The Winter Album", "Tha Gangsta Mix", "Hymns by Johnny Cash", "The Pursuit of Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Live on the Other Side", "Youth and Young Manhood / Aha Shake Heartbreak", "Live at Madison Square Garden", "Crazy Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Dedication 3", "Show Your Glory", "Come Around Sundown", "Power Metal demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Aha Shake Heartbreak", "Tha Carter", "People Just Like Us", "Having a Blast"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Contra", "Dream Factory", "iTunes Live From SoHo", "All Excess"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Live at Bonnaroo", "Sunfly Gold Vol. 34: Linkin Park & Limp Bizkit", "Soled Out", "Crush"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Reggae Legends", "Oklahoma City 1972", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1", "Manhattan"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Bob Dylan's Greatest Hits", "When the Whip Comes Down", "Because of the Times", "Broken Arrow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["The Fabulous Johnny Cash", "13", "Youth & Young Manhood", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Dehumanizer", "The Very Best", "Great White Wonder", "Pistol of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Obscured by Clouds", "Ragged Old Flag", "Boxed", "**** Live in Phoenix"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Super Soaker", "Wide Eyes Blind Love", "The Best Of", "Queen II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["BBC Radio 1: Christmas Gifts", "Absolute Greatest", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta", "Reg Strikes Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Soul Shakedown Party", "Only By the Night", "Justified", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kings of Leon?", "answers": ["Pac-Man Punch", "Mechanical Bull", "The Grey Album", "Bob Marley: Double the Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["American Life/Music", "The Metallica Collection", "Speak My Mind", "Touring Band 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Ozzy Osbourne Years", "Reload", "Elvis The King", "Live at the Roxy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Controversy", "The Beatles Box Set", "Master of Puppets", "Got Live If You Want It!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["American Idiot", "Horsemen of the Apocalypse", "Korn: Collected", "Shindig Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Death Magnetic", "Distant Relatives", "Live After Death", "Grace Under Pressure Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Best of Tool", "Death of Escobar", "Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Grooving Kingston 12", "Lights Out", "The Ray Gillen Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Backstage and Dangerous: The Private Rehearsal", "Live from London", "Fan Can #2", "NKOTBSB"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin II", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge", "The Entire Population of Hackney"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Outcesticide: In Memory of Kurt Cobain", "R.", "It's Only Rock'n Roll", "Acoustic metal"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Load", "Oracular Spectacular", "Best of 50 Cent", "KISSology Volume One: 1974\u20131977"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Daytrotter Session-live album", "Hunky Dory", "Cunning Stunts", "Under the Red Sky"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Let It Be", "Talk That Talk", "Bob Marley", "Kill 'Em All"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Lost Tapes: Limited Edition", "St. Anger", "Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "News of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon II: The Legend of Mr. Rager", "16 Biggest Hits", "Moving Pictures", "Megaforce demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Ride the Lightning", "Best of 50 Cent", "iTunes Festival: London 2008", "The Dynasty: Roc La Familia"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Quebec Magnetic", "A Farewell to Kings", "Cross Purposes", "Future Games"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Journey Through the Past", "St. Anger (studio rehearsals)", "Automatic Gunfire", "\"The \"\"Demo\"\" Tape\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["20th Century Masters \u2013 The Millennium Collection: The Best of Kiss", "Close to the Edge", "Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works...", "Metallica Live in Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Can You Handle Mine?", "Runaway Love (remix)", "Metallurgy", "Greatest!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Rebirth", "\u2026and Justice for All", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "Rock Island Line"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Pistol of Fire", "The Truth About Love", "Road to Revolution: Live at Milton Keynes", "Live from Live Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "Distant Relatives", "Black Tie White Noise", "Live at Wembley Stadium"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Reggae Lion", "Selected Works: 1972\u20131999", "S&M", "The Drought Is Over 2: The Carter 3 Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["2 of One", "Fleetwood Mac", "Jimi Hendrix: The Singles Album", "Get Yer Ya-Ya's Out!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Donington Live 1992", "Live at Woodstock", "Alcoholic (Remixes)", "Live in London: Antipodean Tour Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Friends In High Places", "Live Shit: Binge & Purge (disc 3)", "Olympic Gold", "The Buddha of Suburbia"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Thriller 25 Super Deluxe Edition", "Ode to Deodorant / Brothers + Sisters", "Double Up", "Lulu"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["LotusFlow3r", "Kiss Konfidential", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth", "Metal Up Your Ass"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The King of Limbs", "Power Metal demo", "Songs From the West Coast", "\"12\"\" Masters: Essential Mixes\""], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Personal File", "Household Objects", "Fan Can 4", "Before I Self Destruct: The Selects"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Deuce", "Marley", "Recrimination", "Metallica"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["The Beatles\u2019 Second Album", "The Early Days", "2Pacalypse Now", "Cliff 'Em All"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Kiss the Sky", "Rubber Soul", "People Just Like Us", "Garage Inc."], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["Ron McGovney's '82 Garage Demo", "Rocafella", "Pink Box", "Power of the Dollar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Metallica?", "answers": ["No Life 'Till Leather", "It's Alright", "The Latin Album", "Live: Walmart Soundcheck CD+DVD"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Blow Up Your Video", "The Torture Never Stops", "Never Say Die!", "Voodoo Soup"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Who Then Now?", "Rebel Music", "Dungeon Demo", "3rd Eye Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Power Windows", "Ultra Rare Trax", "Early Classics", "Get Well Soon..."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Zion", "Acid Attack", "Celebration: The Video Collection", "Korn Kovers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["FutureSex/LoveSounds", "Killers", "2002: New York", "Madman Across the Water"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Riverside Blues", "I Am Not a Human Being", "Flowers", "Take a Look in the Mirror"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of Korn", "Ego Trippin'", "A Single Man", "Born to Run: 30th Anniversary Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Sunfly Gold Vol. 34: Linkin Park & Limp Bizkit", "Ciara: The Evolution", "See You on the Other Side", "What You Don't Know"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Live From the Atlantic Studios", "Kornography", "Soul Revolution 1 & 2", "The Very Best of the Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Yestoday", "White Collection - Lion Of Zion", "Greatest Hits", "Pretty Hate Machine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Life Is Peachy", "Somebody to Love (remix)", "Yes Remixes", "The Best of Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Say You Will", "Live at Pompeii", "Got Live If You Want It!", "Live @ The Apollo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Platinum Collection 2000", "It Was... Remixed (Rare Unreleased & remixed)", "Elton John's Greatest Hits Volume II", "Mixtape Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)", "Issues", "This Is Us", "Live on Blueberry Hill"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Best Ballads", "Based On a T.R.U. Story", "The Rules of Hell", "Untitled Korn album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["World Ballads Collection", "Deuce", "Welcome to the New Administration", "Tyr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["The Biggest Thing Since Colossus ...", "Family Values Tour '98", "Rock Island Line", "Born Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["No Stopping Me", "Elvis The King", "MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Paradise Valley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Live", "Live at the Matrix 1967", "In Utero", "FoREVer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Tonight's the Night", "The Remix Suite", "Proud", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Voodoo Lounge", "Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "Wake Up!", "Neidermayer's Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Live at Slane Castle", "Crash My Party", "Olympic Gold", "KoRn Live at CBGBs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["A Bunch of Rarities: Is This Legal?", "By Your Side", "...Baby One More Time / Oops!... I Did It Again", "David Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Abbey Road", "Immortal In-House Cassettes", "Feyenoord Stadium Night", "Forever Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Unplugged: The Complete Acoustic Sessions", "Falling Away from Me: The Best of Korn", "Acoustic metal", "The Singles Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Korn", "Live at Big Day Out 2000", "Live at the BBC", "A Place at the Table"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Story of My Life", "God's Plan", "The X Factor", "The Path of Totality Tour \u2013 Live at the Hollywood Palladium"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Symphony: Alive IV", "Tonite Let's All Make Love in London... Plus", "Double Platinum", "Kornoise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["House of Yes: Live From House of Blues", "Gold Collection 1970-1971", "Super Hits", "The Ultimate Yes: 35th Anniversary Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Bob Dylan at Budokan", "Hot Space", "Family Values Tour 2006", "Inside Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Early Days: Best of Led Zeppelin Volume One", "Write Me Back", "Live & Rare", "His Hand in Mine"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Death on the Road", "Live on the Other Side", "Experience Hendrix: The Best of Jimi Hendrix", "Bruce Springsteen with The Sessions Band: Live in Dublin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["With The Beatles", "Freaked Out & Mixed Up!", "Behind the Mask", "VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Weezy Evolution", "The Path of Totality", "All Pink Everything", "Jake Bugg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["The Fabulous Johnny Cash", "Bob Marley & Peter Tosh", "Live at Montreux 2004", "Earth to Mars"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Tha Carter", "The Paradigm Shift", "Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003", "Nevermind It's an Interview"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["We Sold Our Soul for Rock 'n' Roll", "Yestoday", "Between the Buttons", "Korn: Collected"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Presto", "The Essential Korn", "Freshmen Adjustment 2", "Kiss Konfidential"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Meteora - Live Around the World", "13", "Korn Live: The Encounter", "One Nite Alone... Live!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Untouchables", "In Rainbows: From the Basement", "Settle", "Hannah Montana Forever"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Having a Blast", "Shangri La", "All Excess", "Follow the Leader"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Rasta Revolution", "...Baby One More Time / Oops!... I Did It Again", "The Music of Korn", "Live at the Orpheum Theatre"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Korn III: Remember Who You Are", "Get Rich or Die Tryin'", "VH1 Storytellers: Uncut", "Another Side of Bruce Springsteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Korn?", "answers": ["Forty Licks", "Freak on a Leash", "Manhattan", "Zanjeer -The Game Changer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Distant Relatives", "Live at the Showbox", "Fantasy Ride", "SuperDoors"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Backspacer", "Home for Christmas", "Lost Treasures 1993-1997", "The Beatles' First"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Triple Feature", "Live on Ten Legs", "The Club Remixes", "Pluto"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["The Future Starts Here: The Essential Doors Hits", "Live in Chicago 05.16.2006", "Britney Spears: Live and More!", "The Videos 1989\u20132004"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Nothing Was the Same", "Human After All", "Vitalogy", "Forever Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["R30 - Live in Frankfurt", "Live on Two Legs", "Taylor Allderdice", "Homegrown"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Breaking Hearts", "The Jam Machine", "Unbreakable", "Unrelease V"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["A Decade of Silence", "Animalize", "Something to Remember", "Ten"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "Soul Rebels", "DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "Pearl Jam Twenty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["No Code", "Ride This Train", "21 at 33", "Enema of the State Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Chant Down Babylon", "It's That Girl", "Live At Easy Street", "Keys to Ascension"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["World Gone Wrong", "Pearl Jam", "SuperDoors", "All Eyez on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Greatest Hell's Hits", "Rumours Outtakes", "Lightning Bolt", "Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Chant Down Babylon", "Pin Ups", "Live at Lollapalooza 2007", "On Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Love After War", "Taylor Allderdice", "Touring Band 2000", "At Folsom Prison"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["The Evolution of Robin Thicke", "Lost Dogs", "Live!", "Seventh Star"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Vampire Weekend", "Different Stages Live", "The Final Cut", "Vs. and Vitalogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["2Pac & Friends", "The Best of AC/DC", "Live at the Gorge 05/06", "Sheer Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Farewell Tour I", "Vs.", "Union Live", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Pac-Man Punch", "Dangerous", "Best Tour", "Undercover"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Picture My Pain", "Live in Stockholm", "Exit...Stage Left", "Viva la Vida (The Dirty Funker remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Live in Detroit", "Tha Carter III", "Binaural", "Love Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["The Best of AC/DC", "True (Deluxe Edition)", "The Singles Boxset (Previously Unreleased bonus disc)", "Live in Texas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Live in NYC 12/31/92", "Perception", "Blond Ambition Tour 1990", "Manhattan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Taylor Swift", "Riot Act", "The Drought Is Over 2: The Carter 3 Sessions", "Vapor Trails"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Behind the Mask", "Everyday Chemistry", "Headless Cross", "Live at the Orpheum Theatre"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Love Letter", "Yield", "Waking Up", "Triple Feature"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Double Up", "The Here After", "17 Numbers by the Beast", "Rearviewmirror (Greatest Hits 1991-2003)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Elvis' Christmas Album", "Coverin'", "Ultimate Queen", "Second Night Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Fight (For Your Cause)", "One Love at Studio One", "Backstage and Dangerous: The Private Rehearsal", "The Yes Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Pearl Jam?", "answers": ["Hallucinogenic Recipe", "Prism", "The Best of Both Worlds", "I Created Disco"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Thug Revolution", "Born King", "Backstreet Boys", "Towering Above the Rest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Tailgates & Tanlines", "The Hits: Chapter One", "S.Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Flowers", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)", "The Yes Album", "Greatest Singles Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Never Gone", "Discovery", "Man on the Moon II: The Legend of Mr. Rager", "Hemispheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Strictly 4 My N.I.G.G.A.Z...", "Playlist: The Very Best of the Backstreet Boys", "Roots of a Legend", "All We Know Is Falling"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["All Eyez on Me", "GHV2 Megamix", "Millennium", "A Real Dead One"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "For the Fans", "Hard Rain", "Circus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["A Rush of Blood to the Head (instrumental)", "Unbreakable", "A Show of Hands", "The King of Limbs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Doggy Stuff", "Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "Victim of Love", "For the Fans (disc 2)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["No Limit Top Dogg", "Old Record", "This Is Us", "The Lost Tape"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["In a World Like This", "Enema of the State Demo", "Take a Look in the Mirror", "Stiff Upper Lip"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Bullet in a Bible", "Kid A", "Power Dance Hits", "Best of AC/DC"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Black & Blue", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "The Mighty", "Bleeding Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["The I Heart Revolution: We're All in This Together", "Live in Texas", "20 Greatest Hits", "A Night Out with the Backstreet Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Voodoo Lounge", "Exit...Stage Left", "Cross Purposes", "Backstreet's Back"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["African Herbsman", "NKOTBSB", "The Slaughterhouse", "Metallurgy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Backstreet Boys?", "answers": ["Voodoo Soup", "TBA", "All Eyez on Me", "Return of the Champions"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)", "Goodies: The Videos & More", "Songs for Communion", "Dedication 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of Ciara", "The Complete Best Of", "Greatest Hits (Disc 1)", "Bleach"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 98", "My World", "Ciara: The Evolution", "Black Sabbath: The Dio Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["Simply Worship", "Fantasy Ride", "2007-10-16: An Evening With Avril Lavigne: Live From the Roxy Theatre", "Heartbreak Drake"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["Ciara", "The 50 Greatest Hits", "Room for Squares", "Stone Age"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["Symphonic Live", "A Real Live Dead One", "Goodies / The Evolution", "M!ssundaztood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Ciara?", "answers": ["VH1 Storytellers: Uncut", "June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets", "Bon Jovi", "Basic Instinct"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["iTunes Festival: London 2008", "Ikons", "Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90", "The Entire Population of Hackney"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Live at the House of Blues", "Shout to the Lord 2000", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan", "The Complete Studio Recordings"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Chant Down Babylon", "The Very Best", "From Fear to Eternity: The Best of 1990\u20132010", "FACT Mix 70: The xx"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Somewhere Back in Time: The Best of 1980-1989", "Singles Club", "Symptom of the Universe: The Original Black Sabbath 1970\u20131978", "A Single Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Tailgates & Tanlines", "Cheshire Cat", "Eddie's Head", "No Limit Top Dogg"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Video Pieces", "Deal or No Deal", "Metamorphosis", "NASA Music 2: Space Dreams"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Leather Jackets", "Listen to This Eddie", "Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Best of the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["In the Heart of Sin City", "BBC Archives", "Tree Full of Secrets", "Shout to the Lord"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Somewhere in Time", "Live. Love. ASAP", "Power Metal demo", "Unplugged: The Complete Acoustic Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Green Day Collection", "Nirvana", "En Vivo!", "Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Jigoku-Retsuden", "Catching Up With the B Sides", "KISS Alive! 1975-2000", "Destroyer- Resurrected"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Reasonable Doubt", "Mylo Xyloto", "Metallica Live in Concert", "17 Numbers by the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["VH1 Storytellers: Uncut", "In Concert MTV Plugged", "A Real Live Dead One", "Playlist: The Very Best of Korn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Love You Live", "Rock in Rio", "Harvest"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Essentially Yes", "Flash Gordon", "The Number of the Beast", "Follow You"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Watch the Throne", "Revenge", "Ed Hunter", "2004-09-17: Berklee College of Music Clinic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Merry Christmas", "Visions of the Beast", "It Was... Remixed (Rare Unreleased & remixed)", "Teenage Dream"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Prince from Another Planet", "The First Ten Years: The Videos", "HOWWA 2", "Absolute Greatest"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Death on the Road", "Queen", "St. Anger", "Death of Escobar"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The W. Carter Collection 2", "The 20/20 Experience: The Complete Experience", "Live in Philadelphia '70", "A Real Live One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Live After Death", "Number 1's", "Power of the Dollar", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The X Factor", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1", "The Unplanned Mixtape", "The Beatles' Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits", "Dance Hits & Remixes", "Live: Walmart Soundcheck CD+DVD", "Edward the Great"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Fear of the Dark", "Snoop Dogg - We Da West Vol 1", "The Very Best of The Doors", "Rasta Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Unorthodox Jukebox", "The Final Frontier", "Caribou", "Live at Budokan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Reasonable Doubt", "The Remixes", "Right In Two", "No Prayer for the Dying"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Studio Albums 1972-1979", "A Real Dead One", "Keys to Ascension", "Great White Wonder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Live in Stockholm", "Live at Pompeii", "Donington Live 1992", "R30 - Live in Frankfurt"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Keystudio", "Best Ballads", "S&M", "Iron Maiden"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Mariah Carey", "Ultimate Collection Volume II", "The Top Ten Hits", "B-Sides of the Beast"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Louis Vuitton Spring", "Insomniac", "KISSology Volume One: 1974\u20131977", "Powerslave"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Maiden England", "On Another Planet", "Dreams of Freedom", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Solid Gold Collection", "Dance of Death", "Playlist: The Very Best of R. Kelly", "Reanimation"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Fame Kingdom", "Over the Counter", "Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks", "Bye Bye Bruce"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Early Days", "Target Exclusive", "Harvest Moon", "Parade: Music From the Motion Picture Under the Cherry Moon"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Essential Iron Maiden", "What Live Album !?", "SQ6", "Melodic Flea Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Brave New World", "\"12\"\" Masters: Essential Mixes\"", "This Left Feels Right Live", "Stiff Upper Lip"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The First Ten Years", "ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne", "KoRn Live at CBGBs", "Tha Carter II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["American Life", "Virtual XI", "Blues", "Trin-i-tee 5:7"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["This Note's for You", "Ultimate Collection", "The Fame", "Computer K.O."], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Live at the Rainbow", "Shakurspeare", "The Studio Albums 1990\u20132009", "From the Vaults Vol.4"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Great White Wonder", "The Winter Album", "Promised Land", "Flight 666 - The Original Soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Behind the Iron Curtain", "Fly From Here", "Exclusive", "Soul Rebel"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Way He Wanted It", "With The Beatles", "Best of the 'B' Sides", "Ikons"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Codeine Cowboy (A 2 Chainz Collective)", "The Baggy's Rehearsal Sessions", "Killers", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Blue Hawaii", "Folie \u00e0 Deux", "Seventh Son of a Seventh Son", "The Miracle"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Fame and Fashion (David Bowie\u2019s All Time Greatest Hits)", "Beast over Hammersmith", "Untitled Nas album", "Jimi Plays Berkeley"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["The Metallica Collection", "A Matter of Life and Death", "Glitter", "Venus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Write Me Back", "Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones", "Piece of Mind", "Farewell I Tour (Bonus Disk)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Iron Maiden?", "answers": ["Live at Donington", "Working on a Dream", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "Live from Live Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Sleeping with Sirens?", "answers": ["Let's Cheers to This", "The Stripped Mixes", "Proud", "Batman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Sleeping with Sirens?", "answers": ["Gone Girl", "All of the Above", "Carry the Cross", "With Ears to See and Eyes to Hear"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Sleeping with Sirens?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "Feel", "At the Apollo", "Tokyo 1990"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["Live at the BBC", "Home for Christmas", "Best Selection", "On the Border"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["The Collection", "2004-09-17: Berklee College of Music Clinic", "The Underground Collection", "Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["Acoustic Jams", "Me Against the World", "Get Lifted", "Celebrity"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Scummy Man", "Meri Kahani", "The Legend of Johnny Cash"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["The Freestyle Manual", "Death Magnetic", "The Winter Album", "Reality"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["No Strings Attached", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth", "Vampire Weekend", "The Latin Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by 'N Sync?", "answers": ["Queen Rock Montreal", "The Best of Pink Floyd", "Key Cuts from Remixed", "*NSYNC"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["Hall of Fame", "Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "Steel Wheels", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["Detroit", "Grace Under Pressure", "1988", "Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big", "Tokyo Tattoo", "Yeezus", "The Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits (Disc 1)", "T.N.T.", "Greatest Hits", "Finally Famous"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["The Early Days", "Finally Famous-The Mixtape", "The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One", "The Most Gigantic Lying Mouth of All Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Big Sean?", "answers": ["Animalize Live Uncensored", "Take a Bow (remixes)", "The VS. Redux", "U Know Big Sean\u2013Finally Famous Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Script?", "answers": ["Rock Legend", "Coldplay Live 2012", "Penguin", "The Script"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Script?", "answers": ["Science & Faith", "Mylo Xyloto", "Get Rich or Die Tryin'", "Deuce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Script?", "answers": ["Call And Response: The Remix Album", "Nevermind: The Singles", "Believe", "#3"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Script?", "answers": ["Road Rock Vol. 1", "iTunes Festival: London 2008", "Ozzy Meets the Priest", "Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["It's Only Rock'n Roll", "Fatal Attraction", "Black Sabbath: The Dio Years", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Jump Back: The Best of the Rolling Stones", "Graffiti", "F.A.M.E.", "New Jersey: The Videos"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Millenium Hits 2000", "Still Life", "Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1", "Lodger"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Out of Our Heads", "'Hours...'", "Stranger Than Fiction", "Me Against the World 2: Codeine Withdrawal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["The Rolling Stones", "Elton John One Night Only \u2013 The Greatest Hits", "Vapor Trails", "A Nice Pair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Get Yer Ya-Ya's Out!", "Volts", "Dead Perspective", "Born This Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Unhappy", "Houses of the Holy", "The Rolling Stones Rock and Roll Circus", "27-5-94: The Astoria London Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["GRRR!", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)", "Road Rock Vol. 1", "Down in the Groove"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["A Bigger Bang", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Quebec Magnetic", "The Emancipation of Mimi"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["John Wesley Harding", "Metamorphosis", "Feel", "2011-06-04: KROQ Weenie Roast 2011-live album"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Grunge Is Dead", "Yield", "Loving the Alien", "No Security"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Dirty Work", "Lively Up Yourself", "Kaya", "Da Drought 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["The Pious Bird of Good Omen", "ChangesTwoBowie", "Some Girls", "Panjaban"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Bridges to Babylon", "Unhappy", "Elvis The King", "Past Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Live from Shepherd's Bush Empire", "808s & Heartbreak", "All Over the Place", "Between the Buttons"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Stone Age", "Tamar", "Exodus", "Can't Take Me Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Their Satanic Majesties Request", "DJ Hero Renegade Edition", "Yellow Submarine", "Live at the Fillmore East"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Valleys of Neptune", "Black and Blue", "Live @ Rex Club Paris", "Keystudio"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Let It Bleed", "Soled Out", "On the Border", "Deuce"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Queen 40", "Got Live If You Want It!", "Volts", "Catch a Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Duets", "The Ultimate Collection", "The Basement Tapes", "Beggars Banquet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Louis Vuitton Spring", "Exile on Main St.", "The Great Bob Marley", "Chocolate Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits", "Organic Soundball", "More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "Daft Punk Live in NYC"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Ale to the Thieves", "Brussels Affair (Live 1973)", "Re-ac-tor", "Radiohead for Haiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Flashpoint", "Spring Break... Here To Party", "Curtis", "At the Beeb"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Live at Eddie's Attic", "Girl 6", "Please Please Me", "Aftermath"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Bad Blood", "Hyde Park Live", "Hammer of Gods", "Playlist: The Very Best of Britney Spears"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Live from London", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live", "Emotional Rescue", "When the Whip Comes Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Steel Wheels", "An Introduction to Syd Barrett", "Best Selection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["People Just Like Us", "Undercover", "Wake Up!", "Self Portrait"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Makaveli 7: Lost Souls", "Virtual Zabriskie Point", "Unplugged: The Complete Acoustic Sessions", "Tattoo You"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Unapologetic", "Curtain Call: The Hits", "Made in the Shade", "Untouchables"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)", "Tha Carter 2.5", "Accoustic Concert Live Performance", "Backstreet Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["R30 - Live in Frankfurt", "Got to Be There", "Hot Rocks 1964-1971", "Recharged"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["How Fly", "Singles Collection: The London Years", "Hannah Montana Forever", "Seventh Studio Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Loud", "Cherry Blue Skies", "Stages", "Stripped"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["X & Y Live 2005", "Vitalogy", "Goats Head Soup", "I'm Breathless"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Newton Abbot Demo", "X", "Shine a Light", "Elv1s: 30 #1 Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["The Heist", "Rewind (1971\u20131984)", "Puff Puff Pass Tuesdays Mixtape Vol. 1", "In Utero"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["I'm Not Dead", "Sticky Fingers", "Nightmare", "All Saints"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Voodoo Lounge", "Manhattan", "It Was Written", "In the Zone / Britney"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)", "MDNA", "The Beatles' First", "Best of Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["The Carter Files", "The Singles", "Newton Abbot Demo", "Flowers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Recharged", "Love You Live", "Jake Bugg", "Folie \u00e0 Deux"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Sabbath Bloody Sabbath", "Live Licks", "Having Fun With Elvis on Stage", "Exodus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Moving Pictures", "It's Alright", "Atom Heart Mother", "12 x 5"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Aloha From Hawaii: Via Satellite", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles", "No Stone Unturned", "Curtain Call: The Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Parachutes / A Rush of Blood to the Head / Live 2003", "Human After All", "Serious Business DJ Clue & Keyz Collaboration", "Rolled Gold: The Very Best of the Rolling Stones"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The Rolling Stones?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "La voix du Rock", "Forty Licks", "Elvis: Ultimate Gospel"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Speak Now", "Live at the Riverboat 1969", "Breakout", "Sex Therapy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["The Evolution of Robin Thicke", "Circus", "Live at Hammersmith Odeon", "The Vault... Old Friends 4 Sale"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["2 Tracks Demo", "Fire: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Something Else", "Doggumentary"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Nu-Mixx Klazzics", "Love After War", "A Thousand Suns - Live Around the World", "Stranger Than Fiction"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Don't Forget", "Breaking Hearts", "Hannah Montana: Hits Remixed", "Blurred Lines"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Soul Adventurer", "Can't Tell Me Nothing: The Official Mixtape", "Dressed to Kill", "Cherry Blue Skies"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Robin Thicke?", "answers": ["Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "The River", "Tiny Desk Concert", "A Beautiful World"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns", "Collaborations", "Warning", "Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["The Studio Albums 1990\u20132009", "Self Portrait", "Something Else", "Bare Trees"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["GHV2 Megamix", "Lo nuevo y lo mejor", "The Best of The Doors", "Preaching the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Flight 666 - The Original Soundtrack", "In the Zone", "Cigarettes and Valentines", "End of Silence"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Grow Season", "Release the Panic", "On the Radio", "Dedication 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Live at the Matrix 1967", "Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "Oooh What a Green Day!", "Earthling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Live from Live Earth", "Nightmare", "Revolver", "More Boring Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["City of Evil", "King Creole", "Live From the Atlantic Studios", "Anyway"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Desperado", "Having a Blast", "International Villager", "Rap Phenomenon III"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Waking The Fallen Demo", "Transmissions", "Goodbye Lullaby", "Delicate Sound of Thunder"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Around the World", "\u00a1Uno!", "Snakes & Arrows", "You Make Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Pop Disaster Tour 2002", "The Streets Is Watching", "Metamorphosis", "The Doors Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Presence", "Only in America", "Still Life", "Last Night on Earth: Live in Tokyo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["\u00a1Tr\u00e9!", "R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour", "Power Metal demo", "The Dance"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Shindig Demo", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D", "Johnny Cash With His Hot and Blue Guitar", "International Superhits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["American Idiot", "Dedication: Gangsta Grillz", "B Is for Bob", "The Best of Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Con Todo", "Stiff Upper Lip Tour Edition", "21st Century Breakdown", "West Coast King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["One Nite Alone", "People Just Like Us", "Enema of the State Demo", "Kerplunk"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Shenanigans", "SQ6", "Losing It", "Can You Handle Mine?"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Uno... Dos... Tr\u00e9!", "Before I Self Destruct", "All Ice on Me", "Vitalogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Zanjeer -The Game Changer", "Diary of a Soldier", "Insomniac", "Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Awesome as Fuck", "The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Hunky Dory", "The Platinum Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Fixed", "American Idiot: The Original Broadway Cast Recording", "Rocket Man: The Definitive Hits", "Gnomeo & Juliet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["School Daze", "Second Night Unplugged", "Nastradamus", "Powerage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["NKOTBSB", "The Singles 1999\u20132006", "God Bless Amerika", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Outakes and Demos 1985-1988", "David Bowie", "Tha Gangsta Mix", "The Green Day Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Household Objects", "Viva la Vida or Death and All His Friends", "Aftermath", "Green Day: Rock Band Soundtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Gold", "Spitting", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues", "Good Times"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Egocentric Plastic Men", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta", "Flowers", "XX"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Live on Air", "Freedom Songs", "HOWWA 2", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Dedication 1", "The Game", "Bullet in a Bible", "The Biggest Thing Since Colossus ..."], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Fade 2 Black - The Mixtape", "Dookie", "The Lost Tapes: Limited Edition", "Listen to This Eddie"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["This Left Feels Right: Greatest Hits With a Twist", "Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home", "Thriller", "Nimrod"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Live Tracks", "With the Lights Out", "Farewell I Tour: Live from Melbourne", "The Big Picture"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["39/Smooth", "The Very Best of The Doors", "Come Around Sundown", "Then Play On"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["Star Power", "December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)", "Live in Vancouver", "Time and a Word"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Green Day?", "answers": ["7800\u00b0 Fahrenheit", "Wasted Time (Minneapolis 25-02-1995)", "\u00a1Dos!", "The Chocolate Invasion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lana Del Rey?", "answers": ["Lana Del Ray a.k.a. Lizzy Grant", "4 CD Catalogue Set", "The Woman in Black", "On the Radio"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Lana Del Rey?", "answers": ["Never Say Never: The Remixes", "Eminem is Back", "Born to Die", "Right In Two"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Lana Del Rey?", "answers": ["Live At Reading", "Bob Dylan at Budokan", "Madonna", "Die for Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Legacy: The Absolute Best", "I'm Breathless", "Retrospective I: 1974-1980", "Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["The Best of Snoop Dogg", "Friends In High Places", "Archives", "Cash Cow"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Keep On Skanking", "Creatures of the Night", "The Underground Collection", "Exit...Stage Left"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Rare", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "2112", "TRON: Legacy R3CONF1GUR3D"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Pure Heroine", "Greatest Hits Vol 1", "A Bigger Bang", "Hemispheres"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["B-Sides", "Nevermind It's an Interview", "R30: 30th Anniversary World Tour", "All Access Europe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Beatles \u201965", "Natural Mystic", "17 Numbers by the Beast", "Profiled"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Speak Now", "Rock the Nation Live!", "Clockwork Angels", "The Purple Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Kiss Land", "Retrospective III: 1989x13x32x30x30x38", "December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)", "Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Profiled", "MGMT", "Gold", "Pac-Man Punch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Tha Block Is Hot", "The Seventh Coming", "Fly by Night", "Live at Bonnaroo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Prism", "Ten", "Time Stand Still: The Collection", "Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Exit... Stage Left", "Lollipop (remix)", "Stop That Train", "Garage Inc."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Reunion", "Believers Never Die \u2013 Greatest Hits", "Retrospective II: 1981-1987", "Breakout"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["19", "Daft Club", "The Studio Albums 1989-2007", "The Essential Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Carry the Cross", "Time Machine 2011: Live in Cleveland", "Hangami Halaat", "\u00a1Uno!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Moving Pictures", "All Eyez on Me", "The Sabbath Stones", "Call And Response: The Remix Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Rush Replay X 3", "Stone Age", "Loyal to the Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Trilogy", "Live at the Gorge 05/06", "Rush - Profiled!", "Beast over Hammersmith"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Golden Ballads", "King of Reggae", "Sector 1", "Piece of Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Power Windows", "Bare Trees", "Heroes and Heroin", "Black Tie White Noise"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Hold Your Fire", "Get Well Soon...", "NKOTBSB", "Revenge"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["How the West Was Won", "Coexist", "Rush", "The Urethra Chronicles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Permanent Waves", "Pink Friday", "Science & Faith", "Can't Take Me Home"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["The Massacre", "Snakes & Arrows Live", "8 Mile", "Greatest Hits II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["The Archives Vol. 1 1963\u20131972", "Virgin Songs", "Anatomy of a Drum Solo", "A Momentary Lapse of Reason"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Vapor Trails", "DJ A-Trak & Kanye West: Welcome 2 Kanye's Soul Mix Show", "Happy People / U Saved Me", "The Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Backspacer", "Everything Your Listeners Ever Wanted to Hear by Rush... But You Were Afraid to Play", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Archangel Rides Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Through the Camera Eye", "Let It Be... Naked", "Teenage Dream", "5 Album Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Grace Under Pressure", "Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "Tonight", "Zanjeer -The Game Changer"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["All the World's a Stage", "17-11-70", "American III: Solitary Man", "Best 99"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["The Spirit of Radio: Greatest Hits 1974-1987", "The Slim Shady LP", "Gold Digging: As Sampled By Kanye West", "Touching Heaven Changing Earth"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Different Stages Live", "Re-ac-tor", "Out of Our Heads", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Freestyle B4 Paystyle", "Music & Me", "Unified:Praise", "Signals"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Rush ABC: Live from Cleveland\u2019s Agora Ballroom 1974", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Oxford's Angels", "Golden Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["(A) Katy Perry", "Crush", "Rock Island Line", "Grace Under Pressure Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Feedback", "The Eminem Show", "The Union", "A Total Waste of Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Live at Wembley Stadium", "Elvis Presley", "The Early Years", "Snakes & Arrows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Tha Last Meal", "Caress of Steel", "\u00a1Tr\u00e9!", "Maximum Rock N' Roll"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["The Singles Collection", "Tracks Through Time", "Greatest Kiss", "The Bright Midnight Sampler"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Rich Gang: Flashy Lifestyle", "HIStory", "Sector 2", "ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin Remasters", "A Farewell to Kings", "The Remix", "Serious Moonlight"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Platinum Collection \u201999", "Moonwalker", "Counterparts", "Live at Last"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Can\u2019t Back Down", "R30 - Live in Frankfurt", "Best Of", "Californication"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Minutes To Midnight", "*NSYNC", "Presto", "Gone Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Rush Through Time", "Lost Highway", "Insomniac", "Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Rush in Rio", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "Live At Easy Street", "Gangster and a Gentleman"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Riverside Blues", "DJ Mix", "Roll the Bones", "Saved"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Cabin Fever 2", "Chronicles", "Hotel California", "The Hits: Chapter One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Ben", "Fortune", "Test for Echo", "One of These Nights"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Rush?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Rock!", "A Show of Hands", "News of the World", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Young Americans", "The Essential Mariah Carey", "God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project", "Trilogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Profiled", "Pre-Illmatic", "Live at the Riverboat 1969", "Nirvana"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Beginning of the N VLS", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "The Film-soundtrack", "Who's That Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Immaculate Collection", "Mechanical Bull", "8 Mile", "Carry the Cross Chapter Two (The Rebirth)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["From Ashy to Classy", "Death of Escobar", "Hot Space", "Golden Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Fragile", "The Illmatic Collection", "From the Vaults Vol.4", "Speak My Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Lick It Up", "Greatest Hits", "Double Platinum", "All That Glitters Is Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Slap Happy", "Stillmatic", "Indigo Nights", "No More Thank Yous"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["\u00c7a Ira", "Master of Puppets", "Yesstories", "The Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Lost Tapes", "Small Axe", "Good Morning to the Night", "Live in Pittsburgh 1970"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Recharged", "Blood on the Tracks", "Unidos Permanecemos", "God's Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Nigger Tape", "Live at Pompeii", "Wrecking Ball", "TP3 Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Acid Attack", "It Was Written", "18 Months", "The Ultimate Yes: 35th Anniversary Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Texas (San Antonio)", "The One", "Going No Where", "Nas & Ill Will Records Presents QB's Finest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["At the Beeb", "Remix Project", "Teenage Dream", "The Seventh Coming"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Life Is Good", "The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "Rasta Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["I Am...", "Comes a Time", "The Winter Album", "The Best of Nirvana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Lost Tapes: Limited Edition", "Farewell I Tour (Bonus Disk)", "Future Games", "A Nice Pair"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Best of Nas", "West Coast Seattle Boy: The Jimi Hendrix Anthology", "On the Radio", "Gold"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Elvis Movies", "Black Holes and Revelations", "Untitled Nas album", "21st Century Breakdown"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Con Todo", "Ring the Alarm: Remixes", "Ozzy Meets the Priest", "Street's Disciple"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Living With War", "Distant Relatives", "Babel", "Rare Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Carter Files", "Seven Bridges Road", "Illmatic", "Something to Remember"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["It Was... Remixed (Rare Unreleased & remixed)", "Target Exclusive", "Live at the Hollywood Bowl", "Sugar Mountain - Live At Canterbury House 1968"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Kiss Land", "The Lost Tapes 2", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Physical Graffiti"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Led Zeppelin Boxed Set 2", "The Eminem Show", "One Love: 20 Greatest Hits", "The Prophecy"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["American III: Solitary Man", "Video Anthology Vol. 1", "Discovery", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Big Generator", "Freedom", "Hip Hop Is Dead", "Studio Daze"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["NASA Music 2: Space Dreams", "Power Flower Trouble Fruits", "Nastradamus", "Men of the World: The Early Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["Carry the Cross", "One Day in Your Life", "By Your Side", "The Ozzy Osbourne Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nas?", "answers": ["The Lost Prophecy", "Sticky Fingers", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "Live Santa Monica \u201972"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Shindig Demo", "HOWWA 2", "Physical Graffiti", "Early Classics"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Live in Praha", "Trans", "Ready 2 Die", "Cross Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Teenage Dream: The Complete Confection", "Pablo Honey", "Live at Wembley Stadium", "Sabotage"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Dream Factory", "Oxford Devils", "Snoop Dogg Presents...Doggy Style Allstars Vol. 1", "Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Live from Le Cabaret", "Live Licks", "Tree Full of Secrets", "Kill All: The Rarities Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Malice N Wonderland", "Best of 2Pac", "Greatest Hits: The Ultimate Collection", "Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["not my fault", "Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970", "Live at the BBC", "The X Factor"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Me & This Army: Radiohead Remixes", "He Touched Me", "Exit... Stage Left", "Best of Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Satisfy My Soul", "Weird Scenes Inside the Gold Mine", "Kiss Chronicles: 3 Classic Albums", "The Bends"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["The Green Day Collection", "R.", "Towering Above the Rest", "Dead Perspective"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged", "Rasta Revolution", "Alive!", "Acid Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Ale to the Thieves", "The Wanted (Special Edition)", "Sabbath Bloody Sabbath", "A Day at the Races"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["FoREVer", "Live in Philadelphia '70", "Physical Graffiti", "Unplugged Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Outcesticide: In Memory of Kurt Cobain", "Climbing Up the Walls", "The Singles", "A Matter of Life and Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Pistol of Fire", "The Greatest: Duets", "Twilight of the Gods", "Unplugged: The Complete Acoustic Sessions"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Computer K.O.", "TRON: Legacy", "Live", "Warning! High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Rock!", "Project Revolution", "Radiohead Box Set", "Best of Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Melodic Flea Way", "Symbolic Beginning", "Acid Attack", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Gold Digging: As Sampled By Kanye West", "Better Dayz", "B-Sides", "Master of Puppets"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Experience", "On Another Planet", "Greatest Hits 98", "La voix du Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Stone Age", "Good as I Been to You", "World Ballads Collection", "Christmas in the Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "The Crown", "Oxford's Angels", "Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["A Total Waste of Time", "Best Tour", "Decade", "Les 50 Plus Belles Chansons"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Tha Dogg: The Best of the Works...", "Kid A", "True (Deluxe Edition)", "Pearl Jam"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Behind the Iron Curtain", "A Rush of Blood to the Head / Parachutes", "Death on the Road", "Hail to the Thief"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Who Then Now?", "Radiohead for Haiti", "Freshmen Adjustment", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions (American Land Edition)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Fuck Death Row", "Dungeon Demo", "A Thing Called Love", "Youngest Head Nigga in Charge (Hub City Threat: Minor of the Year)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["NASA Music", "Gagging Order: Acoustic Renditions", "Reunion", "Backstage and Dangerous: The Private Rehearsal"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Rocks Germany 2001", "\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\" 2\"", "Cheshire Cat", "Black Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Asylum", "I'll Stay Me", "Manic Hedgehog demo tape", "Waking The Fallen Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Drama", "Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "I Might Be Wrong: Live Recordings", "Lulu"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Good Morning to the Night", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "I Can't Live", "The Most Gigantic Lying Mouth of All Time"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["4 CD Catalogue Set", "Wicked Man's Rest", "Early Classics", "OK Computer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Looking Back at...", "Bob Marley: Double the Hits", "God He Reigns", "Looking Back to Yesterday"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "Still Life", "...Baby One More Time", "Ron McGovney's '82 Garage Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["The King of Limbs Live From the Basement", "[a_CROSS//the_EARTH]:: Tear Down The Walls", "What About Now", "Get Yer Ya-Ya's Out!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Top Dogg", "In Rainbows", "X", "\u00a1Tr\u00e9!"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["TKOL RMX 1234567", "Le Noise", "Toy", "Bright Midnight: Live in America"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Mimi", "The Dark Side of the Moon", "Remix Project", "Youth and Young Manhood / Aha Shake Heartbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "5 Album Set", "A Day at the Races", "Sucka Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Ride the Lightning", "Raretrax 2", "Woodstock 99", "In the Zone / Britney"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Love and War", "Amnesiac", "Whole Lotta Rock!", "Led Zeppelin"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Loud", "Virtual XI", "Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life", "27-5-94: The Astoria London Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Boxed", "In Rainbows: From the Basement", "True Blue", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["The Golden Unplugged Album", "The Diving Board", "Da Drought 2", "Elvis in Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Africa Unite: The Singles Collection", "Live at the 10 Spot", "Presence", "City of Evil"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Tha Last Meal", "B-Sides of the Beast", "The King of Limbs", "For All You've Done"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Creatures of the Night", "Idiot Computer", "Backstage and Dangerous: The Private Rehearsal", "Introducing\u2026 The Beatles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Radiohead?", "answers": ["Tha Carter III", "Lost Treasures 1993-1997", "90125", "This Left Feels Right Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Unorthodox Jukebox", "Unbroken", "Dedication 2", "18 Tracks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Got to Be There", "Elvis Presley", "Jimi Plays Monterey", "Can\u2019t Back Down"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["The Pious Bird of Good Omen", "Hyde Park Live", "Devil in a Blue Dress", "Demi"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Psycho Circus", "Outakes and Demos 1985-1988", "Nevermind It's an Interview", "Camp Rock 2: Live Walmart Soundcheck"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Don't Forget", "Five Feet High and Rising", "3121", "Kornography"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["The Final Riot!", "Neon Lights", "Binaural", "Led Zeppelin II"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Here We Go Again", "The James Arthur Collection", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome", "Union"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Live: Walmart Soundcheck CD+DVD", "Led Zeppelin III", "Dynamic Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Demi Lovato?", "answers": ["Any Given Thursday", "Demi Lovato", "The Music of Korn", "God's Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["The Plasma Shaft", "Box of Tricks", "Greatest Hits... So Far!!!", "Humbug"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Live on Air", "Live @ The Apollo", "Bigger Boys and Stolen Sweethearts", "S.Carter Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["72826", "Doorie", "Beneath the Boardwalk", "Celebration: The Video Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Daft Punk Live in NYC", "Boston Blues", "The Division Bell", "Favourite Worst Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Suck It and See", "White America", "Rock in Rio", "Alive"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["AM", "Steel Wheels", "Rainbow Show", "Days Are Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Live in Texas: 7 June 2006", "Backstreet Boys", "Kiss Land", "Greatest Kiss"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Scummy Man", "Topography: The Yes Anthology", "Best of Both Worlds Concert", "Trapped in the Closet"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Arctic Monkeys?", "answers": ["Profiled", "Lively Up", "Metallurgy", "At the Apollo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Everybody Loves a Nut", "E=MC\u00b2", "Ale to the Thieves", "Sleeping With the Past"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Johnny Cash With His Hot and Blue Guitar", "Ballbreaker", "Pure Michael: Motown a Cappella", "Awesome as Fuck"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Flies on the Soundboard", "Rock Island Line", "Live at Eddie's Attic"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["I Walk the Line", "The Anger Management Tour Live", "Alphabet St.", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["YesYears", "Madonna", "Orange Blossom Special", "Live in Australia with the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheap", "Greatest!", "Anyway", "Live at the Royal Albert Hall 1970"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Art of Letting Go", "The Legend of Johnny Cash", "The Miracle", "The Bible According to Black Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Best of the Wailers", "Gone Girl", "NASA Music", "Kush & Orange Juice"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Write Me Back", "The Big Picture", "The Johnny Cash Children's Album", "Led Zeppelin II"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Very Best Of", "Death of Escobar", "The James Arthur Collection", "VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Jewels", "The Pursuit of Freedom", "Daft Punk Live in NYC", "Man in Black"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The I Heart Revolution: We're All in This Together", "The Essential Johnny Cash", "The Kings of Hell", "Triumphant (Remixes)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Bitter Tears", "Cabala", "The Complete Doors Studio Albums", "Flight School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Kiss", "Seventh Star", "Every Song Tells a Story", "No Sleep 'Til NYC"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Gold Collection 1970-1971", "Tha Carter III: The Rebirth", "Digital Decks", "At Folsom Prison"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["ChangesTwoBowie", "16 Biggest Hits", "Magnification", "Time Out of Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["xero", "American Recordings", "Led Zeppelin III", "Past Lives"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Greatest: Duets", "American Life/Music", "In Concert", "Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Laban Nating Lahat Ito", "English Rose", "Labyrinth", "Sings the Ballads of the True West"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Rasta Revolution", "Dylan & The Dead", "Hymns by Johnny Cash", "Live at the Fillmore East"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Collaborations", "Let There Be Rock", "Berlin Trilogy", "From Sea to Shining Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["At San Quentin", "Live in New York City", "The Beatles 1967-1970", "Soul Rebels"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Nu-Mixx Klazzics", "Death on the Road", "Jal Pari", "Silver"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Legend", "Friday Night Lights", "Distant Relatives", "Band of Gypsys 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["It's Only Rock'n Roll", "Lucky Town", "A Thing Called Love", "Cosmic Climb"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["By Your Side", "Panjaban", "Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming", "Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Songs of Our Soil", "Double Up", "Dookie", "For the Fans (disc 2)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Best of The Doors", "Boom Chicka Boom", "Greatest Hits", "The Singles Collection Volume 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Complete Studio Albums (1983-2008)", "The Platinum Collection", "Unearthed", "Dreaming Out Loud"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Bends", "Best 99", "Gridlock'd", "The Gospel Road"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Singles", "Stone Age", "Dedication 2", "Five Feet High and Rising"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Division Bell", "Vintage Years", "20 Greatest Hits", "Ring of Fire: The Best of Johnny Cash"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Sunday Morning Coming Down", "Love Death Travel Box Set", "Sorry 4 the Wait", "ICON"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Second Night Unplugged", "The Winter Album", "Flashpoint", "American III: Solitary Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Talk That Talk", "Johnny Cash: The Complete Columbia Album Collection", "The Slim Shady LP", "Jumping at Shadows: The Blues Years"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Pin Ups", "Personal File", "Christmas Duets", "Best 99"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Avenged Sevenfold", "Pink's fifth studio album", "Ragged Old Flag", "A Night Out with the Backstreet Boys"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Clockwork Angels", "Moist Vagina", "The Best of J. Hova", "American VI: Ain't No Grave"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Fabulous Johnny Cash", "Things Falling Apart", "Open Your Eyes", "Uprising"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Unchained", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2", "Live at Last", "Jay-Z: Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Emancipation of Mimi", "Oh Mercy", "So You Wanna Freestyle?", "Sunday Down South"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["SQ5", "Land of the Free Home of the Brave", "Absolution", "Metallica Live in Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["The Pious Bird of Good Omen", "The Very Best", "Greatest Hits", "Ride This Train"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Box Set", "The 2nd Law", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Ed Hunter"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["Strawberry Cake", "The Don Killuminati: The 7 Day Theory", "These Days", "Love You Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets", "Reggae Legends", "Rocafella", "Nu-Mixx Klazzics Vol. 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Johnny Cash?", "answers": ["A Matter of Life and Death", "American V: A Hundred Highways", "The Complete Studio Albums (1983-2008)", "The Original Soul of Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jessie J?", "answers": ["Rocket Man: Number Ones", "Sorry 4 the Wait", "Cash Cow", "Alive"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jessie J?", "answers": ["Iron Man 2", "Road to Revolution: Live at Milton Keynes", "Who You Are", "Mighty to Save"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by K.Michelle?", "answers": ["Animalize Live Uncensored", "Things Falling Apart", "Numb", "Rebellious Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by K.Michelle?", "answers": ["Recharged", "As Is: Volume One", "Speak Now - World Tour Live", "0 Fucks Given"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by K.Michelle?", "answers": ["Crash My Party", "Union Live", "What's The 901?", "Get the Funk Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by K.Michelle?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "For Colored Girls/Pre-Pain Medicine", "Doggystyle", "Trap-A-Velli"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Live in the LBC & Diamonds in the Rough", "Survival", "American Pie + Best Songs", "In the Flesh - Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Bright Midnight: Live in America", "Shine a Light", "The Confessions Tour", "When the Wind Blows"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Discovery", "Eye's and Imagination", "\u00c7a Ira", "Recharged"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["S.Carter Collection", "Greatest Hits '94", "Da Drought 2", "Amused to Death"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Archives", "Greatest Hits 1973-1982", "Live from SoHo", "The Wall: Live in Berlin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["United We Stand", "Christmas", "Radio K.A.O.S.", "Chocolate Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Love Land", "Sonic Boom", "The Pros and Cons of Hitch Hiking", "Retrospective II: 1981-1987"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["Flickering Flame: The Solo Years Volume 1", "Moving Pictures", "Eponyme", "Welcome to tha Chuuch: Da Album"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Roger Waters?", "answers": ["A Beautiful World", "The Eternal Legacy", "Live from London", "Music From the Body"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Natural Mystic: The Legend Lives On", "Archives", "The Razors Edge", "High Voltage"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["TP-2.com", "Magnification", "The Best of Bob Marley and The Wailers", "Justified"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Pyass", "Live @ Glastonbury '08-live album", "Nu-Mixx Klazzics Vol. 2", "Freedom Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Death of Escobar", "Kiss Unplugged", "Chances Are", "Love You Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Farewell My Summer Love", "The Definitive Collection", "Gold", "Live Licks"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Complete Upsetter Collection", "Live Rust", "Rock 'n' Roll Music", "KISS Alive! 1975-2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Gagging Order: Acoustic Renditions", "Natty Dread", "Hallucinogenic Recipe", "Trilogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["All the Little Lights", "Ego Trippin'", "Grooving Kingston 12", "Best Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Queen Rocks", "Sigh No More", "Mighty to Save", "Greatest Hits at Studio One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Rare Masters", "Chant Down Babylon", "VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The I Heart Revolution: We're All in This Together", "King Creole", "Wail'n Soul'm Singles Selecta", "The Soft Parade"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Mob Rules", "Live at S\u00f6dra Teatern", "The 50th Anniversary Collection", "Soul Rebels"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Legend of Johnny Cash", "Michael Jackson's This Is It", "Live at the Roxy", "Believe"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Raretrax 2", "The Sabbath Collection", "Confrontation", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["And All that Could Have Been", "Permanent Waves", "Road to Recovery: Withdrawal", "Soul Revolution 1 & 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["KISS Alive! 1975-2000", "The Best of Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac", "Mellow Moods", "Girl 6"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Who's That Girl", "God He Reigns", "The Birth of a Legend", "The Prophecy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Singles", "Live at S\u00f6dra Teatern", "King of Reggae", "Neil Young"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Yesstories", "Ozzy Meets the Priest", "Songs of Freedom", "Makaveli 5: Thug Passion"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Fabulous Johnny Cash", "Sound + Vision", "Rock to the Rock", "Ciara"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Golden Unplugged Album", "Lil Wayne: Suffix", "Survival", "The Original Soul of Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Legend: The Best of Bob Marley and the Wailers", "Lollapalooza '92", "On the Radio", "Me & This Army: Radiohead Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Tumbleweed Connection", "B Is for Bob", "The Indispensable Collection", "The Remix"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Kaya", "BBC Archives", "Friends In High Places", "Fleetwood Mac in Chicago"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Black Sabbath: The Dio Years", "Leather Jackets", "Destroyer- Resurrected", "Rebel Music"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Plug Me In", "The Lion King", "Some Girls", "Kinky Reggae"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon III", "Born into the 90's", "Stop That Train", "Black Ice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Kingdom Come", "Triumphant (Remixes)", "Satisfy My Soul", "Random Access Memories"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Collection", "21", "2Pacalypse Now", "Uprising"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["G.I. Blues", "Lively Up", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "2 Tracks Demo"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "A Bigger Bang", "Exodus", "The Beatles at the Hollywood Bowl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Roots of a Legend", "Kiss Instant Live", "Fire: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Riot!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Soul Adventurer", "Greatest Hell's Hits", "Touching Heaven Changing Earth", "I Am Not a Human Being II"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2", "Boy in Detention", "The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition", "One Love at Studio One"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Best of the Wailers", "Camp Rock 2: Live Walmart Soundcheck", "The Passion of Tupac", "Cornerstone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Catch a Fire", "Revolution", "American V: A Hundred Highways", "Got to Be There"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The 2nd Law", "Kingdom Come", "Fecal Matter", "One Love: The Very Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Doggystyle", "Alive III", "Labyrinth", "Talkin' Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Take Care", "Reggae Legend", "American Life/Music", "The Hits 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Chrome Dreams II", "Live at Wembley", "Legend Remixed", "Heart of Jamaica"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Outcesticide III: The Final Solution", "Keep On Skanking", "HAARP", "Peter Green's Fleetwood Mac"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Collectors Box", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Darlene Zschech", "I Might Be Wrong: Live Recordings", "News of the World"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Africa Unite: The Singles Collection", "Rocket Man: Number Ones", "American Life", "Aftermath"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Reggae Legends", "The Best Of", "Outcesticide III: The Final Solution", "Darkness on the Edge of Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Rasta Revolution", "Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "Live at Wembley", "Fly by Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["The Paradigm Shift", "Dressed to Kill", "Bones", "African Herbsman"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Soul Captive", "Live!", "TKOL RMX 1234567", "Pistol of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Only By the Night", "To the Ends of the Earth", "Marley", "The Music of Korn"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Woodstock '99 Live Set", "Fan Can 4", "Coexist", "Rastaman Vibration"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bob Marley & The Wailers?", "answers": ["Psychedelic Pill", "Number Ones", "Babylon by Bus", "Solo Sessions Vol. 1: Live at the Knitting Factory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Newman?", "answers": ["Tribute", "Bob Marley: Double the Hits", "Gone Girl", "Union Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Outcesticide III: The Final Solution", "Showbiz", "Goodbye Lullaby", "2Pacalypse Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "Big Hits (High Tide and Green Grass)", "Fantasy Ride", "Maximum 2Pac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Catching Up With the B Sides", "Live in New York City", "Best Hits", "Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Off the Wall", "Me Against the World", "The Final Riot!", "G.I. Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Before I Self Destruct: The Selects", "Greatest Hits", "Sounding the Seventh Trumpet", "All Pink Everything"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Crazy Nights", "Let It Be", "Until the End of Time", "Metallica Live in Concert"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The Essential Elvis Presley", "Makaveli 6: Thug 4 Life", "Lights", "Hard Candy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Chapter One", "Live at Montreux 2003", "The Essential Korn", "Best of 2Pac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Mylo Xyloto", "American Life/Music", "Westside Reloaded", "2pac"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["In His Own Words", "Lady Samantha", "Live @ Lowlands (24.08.2001)", "The Very Best"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The Passion of Tupac", "Magna Carta... Holy Grail", "Music from the Major Motion Picture Crossroads", "No Ceilings"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Green Shadows", "For Bon Far Gone", "Nimrod", "The Here After"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Never Say Never: The Remixes", "The Birth of a Legend", "2Pac & Friends", "Elvis Now"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["\"\"\"Heroes\"\"\"", "Yestoday", "Girlfriend (Junkie XL Remix)", "Live 2 Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["On Stage", "Nu-Mixx Klazzics", "Yesshows", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Rare Masters", "The Revival", "The Prophet Returns", "Hard Candy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["All Eyez on Me", "Future Games", "Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere", "A Real Live One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Planet Earth", "Let It Bleed", "Live at Wembley", "Gridlock'd"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Picture My Pain", "What You Don't Know", "Hallucinogenic Recipe", "Fly on the Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Rock!", "Based On a T.R.U. Story", "Piece of Mind", "Thug Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["By the Way", "Only in America", "Greatest Hits", "The Ultimate Fan Extras Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Shakurspeare", "More Malice", "Plug Me In", "The Miracle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Live at the House of Blues", "The First Ten Years: The Videos", "Tha Unreleased Vol. 1", "The Very Best of the Eagles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Still I Rise", "Greatest Hits", "What Hits!?", "Full Circle"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["What Hits!?", "Beginnings: The Lost Tapes 1988\u20131991", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 2", "Snoop Dogg Presents Christmas in tha Dogg House"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Better Dayz", "Chapter One: Greatest Hits", "Sign 'O' the Times", "Fleetwood Mac"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The Rose That Grew From Concrete", "Flight School", "Folie \u00e0 Deux", "The Bonez Tour 2004: Avril's 20th Birthday Party"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "Recovery", "MTV Unplugged in New York", "2Pac Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Bad 25", "Queen in Nuce", "R U Still Down? (Remember Me)", "Visionary: The Video Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Soul Rebel & Other Great Reggae Hits", "Makaveli 2: The Lost Album", "Sector 1", "Eagles Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Brutal Artistry", "The Prophet: The Best Of The Works", "Long.Live.A$AP", "The Rainbow Children"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Time Machine 2011: Live in Cleveland", "The Lost Prophecy", "The Way He Wanted It", "Family Values Tour '98"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Oops! I Did It Again: The Best Of Britney Spears", "Radiohead for Haiti", "Loyal to the Game", "For This Cause"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Makaveli 5: Thug Passion", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 3", "12 Play", "Epic"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["TRON: Legacy", "Brand New Eyes", "Bonez Tour 2005: Live at Budokan", "Makaveli 6"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Live", "Makaveli 7: Lost Souls", "The Buddha of Suburbia", "The Lion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Over the Counter", "The Album Collection", "New orleans nightmare", "Makaveli 4: Thug in Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Never Done Before", "Limitless and Free", "A Decade of Silence", "Artpop"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Road Rock Vol. 1", "Tamar", "The First Ten Years: The Videos", "Ghetto Superstar"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Beatles VI", "Climbing to New Lows", "The Don Killuminati: The 7 Day Theory", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The Prequel", "Tattoo You", "Make It or Break It Videos", "The Collection 1973-84"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Moody Blue", "Makaveli 8", "Yessongs", "Low"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Live in Pittsburgh 1970", "In Da Hood", "Nu-Mixx Klazzics Vol. 2", "Hands All Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The First Ten Years", "Makaveli 2: When My Enemies Fall", "Eponyme", "Snoop Dogg Presents: Unreleased Heatrocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["The Collection: Britney Spears", "Unapologetic", "Throw Your Dubs Up", "Pac's Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Paramore", "Show Your Glory", "Tupac: Resurrection", "The Best of Bob Marley"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Makaveli 2000", "American Gangster", "Greatest Street Hitz", "In My Zone 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Down in the Groove", "Strictly 4 My N.I.G.G.A.Z...", "More Boring Days", "VH1 Storytellers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Tupac Shakur?", "answers": ["Guess Who's Back?", "Freedom", "An Evening With", "Ready 2 Die"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Singing Between the Lines", "Mischief: The Mixtape", "The Ultimate Collection", "Love in the Future"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Pure Michael: Motown a Cappella", "Bowie at the Beeb: The Best of the BBC Radio Sessions 68-72", "Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "Dedication: Gangsta Grillz"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["His Hand in Mine", "Hannah Montana: Hits Remixed", "Classic", "The Sabbath Stones"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Live at River Plate", "Thriller 25 Super Deluxe Edition", "Yes", "Best of Yes"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Awesome as Fuck", "Dynasty", "Essential Rarities", "Hello World: The Motown Solo Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Essential Bob Dylan", "50 Best Songs \u2013 The Motown Years: Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Live in Detroit", "Classic Queen"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Division Bell", "Live at Big Day Out 2000", "Yes", "Off the Wall"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Dangerous", "Led Zeppelin II", "Continuum", "The Collection: Britney Spears"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Live", "One Love at Studio One", "Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2", "The Remix Suite"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Fuckin' Crazy", "Tunnel of Love", "Horsemen of the Apocalypse", "Michael Jackson's This Is It"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Definitive Collection", "Live at the Fillmore East", "iTunes Festival: London 2011", "Out in L.A."], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["King of Pop", "Graduation", "Bob Marley: Double the Hits", "The Best of Tool"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Fragile", "The Uplift Mofo Party Plan", "Moonwalker", "Controversy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Best Selection", "Hyde Park Live", "Prince of the City 2", "Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The 50th Anniversary Collection", "Music & Me", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Blood on the Dance Floor (HIStory in the mix)", "The Song Remains the Same", "The Chosen Rejects", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Freaky Styley", "Bad 25", "Lively Up", "The Promise: The Darkness on the Edge of Town Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Snoop Dogg - We Da West Vol 1", "Thriller", "Believe", "Pulse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Best of Michael Jackson", "Queen in Nuce", "The Buddha of Suburbia", "The Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Clinton Sparks Presents: Jay-Z: Live Concert on Smash", "Cash Cow", "What About Now", "The Essential Michael Jackson"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Love Letter", "The Captain & the Kid", "The Rose That Grew From Concrete", "Number Ones"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Studio Albums 1989-2007", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 2", "Room for Improvement", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Live in Australia with the Melbourne Symphony Orchestra", "I Am... World Tour", "The Ultimate Fan Extras Collection", "Live. Love. ASAP"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Live Magic", "The Stripped Mixes", "Maiden England", "Pablo Honey"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Club Remixes", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "The 20/20 Experience", "Thriller 25"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Brand New Eyes", "Michael Jackson & The Jackson 5", "Human After All", "A Single Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Original Soul of Michael Jackson", "Burning Desire", "Youth and Young Manhood / Aha Shake Heartbreak", "Kiss & Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Best of 2Pac", "HOWWA 2", "Anthology", "GRRR!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Indispensable Collection", "All Saints", "The Diving Board", "Exit...Stage Left"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["A Collection of Michael Jackson's Oldies", "Live in London: Antipodean Tour Edition", "Yestoday", "Me & This Army: Radiohead Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Visionary: The Video Singles", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "500 Degreez", "Runaway Love (remix)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Live @ Rex Club Paris", "Before I Self Destruct", "Michael", "Gridlock'd"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Rebel Music", "Michael Jackson: Love Songs", "Ego Trippin'", "The Studio Albums 1972-1979"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The 2nd Law", "The Best of Eagles", "Yes", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Past Lives", "The One", "Live at Montreux 2004", "Nastradamus"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Legend Remixed", "Looking Back to Yesterday", "Live At Reading", "Take a Look in the Mirror"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["It's Better to Burn Out Than to Fade Away...", "Live at Wembley Stadium", "Live in Bucharest: The Dangerous Tour", "Burning Desire"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Golden Legends", "2Pac & Friends", "Ben", "Live in Detroit"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Getcha Girl Dogg", "The Birth of a Legend", "One Night in Japan", "Something Else"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["The Singles Collection Volume 1", "Fat Old Gigs", "Michael Jackson Story", "In Da Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Legend of Hip Hop", "The Wiz: Original Motion Picture Soundtrack", "The Downward Spiral / With Teeth", "Lightning Bolt"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Open Your Eyes", "HIStory", "The I Heart Revolution: With Hearts As One", "2004-09-17: Berklee College of Music Clinic"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Space Odyssey", "Confessions on a Dance Floor", "Exile on Main St.", "Michael Jackson's Vision"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Alive", "James Arthur", "Invincible", "Stone's Been Rolled Away"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Immortal", "Gagging Order: Acoustic Renditions", "ITunes Essentials: Avril Lavigne", "Mellow Moods"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Farewell My Summer Love", "Pre Ordained", "Presence", "Greatest Video Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged in New York", "One Day in Your Life", "Live and Fucked Up", "The Marshall Mathers LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["From Ashy to Classy", "Something Else", "The Collection", "Alive!"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Michael Jackson?", "answers": ["Absolution", "Got to Be There", "Woke Up This Morning and Found Myself Dead", "Neidermayer's Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Having a Blast", "Loving the Alien", "Lyrical Homicide", "Woodstock"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Roots of a Legend", "Dream Factory", "Live at Woodstock", "Live in Praha"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Time to Pretend", "For Colored Girls/Pre-Pain Medicine", "Stages", "Goodbye Lullaby"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Drought Is Over Pt. 4", "Roots of a Legend", "First Rays of the New Rising Sun", "Darkness on the Edge of Town"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["More Experience", "Technical Ecstasy", "Overwhelmed", "Everybody's Rockin'"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Rated R: Remixed", "Morning Symphony Ideas", "The Complete Studio Recordings", "Fecal Matter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Live at the Boston Tea Party", "The Beat", "Soundtrack Recordings from the Film Jimi Hendrix", "Love Land"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Band of Gypsys", "Songs From the West Coast", "Number Ones", "Texas (San Antonio)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Experience Hendrix: The Best of Jimi Hendrix", "Reggae Legend", "Archangel Rides Again", "Best of Hannah Montana"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Eye's and Imagination", "Maximum Rock N' Roll", "Live Compilation", "Live in Chicago 05.16.2006"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["A Date With Elvis", "Live From the Atlantic Studios", "Jimi Plays Monterey", "The Fragile"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Dedication 2", "My World", "Isle of Wight", "Pure Michael: Motown a Cappella"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Platinum Collection Volume 1: Shout to the Lord", "Femme Fatale / Circus", "The Kings of Hell", "The Ultimate Experience"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Da Drought 2", "Burning Desire", "World Gone Wrong", "In My Zone 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["I Am\u2026 Sasha Fierce", "Jimi Plays Berkeley", "Original Album Series", "Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Fire: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Maiden England", "The Best of Bob Marley: 35 Greatest", "Oh Mercy"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Early Years", "Strawberry Cake", "Jesus Is My Superhero", "Hendrix in the West"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["To Be Continued...", "Unbreakable", "West Coast Seattle Boy: The Jimi Hendrix Anthology", "Yes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Bleeding Heart", "Freaky Styley", "Hail to the King", "The Chosen Rejects"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Funhouse Tour: Live in Australia", "Woke Up This Morning and Found Myself Dead", "Empire Burlesque", "Live in Praha"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Metal Up Your Ass", "Long Time No See", "The Lost Tapes 2", "Live in Ottawa"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Tailgates & Tanlines", "Lightning Bolt", "Valleys of Neptune", "Caribou"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Lifelines: The Jimi Hendrix Story", "Legend of Hip Hop", "No Prayer for the Dying"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["A Tree with Roots", "Hitstory", "Band of Gypsys 2", "Number Ones"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Just Finish It", "Martin Scorsese Presents the Blues: Jimi Hendrix", "Prairie Wind", "Super Soaker"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)", "Greatest Hits II", "Live at the Fillmore East", "Pop Disaster Tour 2002"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Blues", "Unplugged Again", "Somewhere Back in Time: The Best of 1980-1989", "Project Revolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["At His Best", "The Beatles Stereo Box Set", "Lulu", "The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Mother's Milk", "Collectors Box", "Acoustic Jams", "Justified"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Kiss the Sky", "Lemmings / Going Nowhere / One Track", "All Pink Everything", "Road to Recovery: Withdrawal"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Live/1975-85", "Johnny B. Goode", "Live!", "Overexposed"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Baggy's Rehearsal Sessions", "VH1 Storytellers: Johnny Cash & Willie Nelson", "All Saints", "Story of My Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Bends", "Tree Full of Secrets", "Alive!", "Blue Wild Angel: Live at the Isle of Wight"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Loose Ends", "Exit... Stage Left", "Death of Escobar", "Pistol of Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["A Date With Elvis", "Olympic Gold", "The Essential Jimi Hendrix Volume Two", "Street-Legal"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Love You Live", "The Jimi Hendrix Concerts", "100 Million Bon Jovi Fans Can't Be Wrong", "Purple Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan", "Midnight Lightning", "Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Tha Block Is Hot", "Early Classics", "Live at the Aquarius Theatre: The Second Performance", "Strung Out on Avenged Sevenfold: The String Tribute"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Dance", "Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big", "The Blueprint 2.1", "Crash Landing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["War Heroes", "Common Courtesy", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative", "Sunday Down South"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Live in Cologne", "Quebec Magnetic", "Blackout", "Virgin Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["For Those About to Rock (We Salute You)", "The Very Best of Kiss", "Nine to the Universe", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["The Cry of Love", "In a World Like This", "Journey Through the Past", "A Real Live One"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Voodoo Soup", "Wicked Man's Rest", "Rock of the Westies", "Stripped"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits 1970\u20131978", "The Come Up", "Jimi Hendrix: The Singles Album", "HIStory"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Hangami Halaat", "Experience", "Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs", "Catch a Fire"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["90125", "Rainbow Bridge", "Queen II", "Live in Detroit"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["South Saturn Delta", "Greatest Hits", "The Future Starts Here: The Essential Doors Hits", "The Black Sabbath Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Jimi Hendrix?", "answers": ["Nimrod", "Age of Giants", "More Hot Rocks (Big Hits & Fazed Cookies)", "Voodoo Child: The Jimi Hendrix Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Flickering Flame: The Solo Years Volume 1", "The Album", "The Singles", "A Year Without Rain"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["The Revival", "Rock of the '70s", "Africa Unite: The Singles Collection", "Kiss & Tell"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Voodoo Lounge", "Can't Be Tamed", "When the Sun Goes Down", "Late Registration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Selena Gomez & the Scene?", "answers": ["Michael Jackson's Vision", "The Club Remixes", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "In Brazil: LP"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Oklahoma City 1972", "Battle Studies", "DJ LRM & Stackhouse: Alter Ego", "Argenfornication"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Babel", "Ciara", "My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy", "Gold Collection 1970-1971"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Get the Funk Out", "Creatures of the Night", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome", "Freshmen Adjustment 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Daytrotter Session-live album", "The Mighty Bob Marley", "Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "808s & Heartbreak"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Empire Burlesque", "Class of '06: World's Best Dressed Label Under G.O.O.D Music", "Tamar", "Bon Scott Rarities"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["VH1 Storytellers", "Vampire Weekend", "Sunfly Gold Vol. 34: Linkin Park & Limp Bizkit", "December\u2019s Children (and Everybody\u2019s)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Halcyon Days", "Under Wheels of Confusion", "Second Semester", "FACT Mix 327: Disclosure"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Kiss Instant Live", "All Ice on Me", "Loud", "Freshmen Adjustment"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Love Death Travel Box Set", "The Beatles\u2019 Long Tall Sally", "Another Side of Bob Dylan", "Kon The Louis Vitton Don"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Late Orchestration", "Elvis", "Curtis", "Celebration"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["One Nite Alone... Live!", "Live Tracks", "Power (remix)", "Live from London"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Closure", "Ego Trippin'", "The Late Mixtape", "Magnification"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits '94", "Born to Run: 30th Anniversary Edition", "Greatest Hits", "The Graduate"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Graduation", "Origin of Symmetry", "The Razors Edge", "Isle of Wight"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Kanye West presents: The Lost Tapes", "Led Zeppelin BBC Sessions", "ChangesTwoBowie", "Elton John"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Only By the Night", "Can't Tell Me Nothing: The Official Mixtape", "Born This Way: The Remix", "Welcome To The Dogg House"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Get Well Soon...", "Let's Dance", "Zion", "Dark Emotion"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Lushlife Presents: West Sounds", "Voodoo Child: The Jimi Hendrix Collection", "Best Hits", "June Carter and Johnny Cash: Duets"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["From Ashy to Classy", "Heartache Tonight", "Long Road Out of Eden", "DJ A-Trak & Kanye West: Welcome 2 Kanye's Soul Mix Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["The Hits: Chapter One", "Live at the 10 Spot", "Gold Digging: As Sampled By Kanye West", "Sabbath Bloody Sabbath"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Conscience", "The Platinum Collection Volume 1: Shout to the Lord", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 3", "Seventh Son of a Seventh Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["The College Dropout: Mixtape Version 2", "Amused to Death", "The Eagles / Desperado", "For Bon Far Gone"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["The Woman in Black", "Best of the Beast", "World Without End", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Live", "\"12\"\" Masters: Essential Mixes\"", "Watch the Throne", "Dead Man"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2", "Speak Now - World Tour Live", "The City Is Mine", "The Best of J. Hova"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["The Fame Kingdom", "Thriller", "My Worlds", "Best of Kanye West"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["This Note's for You", "Runaway Love (remix)", "Born This Way", "The Beatles' Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["LeftRightLeftRightLeft", "DJ LRM: Instrumental World", "AC/DC Live", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Reuben Morgan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Time and a Word", "Kanye West Presents: Promise", "Deuce", "Goodies: The Videos & More"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["That's the Way Through the Out Door", "Yeezus", "In His Own Words", "Tyr"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Definitive Collection Mini LP Replica CD Boxset", "Late Registration", "LotusFlow3r", "Magna Carta... Holy Grail"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["At Folsom Prison", "Heathen", "The Beat", "Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big", "Sky High: Presented by DJ Benzi and Plain Pat", "Legacy: The Absolute Best", "Chapter One: Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Kanye West?", "answers": ["The College Dropout", "Magic", "Profiled", "12 Play"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Elvis The King", "The W. Carter Collection 2", "Greatest Hits", "Doin' My Thing"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Tailgates & Tanlines", "T.N.T.", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions (American Land Edition)", "Malice N Wonderland"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Sticky Fingers", "Crash My Party", "Doorie", "Seventh Son of a Seventh Son"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["I'll Stay Me", "Let There Be Rock: The Movie", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions", "Legacy CD1"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Luke Bryan?", "answers": ["Spring Break... Here To Party", "Stop That Train", "Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2", "The Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Reggae Lion", "Common Courtesy", "The Boss Keeps Rockin'", "The Road to Carter 4"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Collection: 1973 - 2012", "Made in Heaven", "Room for Squares", "Strawberry Cake"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Whole Lotta Rock!", "Forever King", "Snoop Dogg Presents: The West Coast Blueprint", "Feyenoord Stadium Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Harvest", "The Rising", "SQ6", "Moving Pictures"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Keystudio", "The Vault... Old Friends 4 Sale", "13", "Bruce Springsteen with The Sessions Band: Live in Dublin"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["\"The Born in the U.S.A. 12\"\" Single Collection\"", "I Can't Live", "Tha Carter", "Best Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["From Nashville to Memphis: The Essential '60s Masters", "Lucky Town", "Sunday Down South", "Babel"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The Remix", "The Essential Bruce Springsteen", "Doggy Stuff", "Top Dogg"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Piece of Mind", "Men of the World: The Early Years", "Video Anthology / 1978\u201388", "The College Dropout: Mixtape Version"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Live in New York City", "Because of the Times", "In the Zone / Circus", "Diary of a Soldier"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["My World", "House of Balloons", "Here's To Ya (Part One)", "Red Hot Skate Rock"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Ballbreaker", "The Solid Gold Collection", "0 Fucks Given", "Original Live Recorded"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Lateralus", "Divers & Submarines", "In Concert MTV Plugged", "Loose Ends"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Inside Black Sabbath \u2013 1970\u20131992", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)", "Flight School"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions", "Absolutely Live", "Metal Up Your Ass", "Live in New York"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Tunnel of Love", "25 Years - The Chain", "By Your Side", "The Freestyle Manual"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "The Ghost of Tom Joad", "Get the Funk Out", "Dehumanizer"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The Complete Blue Horizon Sessions: 1967\u20131969", "Best 99", "This Is Rihanna", "The Eminem Show"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90", "The Best Of", "Wrecking Ball", "Serious Business DJ Clue & Keyz Collaboration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The Urethra Chronicles II: Harder Faster Faster Harder", "Reggae Legend", "The Collection 1973-84", "In the Flesh - Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["More", "Rush Through Time", "Seventh Heaven", "Human Touch"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Beam Me Up Scotty", "Live in Stockholm", "Born in the U.S.A.", "Past Masters"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Blond Ambition - Japan Tour '90", "The Yes Album", "Magic", "Tonight's the Night"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Darkness on the Edge of Town", "4 Way Street", "Metallurgy", "Boy in Detention"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "18 Tracks", "The Best of the Wailers", "Fuckin' Crazy"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Rockin' Live From Italy 1993", "Love", "Space Odyssey", "Jump Back: The Best of the Rolling Stones"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Satisfy My Soul", "Rock in Rio", "Rebel Music", "Another Side of Bruce Springsteen"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["808s & Heartbreak", "Tracks", "Alive!", "Hymns by Johnny Cash"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The River", "Keys to Ascension", "Flick of the Switch", "Class of '55: Memphis Rock & Roll Homecoming"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Garage Inc.", "Icon", "Working on a Dream", "Stage"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Classic Queen", "Devils & Dust", "Promised Land", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["VH1 Storytellers: Uncut", "My Worlds: The Collection", "Live Tracks", "Tokyo Road (live)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Time", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions (American Land Edition)", "Today", "Visionary: The Video Singles"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Born to Run: 30th Anniversary Edition", "Overexposed", "Let There Be Rock", "Greatest Hits 1970-2002"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["The Best of David Bowie 1969/1974", "L.A. Woman", "The Best of the Pink Floyd / Masters of Rock", "In the Heart of Sin City"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Edward the Great", "Peachtree Road", "World Without End", "Nebraska"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Accoustic Concert Live Performance", "Smoking Blues", "Dirty Work", "SQ5"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Girl Happy", "Stiff Upper Lip", "The Ozzy Osbourne Years", "The Promise"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["One of These Nights", "Boss's Birthday Party", "The Wall Singles Collection", "Goodies / The Evolution"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Live/1975-85", "The Remix Suite", "Rumours Outtakes", "The Spirit of Radio: Greatest Hits 1974-1987"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Purple Rain", "The Stripped Mixes", "The Marshall Mathers LP", "The Promise: The Darkness on the Edge of Town Story"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Bruce Springsteen?", "answers": ["Born to Run", "Awake", "Idiot Computer", "The Prophet Returns"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Unsurpassed Masters", "Dreaming Out Loud", "No Strings Attached", "International Villager"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Unidos Permanecemos", "Follow You", "Radiohead Box Set", "Never Done Before"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Lollipop (remix)", "The Rose That Grew From Concrete", "The Essential Fleetwood Mac", "Zanjeer -The Game Changer"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Finally Famous Vol. 3: Big", "Talwar", "The Wanted (Special Edition)", "Loving You"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged", "A Real Live One", "Platinum Collection \u201999", "Jatt Soorme"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["American Stars 'n Bars", "Tha Carter 2.7", "Settle", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Jump Up!", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "The Truth About Love", "Singing Between the Lines"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["American Life/Music", "The Rising Queen", "Highway to Hell", "Piece of Mind"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Outcesticide IV: Rape of the Vaults", "In the Heart of Sin City", "King of Pop", "Born This Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Unrelease V", "Panjaban", "A Collection of Great Dance Songs", "Le Noise"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Merry Christmas II You", "The Next Level", "Yellow Submarine Songtrack", "The Very Best of Prince"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Homework/Discovery", "The Crown", "Warning", "New Jersey: The Videos"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Honey Singh?", "answers": ["Weird Scenes Inside the Gold Mine", "The Definitive Collection", "Trin-i-tee 5:7", "The Beat"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Live at the Roxy", "Late Registration", "Intimidated (Deluxe Edition)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["In the Zone / Britney", "Lost Treasures 1993-1997", "Get the Funk Out", "The Doors \u2013 30 Years Commemorative Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Rumours Outtakes", "Hannah Montana 2 / Meet Miley Cyrus", "The Singles Collection", "Favourite Worst Nightmare"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["The Complete Studio Recordings", "Purgatory / Maiden Japan", "From Ashy to Classy", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative / Live and More!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Blackout", "Under My Skin", "Grow Season", "Revolver"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Key Cuts from Remixed", "Black Album", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "Fat Old Gigs"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["The Division Bell", "Triple Feature", "Insomniac", "Miss Swing Miss Soul"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Orange Blossom Special", "Live in Philadelphia '70", "Madonna: Dalle Origini Al Mito", "In the Zone / Circus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["James Arthur", "Neil Young", "Homesick", "Oops!...I Did It Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "Britney", "Makaveli 6", "Works"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["The Collection: Britney Spears", "\u00a1Uno!", "Section.80", "The Truth About Love"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Devils & Dust", "Born to Run: 30th Anniversary Edition", "Me Against the Music", "I Can't Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter", "The Singles", "American Idiot", "Sigh No More"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Sunday Morning Coming Down", "Elton John and Tim Rice's Aida", "B in the Mix: The Remixes", "Purest Feeling"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Time Out with Britney Spears", "The Best of Nas", "500 Degreez", "Bleeding Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Union", "Missundaztood / Can't Take Me Home", "Changesbowie", "Greatest Hits: My Prerogative"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Playlist: The Very Best of Britney Spears", "Purple Rain", "Black Magic Woman: The Best of Fleetwood Mac", "The Ladder"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Friends", "Circus", "Friends", "One Day in Your Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Shrine '69", "The Beyonc\u00e9 Experience Live", "Oops! I Did It Again: The Best Of Britney Spears", "Who's That Girl"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Purgatory / Maiden Japan", "Le Noise", "Music from the Major Motion Picture Crossroads", "The Singles Boxset (Previously Unreleased bonus disc)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Makaveli 4: Thug in Me", "Dookie", "The Best of the Pink Floyd / Masters of Rock", "Seventh Studio Project"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Caress of Steel", "Studio Daze", "Music & Me", "Britney Spears: Live and More!"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["The Buddha of Suburbia", "Can You Handle Mine?", "American IV: The Man Comes Around", "Live From Wembley Arena"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Morning Symphony Ideas", "Live at Manchester Apollo 30.01.08", "Britney Spears: The Unreleased", "More Boring Days"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Other People's Heartache", "A Tree with Roots", "Femme Fatale / Circus"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Dehumanizer", "Awake", "Gonzaga '68", "Circus / Blackout"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Jimi Plays Berkeley", "2011-06-04: KROQ Weenie Roast 2011-live album", "Tonight", "In the Zone"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["Songs for Communion", "...Baby One More Time", "Stars Dance", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["The Way He Wanted It", "Femme Fatale", "Babylon by Bus", "The Last Supper"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Britney Spears?", "answers": ["U Know Big Sean\u2013Finally Famous Vol. 2", "...Baby One More Time / Oops!... I Did It Again", "Rock to the Rock", "Roots of a Legend"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["The Golden Unplugged Album", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles", "Boot Yer Butt: The Doors Bootlegs", "Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["With Ears to See and Eyes to Hear", "Friday Night Lights", "Dead Man Walkin", "Playtime Is Over"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Family Values Tour '98", "Catching Up With the B Sides", "A Collection", "Beam Me Up Scotty"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["It's Barbie Bitch", "Rhapsody in Pink: The Psychedelic Years", "Proud", "Cunning Stunts"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Cross Purposes Live", "Barbie World: The Mixtape", "Kiss Sonic Boom Over Europe", "The Royal Box"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Dead Man Walkin", "Black Holes and Revelations", "My World 2.0", "Ghetto Barbie"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits Live", "Greatest Hits", "Newpower Soul", "Sucka Free"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["All Pink Everything", "Cabala", "The Road to Carter 4", "Good Girl Gone Bad"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Nicki Minaj?", "answers": ["Metal Up Your Ass", "Comeback Season", "A Year Without Rain", "Pink Friday"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by The 1975?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Facedown", "Ride on Bon", "Try This"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by The 1975?", "answers": ["So Far Gone", "The Nigger Tape", "City of Evil", "IV"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Any Given Thursday", "Madonna: The Confessions Tour", "Elvis: Viva Las Vegas", "Anthology 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Pre Ordained", "As/Is Volume Four: Cleveland/Cincinnati OH 8/03 - 8/04/04", "Live in Texas: 7 June 2006", "By the Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["2004-09-17: Berklee College of Music Clinic", "Alfaaz \u2013 The Boy Next Door", "My President Is Black", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Caress of Steel", "Best Hits", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Battle Studies"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Backstreet's Back", "Wish You Were Here / Early Singles", "1999-06-15: Eddies Attic", "Elvis"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded", "Live Compilation", "Wrecking Ball", "Doggumentary"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["The Torture Never Stops", "Paranoid", "The Eternal Idol", "Where the Light Is: John Mayer Live in Los Angeles"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Mr. Wonderful", "Music From the Body", "Moist Vagina", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1", "Guess Who's Back Again", "As/Is", "Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Sings the Ballads of the True West", "Blaze Of Hits", "As Is: Volume One", "A Momentary Lapse of Reason"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Room for Squares", "Pac's Life", "The One", "Akademiks: Jeanius Level Musik 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Continuum", "Antrabata Sessions", "All the World's a Stage", "Love After War"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Absolute Greatest", "The Soft Parade", "Paradise Valley", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by John Mayer?", "answers": ["Born and Raised", "The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse", "Don't Forget", "In a Valley by the Sea"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Chris Brown", "The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Les Eurock\u00e9ennes de Belfort", "The 20/20 Experience: The Complete Experience"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["FutureSex/LoveSounds", "Live at Montreux 2004", "Purple Sabbath", "Love Death Travel Box Set"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Recrimination", "News of the World", "Contra", "Bonez Tour 2005: Live at Budokan"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["The Evolution of Robin Thicke", "Still Life", "Sector 1", "The 20/20 Experience"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Mr. Timberlake", "Live in NYC 12/31/92", "At the Beeb", "Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Viva Elvis", "All We Know Is Falling", "In Rainbows", "The 20/20 Experience \u2013 2 of 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Antrabata Sessions", "Collaborations", "Bulletproof", "Greatest Hits Live"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Elton John One Night Only \u2013 The Greatest Hits", "Amazing Love", "Soul Rebel - 20 Reggae Hits", "Essential Mixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Live at River Plate", "Merry Christmas II You", "2004-12-29: Webster Hall - John Mayer Plays the Blues"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "The Cry of Love", "Nevermind It's an Interview", "Justified"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Justin Timberlake?", "answers": ["Past Lives", "Live from London", "Con Todo", "The Torture Never Stops"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Adele?", "answers": ["19", "True (Deluxe Edition)", "The W. Carter Collection", "Hot Rocks 1964-1971"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Adele?", "answers": ["Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Miriam Webster", "21", "Celebration", "The Best of Bob Marley and The Wailers"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Adele?", "answers": ["Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome", "Best of Bowie", "Mac & Devin Go to High School", "Greatest Hits"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Adele?", "answers": ["Red Hot Skate Rock", "Mac & Devin Go to High School", "Good Morning to the Night", "1988"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Adele?", "answers": ["Adele Live at the Royal Albert Hall", "iTunes Festival: London 2008", "Limited-Edition Vinyl Box Set", "Innocence And Instinct"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Flight 666 - The Original Soundtrack", "Eponyme", "Acid Attack", "Halcyon"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Symbolic Beginning", "Yours Truly", "Mariah Carey: DVD Collection", "Greatest Hits: The Ultimate Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Gold", "Rocks Germany 2001", "Greatest Hits", "Berlin Trilogy"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Unfinished Business", "The Streets Is Watching", "Rainbow", "Picture My Pain"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Chikara", "A Hard Day\u2019s Night", "Glitter", "13"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Revenge", "Here Is Mariah Carey", "Pink Friday: Roman Reloaded", "On Another Planet"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["I Am Not a Human Being II", "Best Ballads", "Ikons", "Guess Who's Back Again"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Mariah Carey", "Early On (1964-1966)", "Korn Live: The Encounter", "\"\"\"Heroes\"\"\""], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Greatest Hits", "Wake Up!", "Highway to Hell", "Millenium Hits 2000"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Live in Hyde Park", "For You", "The Emancipation of Mimi", "Love and War"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Golden Collection", "Rolling Papers", "'Hours...'", "The Ballads"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Icon", "Touching Heaven Changing Earth", "Johnny Cash With His Hot and Blue Guitar", "Merry Christmas"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Reality", "The Essential Mariah Carey", "We Shall Overcome: The Seeger Sessions", "Evita (The Motion Picture Music Soundtrack)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Tha Massacre (bonus disc)", "Guess Who's Back Again", "Doo-Wops & Hooligans", "Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel Remix Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Singles Collection Volume 1", "Meteora", "E=MC\u00b2 Adventure Box", "The Complete Best Of"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["He Touched Me", "Number 1's", "Comes a Time", "The Best of Bob Dylan"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Best Songs R&B", "Simply Worship Three", "All We Know Is Falling", "In the Heart of Sin City"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Adventures of Mimi", "Gameboy Gaga (Jaysta)", "Yes Remixes", "The Beat"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Homesick", "The One", "Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel", "The Club Remixes"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["West Coast King", "Daydream", "Celebrity", "Sexual Exposure"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Script", "Fragile", "Around the World", "The Wall: Live in Berlin"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["A Decade of Silence", "The Collection", "Playlist: The Very Best of Mariah Carey", "The Lion King"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["\u00a1Tr\u00e9!", "Lil Wayne: Suffix", "MTV Unplugged", "Beauty and the Beast: Slowed Down Sessions (Chapter 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["The Prophecy", "Merry Christmas II You", "Curtain Call: The Hits", "Kingdom Come"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Woke Up This Morning and Found Myself Dead", "FACT Mix 70: The xx", "The Remixes", "How Fly"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Butterfly", "(A) Katy Perry", "Gone Girl", "Never Say Die!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["E=MC\u00b2", "King of the Air Waves", "Live in Vegas Instrumentals", "St. Anger (studio rehearsals)"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Behind the Iron Curtain", "Johnny Cash: The Complete Columbia Album Collection", "Extravagant Worship: The Songs of Reuben Morgan", "Charmbracelet"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Dreamin Man Live '92", "Emotions", "Lost Dogs", "Discovery: Bonus Tracks From daftclub.com"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Battle Studies", "Moody Blue", "(A) Katy Perry", "The Art of Letting Go"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Triumphant (Remixes)", "Led Zeppelin Remasters", "A Collection of Great Dance Songs", "Da Drought 3"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Mariah Carey?", "answers": ["Music Box", "Listen to This Eddie", "MTV Unplugged: Korn", "Uno... Dos... Tr\u00e9!"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Selena Gomez?", "answers": ["MTV Unplugged in New York", "Westside Reloaded", "Stars Dance", "Late Orchestration"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Native", "The Heist", "This Is Rihanna", "The Blueprint 2: The Gift & The Curse"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Box Set", "To Be Continued...", "The Language of My World", "Feedback"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Macklemore?", "answers": ["The VS. Redux", "Live from SoHo", "The Road to El Dorado", "Memoirs of an Imperfect Angel Remix Edition"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Macklemore?", "answers": ["Tiny Desk Concert", "Yesterday\u2026 and Today", "Greatest Hits Vol 1", "Stages"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Macklemore?", "answers": ["God's Gift: The Nas/Jay-Z Project", "The Unplanned Mixtape", "Love After War", "I'll Stay Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Rudimental?", "answers": ["Get Rich or Die Tryin' / The Massacre", "Soul Captive", "Home", "Rated R: Remixed"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Videos 1989\u20132004", "Return of the Champions", "Millennium", "Good Girl Gone Bad (remix bonus disc)"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Charmbracelet", "Boss's Birthday Party", "Queen 40", "The Lost Tapes 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Man on the Moon: The End of Day", "Soul Shakedown Party", "Black Album", "Box of Tricks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Piper at the Gates of Dawn", "Crash Landing", "World Gone Wrong", "Absolute Greatest"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Barbadian Superstardom", "News of the World", "Vol. 3... Life and Times of S. Carter", "Kiss My Ass: The Video"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Singles 1999\u20132006", "BBC Session", "LotusFlow3r", "The Miracle"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Broken Arrow", "Saviour King", "In the Heart of Sin City", "Queen Live at Golders Green Hippodrome"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Cross Purposes Live", "The Singles Collection Volume 3", "Rock of the Westies", "Westside Reloaded"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Mother's Milk", "The Cry of Love", "Brussels Affair (Live 1973)", "The Game"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Kaleidoscope Dream", "Signals", "Live at Wembley '86", "With the Lights Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Breakout: Video Singles", "Queen Rock Montreal", "Meet the Beatles!", "Born This Way"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Live & Rare", "This Is A Muse Demo", "Seek Bromance (Remixes)", "Live Killers"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Queen", "A Collection of Michael Jackson's Oldies", "Elvis' Golden Records", "Kiss Unplugged"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Crown Jewels: A 25th Anniversary Celebration", "1988", "iTunes Originals \u2013 Red Hot Chili Peppers", "Christmas in the Heart"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Atom Heart Mother", "With the Lights Out", "Come Around Sundown", "The Platinum Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Boom Chicka Boom", "Top Dogg", "Made in Heaven", "A Beautiful World"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Prophet Returns", "The Singles Collection Volume 1", "Neighborhoods", "One Love at Studio One"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Pac's Life", "Gold", "Abbey Road", "Innuendo"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["\"In Memory of \"\"Kurdt Kobain\"\"\"", "F.A.M.E.", "Greatest Hits", "American V: A Hundred Highways"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Soul Revolution 1 & 2", "Cigarettes and Valentines", "In Nuce", "Mick Boogie & Kanye West - Second Semester: Kanye Essentials 2"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Queen Ballads", "Live From the Atlantic Studios", "Blonde on Blonde", "Obscured by Clouds"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Hail to the King", "New Jersey", "The Complete Works", "All Eyez on Me"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Music From the Body", "Elvis: Greatest Hits Volume 1", "I Am\u2026 Sasha Fierce", "Queen Rocks"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["A Day at the Races", "Clinton Sparks Presents: Jay-Z: Live Concert on Smash", "Dedication 1", "The Originals"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["As/Is Volume Four: Cleveland/Cincinnati OH 8/03 - 8/04/04", "Brand New Eyes", "A Kind of Magic", "The 50th Anniversary Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["At the Beeb", "Last Night on Earth: Live in Tokyo", "B-Sides of the Beast", "The Confessions Tour"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Undertow", "Forever Gold", "X & Y Live 2005", "Stone Cold Classics (Limited Edition)"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["A Thousand Suns", "Greatest Hits III", "Epic", "Love Letter"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Essential Korn", "Queen II", "Flight 666 - The Original Soundtrack", "Lulu"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Tha Carter IV", "Flash Gordon", "Don't Forget", "In Da Hood"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Retrospective III: 1989x13x32x30x30x38", "Fuck Death Row", "Queen in Nuce", "Everyday Chemistry"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Musicology", "Live Magic", "Snakes & Arrows", "Love Songs"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Madonna: The Confessions Tour", "The Union", "A Night at the Opera", "Road Rock Vol. 1"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["The Queen Collection", "Red String Tribute", "Echoes: The Best of Pink Floyd", "The Collection 1973-84"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Die for Me", "Ultimate Queen", "Binaural", "Acoustic Jams"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Cornerstone", "Morning Symphony Ideas", "Live At Reading", "Queen Collection"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["It's That Girl", "On the Radio", "Me & This Army: Radiohead Remixes", "Sheer Heart Attack"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Graduation", "Hullabaloo Soundtrack", "The Buddha of Suburbia", "Pre Ordained"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Come Around Sundown", "Indigo Nights", "Jewels", "Black Ice"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["A Matter of Life and Death", "Best of Queen", "21", "Soled Out"], "correct_ans_ind": 1}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Born This Way: The Remix", "Prince of the City 2", "Greatest Hits II", "Pac-Man Punch"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Tonite Let's All Make Love in London... Plus", "The Madonna Collection", "Miss Swing Miss Soul", "The Works"], "correct_ans_ind": 3}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Queen on Fire \u2013 Live at the Bowl", "Yes Remixes", "Born to Die", "The Rising"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Hot Space", "Fragile", "Something New", "Dreams of Freedom"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["For Those Who Have Heart", "Alive", "Jazz", "The Best of Nas"], "correct_ans_ind": 2}{"question": "Which is an album by Queen?", "answers": ["Classic Queen", "Indicud", "Science & Faith", "Pac's Life"], "correct_ans_ind": 0}